<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588</link>
    <description>Hi everyone,

We&#39;d like to apologize for not giving you a proper heads-up before replacing the demo sounds! We&#39;ve learned that this has been perceived as a rather hostile move due to the poor communication from our side. 

Simply put, we screwed up and for this we&#39;re sorry!

To remedy the situation, the &quot;Original&quot; sound pack has been unlocked and will remain free until the 1st of June. The pack will appear in the list of packs that require subscription, but you should still be able to select sounds and edit your old projects without limitations.

From June onward, Auxy will be a premium product with a very limited set of demo sounds. The reason we&#39;re removing the free tier is pretty straightforward: We need the people who love and use the app regularly to also pay to support it. Otherwise we won&#39;t be able to maintain and develop it further.

To clarify our ambition, we&#39;d like to reiterate what we wrote in our post about [the future of Auxy](https://disco.auxy.co/t/raising-the-bar-for-the-future-of-auxy/3035):

Auxy has come a long way but we still have many exciting things on the roadmap. Our biggest motivation is the magical feeling we get when we hear great new tracks from producers who work hard to push their music forward. We&#39;re fully committed to support these producers who, like us, are determined to shape the future of music.

Feel free to share your feedback below and we&#39;ll do our best to clarify our thinking!

/ Henrik &amp; Fredrik


### FAQ

**Does this mean I cannot use the app for free anymore?**
Yes! From June 1st you will have to get a subscription to use Auxy in a meaningful way.

**What if I have purchased sound packs?**
If you bought any of the sound packs in a previous version, you will always have access to these sounds, as well as the original sounds. Regardless of whether you subscribe or not.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 14:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Official Announcements</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/204">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/204</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-204</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/203">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/203</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 14:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-203</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Seems like we’ve concluded this discussion. Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/202">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/202</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 14:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-202</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackocean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ackshually<br>
Snickers is owned by Mars.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/187">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/187</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 19:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-187</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Goxenar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/skull.png?v=5" title=":skull:" class="emoji" alt=":skull:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=5" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"> milky way?<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/cry.png?v=5" title=":cry:" class="emoji" alt=":cry:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/184">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/184</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 23:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-184</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Indigoo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="39" data-topic="9588">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/goxenar/40/7588_1.png" class="avatar"> Goxenar:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Name a company that hasn’t made a mistake. Name a flawless company</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Snickers</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/183">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/183</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-183</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="176" data-topic="9588">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/blackocean/40/509_1.png" class="avatar"> blackocean:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>they are not money hungry, they physically cannot continue to develop the app at the rate they want to without having a steady source of income.</p>
<p>the premium subscription is not crappy**, it is necessary.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>think of it like this:</p>
<p><em>do you like auxy?</em></p>
<p>well, if you want it to be good, and have good features, and good sounds, the devs gotta spend time on it.</p>
<p>time that could be taken up if they had another job.</p>
<p>so they try not to have another job.</p>
<p>well, how can they get money without another job?</p>
<p>auxy.</p>

P.S. <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/180">(click for more details)</a>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/180">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/180</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-180</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blackocean]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE<br>
sorry it was necessary<br>
my take on the issue is that im glad that this is happening<br>
ok, ok, i have a job, i can pay for it, what can i say, this is biased.<br>
but for the auxy community as a whole, this will be amazing.</p>
<p>track quality will increase tenfold, and it will attract professional musicians because they realize that this is a serious app and not a hobby satisfier. it will give Henrik and Fredrik the monumental exposure they need to develop the app and make it the best it can be.</p>
<p>and while were on the topic, they wont lose money, they wont have “their dreams crumble beneath their feet”, their dreams will be lifted higher than they ever hoped when the app becomes a international phenomenon.</p>
<p>they are not money hungry, they physically cannot continue to develop the app at the rate they want to without having a steady source of income.<br>
the premium subscription is not crappy**, it is necessary.</p>
<p>no need for the aggressiveness, you dont know where they are coming from until you have been in that situation.</p>
<p>Have a nice day <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>blckocean.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/176">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/176</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 19:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-176</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If anyone begins attacking anyone, they are going to be silenced. I’m just letting everyone know.</p>
<p>This is for discussion, not for getting personal. Written retaliation / etc is really not necessary, helpful or pertinent to the topic.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/172">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/172</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 18:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-172</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="126" data-topic="9588">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/kds_official/40/1315_1.png" class="avatar"> KDS_Official:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>now it’s their fault if they lose money I was just giving what I like to call “Harsh Constructive Criticism”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>sounded a lot more like you were saying <strong>“you’re money-hungry and making bad decisions and just wait till all your dreams crumble at your feet”</strong> which isn’t really constructive</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/169">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/169</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 17:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-169</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SonOfRa]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks. The balance is definitely difficult to find. Many of these pieces of software for me can’t truly be replaced due to economics and capability, and I understand the developers of Auxy needing to make the app sustainable. In truth I can’t afford most of the apps you listed, and I’ve had to put the ones I can on hold in my toughest months to pay rent. If I could save up to one time purchase most of the apps I use I would in a heartbeat, as it’s far easier to justify a bigger one time purchase with my budget.<br>
I understand those that ask for others to prioritize. Intuitively it seems like a good option. What it leaves out though is that many of those who struggle economically have to prioritize between rent, food, healthcare, and the art they use to get through it all. It creates an extremely difficult decision for those who face it, and sadly art almost always falls on the wayside.<br>
We are in an unprecedented time for art. Cameras, computers, music software, even some physical supplies are getting cheaper. But as companies seek to find ways to become profitable or even sustainable in an environment where competition has become cutthroat, they (intentionally or unintentionally) leave behind an ever growing population here in the US. Like others of low income status I’ll find a way to make more art (Beepbox is going to be my go to until I get more funds together, it’s awesome and I highly recommend it as a totally different experience from Auxy). We have to ask the hard questions though like you mentioned: what do we actually own of our methods of making art? What of our art itself do we fully own?<em><strong>How will we open up art to all those who need it, without severely restricting them?</strong></em> These are questions not frequently answered, and leave a large population in limbo.<br>
All that being said I don’t want to seem like I’m attacking or ostracizing the devs, as they’ve put a huge amount of work in building the community. The price they’re charging seems fair, and almost underpriced to me. I don’t have the skill (in my own opinion) to utilize to the full extent the tools they provide, but I look forward to when I have the capability to try. The subscription they ask for is far lower than most other artistic and media related software I’ve seen, and the one-year subscription is especially so. Just a little beyond the reach of a few of us right now.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/168">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/168</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-168</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheRealJFalc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Technically it could be, in all legal terms as well. Usually I believe at least two week’s notice is required but the actual owners have no obligation to continue providing the house up for rent as they see fit. You are at their mercy and control. Granted, they probably wouldn’t but that’s not the point here.</p>
<p>I only hope that Auxy will be able to meet sustainability levels, so the investment will be worthwhile.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/167">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/167</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-167</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cornea]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Theoretically, if I rent my house I won’t feel like it’s going to be taken away anytime soon… what’s your point here?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/166">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/166</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-166</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JPNYC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, not gonna lie, I’m happy I purchased every sound pack I could before the subscription model, as it’s just an extra layer of security for me. I like knowing that I own something, even if that something costs me extra up front.</p>
<p>I wear a G-Shock aviation model watch for the same reason. In this world where everyone uses things that run on batteries that need to be replaced, cell phones to tell the time, screens that can crack etc, I like having the security of knowing that I have something on me that never needs a new battery, is practically indestructible and doesn’t need to be updated to stay current.</p>
<p>I think that subscription models help contribute to the anxiety that our society is experiencing around technology. More and more things are out of our control these days. The feeling that what we ‘own’ can be taken away from us at anytime, gives us this nagging feeling like someday around the corner, the things we love could simply disappear.</p>
<p>I found alternatives to Adobe Creative Suite and others, simply for the very reason that I don’t want to wake up one day with an internet issue and find myself locked out of my life.</p>
<p>All that being said, I am an Auxy subscriber, feel the cost is well worth the value of what I receive and will continue to support both Lenburg and Fredrik.</p>
<p></p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b.jpeg" title="0D0B3438-C700-470D-A3C1-C1E014FC8B64.jpeg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b_2_500x500.jpeg" alt="image" width="500" height="500" srcset="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b_2_500x500.jpeg, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b_2_750x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b_2_1000x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a652cd3eab8e047b56e566b977ecce806529390b_2_10x10.png"></a></div><p></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/165">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/165</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 15:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-165</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheRealJFalc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="JPNYC" data-post="163" data-topic="9588">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/jpnyc/40/11039_2.png" class="avatar"> JPNYC:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>the reality that we don’t really ‘own’ much of the media we consume or the apps we use to create that media these days.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>This sums up exactly the problem that this model of software has. While it’s not necessarily a bad thing, the lack of literal ownership means our fate is at the whims of some corporate executive. And that <em>can</em> be a bad thing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/164">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/164</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-164</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JPNYC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This post was all too real. A very well rounded perspective on how hard life can be.</p>
<p>Hulu, Netflix, Spotify, Apple Music, Auxy, Adobe Creative Suite, Amazon Prime, so many things in our world have gone to the subscription based model and all are vying for our attention and our money.</p>
<p>I can hear some say ‘prioritize’ and while there is truth to that, it all adds up, compounded by the reality that we don’t really ‘own’ much of the media we consume or the apps we use to create that media these days.</p>
<p>I worry about the future and what would happen if we lost our data connections, whether it’s through our phones or our router. What do we we truly own?</p>
<p>I digress. Anyhoo, just wanted to say thank you for your perspective. It’s always nice just to have someone acknowledge that finding that balance can be hard.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/163">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/163</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 14:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-163</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Would be so annoying <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/disappointed.png?v=5" title=":disappointed:" class="emoji" alt=":disappointed:"> but now I can’t use it anymore so never mind <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/sweat_smile.png?v=5" title=":sweat_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":sweat_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/162">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/162</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 12:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-162</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/161">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/161</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 12:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-161</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah but at first it was <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/confused.png?v=5" title=":confused:" class="emoji" alt=":confused:"> and now they’re going to lose quite a lot of users</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/160">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/160</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 12:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-160</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh man could you image? Every time you wanna add a instrument you have to watch a 30 second video lol… I mean this kind of stuff is bad enough in games but yeah, yikes, this would be atrocious in any music app lol…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/159">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/159</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-159</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cornea]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Also I believe you will be able to export after June 1st.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/158">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/158</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-158</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Cornea]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>“Open apps” can’t last forever. Unless you want ads, etc… subscription is best way. Auxy isn’t really a casual app anymore</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/157">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/157</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-157</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MSJ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s sad that Auxy isn’t an “open app” anymore because you have gone from a free and community app to something more “private” and premium so now the ones who just do music casually will not be able to do so.  We’ve lost the spirit of the app actually.</p>
<p>Anyway is it possible to still export our old projects after the 1st of June or will it all be deleted because of our non-subscription? So that all what we have done is not lost forever. Or do we need to quickly export everything?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/156">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/156</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-156</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zoruwhite]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The new demo is sure to inspire new users, and it lines up with more popular music genres</p>
<p>I dont doubt that they will want more sounds, but thats the general strategy behind it<br>
If they play around with the demo and realise hiw catchy it sounds, they’ll try to imitate it in a new project and realise they want more sounds</p>
<p>As I mentioned before, most people i would recommend this to, well they’d spend money without a second thought</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/155">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/155</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 08:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-155</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[El1011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>m8 im not a fan of the taking-away-free-sounds move to try and get more people on the subscription platform either.  But for me, it’s not because i think 1/2 the users will stop using Auxy, but because i dont think they’ll rise up the charts as quickly and get as many new users.</p>
<p>I think it will encourage the old/current users to get on the subscription platform because we already know it’s capabilities and have already bought into the app when it was free.<br>
However <strong>I</strong> dont see many new comers feeling the same way just due to lack of sounds/variability of production with the free sounds.  Plus, they’re fresh to the app.  They don’t know what it’s capable of and telling someone to throw $5 at a free app because <em>maybe</em> they might enjoy it seems pretty doubtful.</p>
<p>I want Auxy to succeed and i’m glad the devs seem to feel it will too.   But i dont think the app is ready to take on the 2 dev’s and their financial needs, not with the user-base they currently have.  It needs to grow exponentially but I dont think it will as they continue to take away free users’ abilities to make something new and different.</p>
<p><strong>Again the point i want to make:</strong> 1/2 the current users wont leave, but they’ll certainly have a much harder time in getting new ones, especially those who will stick around long enough to pay.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/154">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588/154</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 07:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9588-154</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/why-were-replacing-the-demo-sounds/9588.rss">Why we&#39;re replacing the demo sounds</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
