<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934</link>
    <description>we have heard quite literally nothing from the devs in months, all this forum is anymore is mindless self promo, and it is super heavily moderated - I don&#39;t doubt this thread will be taken down for fomenting rebellion or some bullsh*t excuse the &quot;janitors&quot; will use to cover their own asses.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 02:39:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KirkLurkPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what’s uppppppp…<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/eyes.png?v=9" title=":eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/99">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/99</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 02:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-99</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lemonboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>oh no… he’s back</em></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/98">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/98</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 10:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-98</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MVTT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Lmao fact</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/97">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/97</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 02:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-97</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It hasn’t changed much, if at all, in the years since the app launched.<br>
It likely doesn’t attract much traffic, and it’s unclear what role it could play in a broader, more pro-active approach to marketing.</p>
<p>They could start posting articles, but content creation like that can be very expensive and time-consuming to do well, so probably isn’t practical at their current size.</p>
<p>A content strategy based around their SC and social channels makes more sense, as they start building their presence as a voice on the topic of mobile music creation, engaging in the conversations already taking place online — potentially becoming a leading voice.</p>
<p>That said, if they do have some high-profile users, it would make sense to get those stories out there.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Most discovery of Auxy likely currently happens through searching/advertising on the App Store or through Auxy being mentioned in articles listing iOS music creation apps.</p>
<p>The <a href="http://Auxy.co">Auxy.co</a> site probably has the least reach of all the options. That’s why they could/should be doing more on their social channels, SC, etc… …as well as behaving in ways that inspire users to become advocates and ambassadors (functionally, a vast, unpaid sales team).</p>
<p>Their behaviour over the past couple of years makes little sense for a small company that claims it’s not yet meeting its growth and profitability aspirations.</p>
<p>Ironically, engaging with an enthusiastic user base and telling the world about the great things those users create with your product can be one of the most rewarding parts of owning and running a product.</p>
<p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/woman_shrugging.png?v=9" title=":woman_shrugging:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":woman_shrugging:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/96">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/96</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 12:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-96</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lemonboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Idk if the actual auxy (not the forum) website might change or smth</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/95">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/95</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 11:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-95</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think so too. Shame he’ll never really engage with the vast majority of points raised.</p>
<p>Frustrating and disappointing.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/94">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/94</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 09:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-94</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lemonboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>You got a point there actually.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/93">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/93</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-93</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BenVacca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ok!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/92">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/92</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 01:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-92</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KirkLurkPU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ooh! I haven’t seen Auxy’s discord. Send link pls <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/star_struck.png?v=9" title=":star_struck:" class="emoji" alt=":star_struck:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/91">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/91</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 01:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-91</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ciro11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes please! Anywhere I can share my music and get some feedback before releasing. I want to hear what other people have to say other than those close to me!</p>
<p>Thank you <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/benvacca">@BenVacca</a> !!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/90">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/90</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 21:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-90</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BenVacca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>actually, there is a very active place for auxy users on discord. it seems more people have moved over to discord which is fine as things evolve. I could give you some links to discord servers where you can get feedback, submit songs for challenges and much more!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/89">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/89</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 21:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-89</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ciro11]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just want to say I agree with everything <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/thoughtfulnoise">@ThoughtfulNoise</a> said above. I’ve been using the app for a year now, and it’s a very fun and inspiring app for music lovers and beginner composers (which is what I’d consider myself). I think having a community and a place to meet is exactly what people like I want and sort of need, but what use is the meeting place if no one is engaged? Just using the website alone has been mildly frustrating.</p>
<p>I’m hesitant to post my music on SoundCloud until getting constructive criticism back, and this is the place to do it. I’m happy I finally found a site where I can share my music, but I’m sorry it’s so quiet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/88">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/88</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-88</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Auxy" data-post="85" data-topic="19934">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/auxy/40/14154_2.png" class="avatar"> Auxy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If people don’t like the product, they should stop using it instead of hoping that we’re going to compensate by being active in a forum etc.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I hear what you’re saying, but you’ve got it backwards.<br>
Actively engaging with your product’s <em>official</em> community — that you created and ‘run’ —  shouldn’t be seen as compensation for anything – just part of having a product, even a great product. Heck, <em>especially</em> a great product.</p>
<p>Engaging with your product’s user community isn’t something failing companies with weak products do. It’s something good companies with good products do.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Hopefully you’ve seen that with no engaged and present moderation, this forum isn’t really achieving all that it could. When members are creating alt Auxy communities which are healthier, more popular and more engaging — precisely <em>because</em> this forum is less than an afterthought for the Auxy team.</p>
<p>Community perks such as <em>Track of the Week</em> bit the dust as soon as iammane left. Kudos to the member who stood in, but they’re not engaged in the same way.</p>
<p>Imo, that should matter to you, as they were appreciated by the community.</p>
<p>Maybe <em>empowering</em> some more mods might be something to consider.</p>
<p>Hey, and maybe those trusted, empowered mods could also be responsible for restarting the Auxy SC reposts.</p>
<p>(Or was that only important while the app was still ‘maturing’ and it no longer makes sense for you to invest a little extra time and effort in your product’s official user community?)</p>
<p>Auxy users, and this forum more than most, are still likely to be your biggest source of <em>free marketing content</em>. Done right, you’ve also got what amounts to a free sales team right here.</p>
<p>The fact that you don’t recognise and appreciate that, and evidently aren’t interested in not only fixing it, but nurturing and building it, is a real shame.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
(I’d be curious to know what you included in the “etc” part — and what you feel might be so wrong with paying customers having some level of expectation around those things. I think there’s likely to be some quite reasonable expectations wrapped up in that “etc”.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>Not sure which apps/companies you’re comparing to when you expect the founders to be present in the community discussions all the time?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Absolutely no-one has suggested that <em>you</em> be here <em>“all the time”</em>.</p>
<p>That said, it’s common for brands/companies to have connected mods present on their official forums who have some kind of direct line to the developers, product team, and who can be a bit more responsive to questions about the product, without requiring the product/company owner to be fielding questions directly.</p>
<p>Your statement does make it sound as though you feel engaging with the forum more regularly is somehow beneath you, as ‘the founder’. That’s pretty high-minded for a 2-person company.</p>
<p>Maybe recruit some mods — and show some appreciation for the time and effort by thanking/rewarding them with free subscriptions? Not a huge amount $-wise, but likely to be welcome to those you pick — and plays better than the free and largely thankless task it’s been to-date.</p>
<p>(I find it surprising that you look at 1-2-1 emails as the optimal way to communicate with users, compared to regular*, timely announcements and catch-ups with groups in one place, like, say, your company’s official forum.)</p>
<p>(* though not necessarily frequent)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Auxy" data-post="86" data-topic="19934">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/auxy/40/14154_2.png" class="avatar"> Auxy:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>If having it open creates an overall negative feeling we can shut it down though. Maybe that would help in terms of setting the expectations straight?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>smh</p>
<p>You don’t think you stand to benefit from a healthy, enthusiastic, thriving and growing community of users and advocates? You don’t think there’s a connection between those things and the popularity and profitability of a company? You don’t see that as sufficient incentive to figure out how to get it from where it is… to where it could be?</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Was building a reasonably popular mobile music app, to create a reasonable, relatively passive income, with minimal ongoing effort, the full extent of the vision/dream?</p>
<p>What happened to this…?</p>
<p></p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4.png" data-download-href="/uploads/short-url/1PlwbX8E2hl8RJUpS1cwwLGIaFK.png?dl=1" title="image" rel="noopener nofollow ugc"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4_2_690x123.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="1PlwbX8E2hl8RJUpS1cwwLGIaFK" width="690" height="123" srcset="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4_2_690x123.png, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4_2_1035x184.png 1.5x, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/0/c/0cd0121ebc659b4219e02259dab9338b02f06da4_2_10x10.png"></a></div><p></p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Mission accomplished? Really?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/87">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/87</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-87</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi all! This discussion has come up before and I think I’ve laid out our perspectives then. Early on in the Auxy history, having a close dialog with users was crucial to take the app forward. However, as things mature, it makes less sense for me to invest time in the forum. Some people might miss chatting with the makers of the app they use, but I think it’s a stretch to go as far as to say that Auxy doesn’t care about its users. We always answer everyone who emails support, and occasionally post stuff here or in other places around the web. Not sure which apps/companies you’re comparing to when you expect the founders to be present in the community discussions all the time?</p>
<p>We’ve kept the forum open for the people who like having a place for dropping tracks and setting up collaborations. If having it open creates an overall negative feeling we can shut it down though. Maybe that would help in terms of setting the expectations straight?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/86">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/86</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 15:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-86</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Auxy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="ThoughtfulNoise" data-post="67" data-topic="19934">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/thoughtfulnoise/40/15848_2.png" class="avatar"> ThoughtfulNoise:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Basically, once they’ve got you signed up, they stop trying to keep you happy or impress you.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>We try to keep people happy by providing an app/service that works and lets you make music. If people don’t like the product, they should stop using it instead of hoping that we’re going to compensate by being active in a forum etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/85">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/85</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 14:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-85</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[The_Osprey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like the life lessons here</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/84">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/84</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 04:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-84</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cursed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, i didnt mean marketing-wise but you’re right.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/82">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/82</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 12:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-82</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="cursed" data-post="80" data-topic="19934">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/cursed/40/16140_2.png" class="avatar"> cursed:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Since auxy is offline (mostly) i think it would work fine even if they took it off the app store.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Quite the opposite.<br>
Afaik, the App Store is the only place they’re putting time and money into promotion/advertising.</p>
<p>Their entire marketing strategy seems to be App Store ads.<br>
Without that, they’d have close to zero new users each month, bc all their other channels are so under-developed.</p>
<p>It’s only bc App Store advertising seems to be ‘good enough’ for growth and profitability that they’re not putting any effort into other marketing methods/channels.</p>
<p>The irony is, if they did more to foster organic marketing using their own channels, they could likely reduce the money spent on advertising and get the same results — or maintain current levels of ad spend and get even better results, as brand recognition and word of mouth (‘earned media’) would start to contribute to shoppers buying decisions.</p>
<p>More potential users would seek out Auxy on the App Store by name, rather than Auxy relying on advertising (and searches) to put Auxy in front of people.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/81">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/81</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-81</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cursed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Since auxy is offline (mostly) i think it would work fine even if they took it off the app store. Worst come to worst, find an external recording tool such as: </p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613.jpeg" data-download-href="/uploads/short-url/uSnBbYswnCkPx2jwsvDsYx9pusH.jpeg?dl=1" title="20201108_150121" rel="noopener nofollow ugc"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613_2_666x500.jpeg" alt="20201108_150121" data-base62-sha1="uSnBbYswnCkPx2jwsvDsYx9pusH" width="666" height="500" srcset="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613_2_666x500.jpeg, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613_2_999x750.jpeg 1.5x, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613_2_1332x1000.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/d/8/d866e6e1f48e6b7710c76cda7f90f1cc11aa4613_2_10x10.png"></a></div><p></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/80">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/80</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-80</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t think they’ll plan to close. It’s profitable, even though it requires barely any upkeep from the team.</p>
<p>The only thing that’s likely to threaten that is subbing users bleeding away to other tools.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/79">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/79</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-79</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/point_up_2.png?v=9" title=":point_up_2:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":point_up_2:"></p>
<p>Kudos for taking the time to give a considered response.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I’m fully aware that I’m one of those <em>“not optimistic”</em> voices – possibly the worst offender. But, as you point out, it’s not coming from nowhere — it’s a negative feedback loop. I’m reacting to something I’m seeing (or not seeing).</p>
<p>I simply get frustrated — and disappointed — by the behaviour and decisions of the Auxy team, in terms of their handling of the app itself, but perhaps more so by their handling of the marketing and the community.</p>
<p>They’re actually squandering a good opportunity for the lack of putting in even just a bit more effort.</p>
<p>It’s hard to have respect for something when the ‘owner’ doesn’t appear to care much about it. That goes for the app, but also for the community to some extent.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
But… it’s all very fixable, if Auxy is willing to put in that extra effort. With the right voices in their ear, or even just paying better attention to the direction the wind is blowing, they’d likely be making better decisions and achieving the level of success they’re seeking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/78">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/78</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-78</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[cursed]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I am literally outside right now just to buy a ipod to make music on it while im on my way to work so if auxy decides to close for any reason in particular im downloading igun and shooting myself</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/77">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/77</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-77</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arimyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="brandnaqua" data-post="73" data-topic="19934" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/brandnaqua/40/16153_2.png" class="avatar"> brandnaqua:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s not about being part of an active form it’s about being a creator of music. The community has grown sale because people who are not optimistic dampen the vibe. So many instruments and everyone asking for more instruments, but have you used all of the instruments yet? There are some musicians who have only ever had a piano in their life and they have composed great music. We have no excuse. We thankfully have a lot of sounds.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I wasn’t really looking to comment on what seems to be the 8th iteration of beating the “forum is dead” horse, but I believe it’s worth pointing out that comments like this and ones made stemming from similar mindsets are likely a large part of why the forum (and the app / business as a whole) is in the state it is today (even more so than the so called “not optimistic” voices around the forum).</p>
<p>While I appreciate you trying to be an advocate for Lenberg and his team, what you might not realize is that by covering up and glossing over the rather obvious issues in Auxy’s leadership both in the areas of software development and marketing (to name a couple), you are actually hurting Auxy’s future as a whole as it does not leave room for constructive discussion let alone improvement. Not to mention that the majority of what people say around here as far as constructive criticism for Auxy is for the most part based on valid points.</p>
<p>So, to summarize:</p>
<p><strong>It’s not about being part of an active form it’s about being a creator of music. –</strong> Being a (good) creator of music is not mutually exclusive and is in fact largely dependent on being part of an active forum of like minded and passionate fellow creators.</p>
<p><strong>The community has grown s(t)ale because people who are not optimistic dampen the vibe. –</strong> Actually, it’s more likely grown stale because of a negative feedback loop of: complete lack of interaction from the developers / forum officials -&gt; those with knowledge and experience to offer leaving / becoming inactive -&gt; traffic being redirected to almost exclusively self promotion -&gt; people complaining about lack of activity -&gt; developers making a brief reappearance before disappearing again -&gt; etc. etc.</p>
<p><strong>So many instruments and everyone asking for more instruments, but have you used all of the instruments yet? –</strong> This is roughly the equivalent of Tim Cook going on stage at Apple’s WWDC and announcing that there will be no new updates to Apple’s software because users have not yet used every single feature of the previous update. I’m reasonably confident that you can see the flaw in that.</p>
<p><strong>There are some musicians who have only ever had a piano in their life and they have composed great music. We have no excuse. We thankfully have a lot of sounds. –</strong> The majority of Auxy users are not coming in with the intention of being classical pianists, and beyond that, sound requests make up a small fraction of feature requests / general comments about Auxy (some of which transcend the app entirely). Nothing really more to say here beyond it being a case of (unintentional) tunnel vision.</p>
<p>In summary of summary:</p>
<p>Positivity and optimism is great, but not at the expense of ignoring / skewing what’s in front of you for sake of painting a prettier picture of reality.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/76">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/76</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-76</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[lemonboy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m thinking lately and I thinks its time to make another one. Everyone please dm for ideas!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/75">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/75</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 07:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-75</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>This forum is officially dead</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>None of what I mentioned relates to the quality of the music that can be made using Auxy or the enthusiasm we might have for it.</p>
<p>The fact that some very good tracks* can be made using Auxy doesn’t take away the fact that it has its limits. Those limits mean that certain musical ideas are simply not possible - or are so difficult to work around in Auxy that it becomes a bad choice of tool for creators wanting to work with ideas even slightly outside the mainstream (or many mainstream ideas not supported within Auxy).</p>
<p>* There is still a significant gap in the audio ‘finish’ of Auxy tracks compared to pro tracks. The soundspace in Auxy feels very limited compared to professionally produced tracks — especially in the stereo space. Maybe it’s the quality of the source sounds. Maybe it’s the quality of the effects or built-in ‘mastering’. Either way, it’s a noticeable characteristic and limitation of Auxy.</p>
<p>Anyhoo…</p>
<p>The main theme of my comments was that with more attention paid to the Auxy creators, including this community, the Auxy team would have a deep well of content to pull on — and put to use as marketing content. Limitless free marketing content in the form of Auxy tracks and Auxy creator stories.</p>
<p>After all, what better way to market your music creation app than by using (read: supporting and promoting) the music created with it and the creators using it — all of which they can access freely (and eagerly from the perspective of the creators).</p>
<p>In my view, Auxy doesn’t deserve to be more profitable, because they’re willingly <em>not</em> doing many of the easy and obvious things that companies seeking to improve profitability do — the main one being marketing.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The other reason this Auxy forum will likely continue to struggle is because members are generally too self-serving. Posting your own music far outnumbers any other single type of post, while the amount of engagement each posted track gets here is getting lower and lower.</p>
<p>This forum is largely becoming a dumping ground for links to our tracks. Somewhere to seed our SC listens, rather than a community that we all want to productively engage with — or learn from, or contribute to. (Simply being a cheerleader for the app isn’t enough to sustain a healthy, worthwhile community.)</p>
<p>Feedback on tracks is generally shallow and uncritical. That’s great for beginners and people seeking small affirmations from online strangers, but not really helpful to creators who genuinely want to develop and grow.</p>
<p>Speaking as one of only a few members actively posting about production or branding and promotion tips, I suspect there are fewer still who actively read those shared posts — and close to zero <em>here</em> that actually follow any of the advice given in those shared articles and videos.<br>
(I’m as guilty as the next person on that score.)</p>
<p>Lastly, or perhaps consequently, this forum skews heavily towards beginners, while more experienced and more serious/dedicated Auxy creators typically move on to other places. That means that there are few advanced creative role models here, because this forum has very little to offer them in return.</p>
<p>(As the saying goes… <em>If you’re the smartest person in the room, find another room</em>.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Imo, all of that is what’s limiting this community’s sense of identity and purpose, and ultimately, its ability to thrive.</p>
<p>Auxy engaging with Auxy music creators, and supporting the Auxy community while also helping themselves by actively leveraging/promoting Auxy tracks for marketing would be a great way to revive and re-engage this community in a way that benefits both Auxy and the user community.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/74">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934/74</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 05:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-19934-74</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/this-forum-is-officially-dead/19934.rss">This forum is officially dead</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
