<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Should I post previews?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173</link>
    <description>Hey guys, BALLISTIK here.  I have seen quite a few producers lately post &quot;sketches&quot; or &quot;previews&quot;.  And, as I&#39;m not as prolific as some others, I was wondering: &quot;Should I post previews of my songs?&quot;
I also say this because I&#39;ve got quite a few half-finished tracks laying around, that I may never get around to finishing and you guys won&#39;t ever get to hear...unless I post them as a sketch.  And...who knows, maybe having an &quot;unfinished version&quot; out on public display will push me to finish more of them.
So, I&#39;d really like it if you guys told me what _you_ think.  Do you personally like it when a producer puts out a &quot;sketch&quot;, and am I just being a perfectionist?  Or is it more professional to just have a smaller number of fully-finished tracks?

Don&#39;t be afraid to share your opinions!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 08:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve always considered my Auxy stuff as competent demos at best (the phrase I use is ‘Auxy finished) - though I’ve recently started labelling some as demos. (Might add ‘demo’ as a tag too.)</p>
<p>As I’ll be looking to release through a label, and they can sometimes be a bit hesitant about taking ‘finished’ tracks that have already been released*, I’m considering adding ‘demo’ to every (full) track I have on SC.</p>
<p>+ I always intended to put the more promising ones through a proper engineering, mix and master process before formally ‘releasing’ them.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
* I’m not convinced even a fussy label would consider the low number of play counts, reposts, etc… my stuff attracts on SC as ‘released’, but hey… <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/8</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 08:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SpaghettiSauce]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Show a preview only if you are taking a long time, and are working very hard on the song. If you dish out songs every week or month, don’t bother. I would give a preview only for big projects.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d do demos. A lot of the BTC’s and the Tournament I’m doing feels like little demos. It just depends what you’re after.</p>
<p>Maybe you want your listeners to sample a very well done 30sec-1min work, seeing if they want more. Or maybe you need feedback. Or maybe you have something cool you want to show off and have no plans for it.</p>
<p>Just make sure your objective with your demos is consistent.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/6</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 23:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BALLISTIK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks everyone!  I’m still not completely sure, I guess it’ll have to depend on the project.  Also, I probably need to build a bigger audience, so people will be willing to wait for a full version.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 23:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Xicon]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you were to upload something BIG, like an Ep or seomthing, then yes. Show a preview.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 22:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="6173">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/ballistik/40/3654_1.png" class="avatar"> BALLISTIK:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Do you personally like it when a producer puts out a “sketch”</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I do.<br>
I don’t encounter them often, but the writer/producer in me enjoys looking at how an idea starts out compared to where it ends up.</p>
<p>And I do it. A lot.</p>
<p>I know some really don’t like the idea, believing it to be ‘bad for your brand’.</p>
<p>I do it for a few reasons.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>It allows me to get some kind of feedback, either here or in the form of likes, reposts, comments, etc… on SC. Feedback before a track is finished helps make the input more active, rather than lessons to be learned ‘next time’. It also allows me to see which sketches I should prioritise in terms of further development. (The Auxy community is not my intended audience, but can be a testing ground, of sorts.)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It stops me being too precious too soon (even though I still struggle to think of anything I’ve ‘finished’ in Auxy as truly ‘finished’).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>It stops an idea languishing at the bottom of my Auxy project list. It makes the idea more real, and something I need to act on. (All my ‘sketches’ are partially-developed ideas that I intend to work up and develop fully at some point.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Seems to be catching on with some big names too, with Khalid releasing a “rough draft” of an upcoming track on SC…</p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/thegreatkhalid/saved-rough-draft">Saved (rough draft) by Khalid</a></p>
<p>-</p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://blog.landr.com/sharing-my-first-track/">https://blog.landr.com/sharing-my-first-track/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 22:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Arimyth]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I never post sketches and wouldn’t consider posting them. For me, if someone posts a preview of a track or a half finished track I’ll usually just take note of it and if I care enough about that producer I’ll wait for the full track to come out.</p>
<p>It’s up to you though. If you truly never intend to finish a track and you see some value in posting what exists of it, then go for it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 22:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Should I post previews?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BALLISTIK]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys, BALLISTIK here.  I have seen quite a few producers lately post “sketches” or “previews”.  And, as I’m not as prolific as some others, I was wondering: "Should I post previews of my songs?"<br>
I also say this because I’ve got quite a few half-finished tracks laying around, that I may never get around to finishing and you guys won’t ever get to hear…unless I post them as a sketch.  And…who knows, maybe having an “unfinished version” out on public display will push me to finish more of them.<br>
So, I’d really like it if you guys told me what <em>you</em> think.  Do you personally like it when a producer puts out a “sketch”, and am I just being a perfectionist?  Or is it more professional to just have a smaller number of fully-finished tracks?</p>
<p>Don’t be afraid to share your opinions!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6173-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/should-i-post-previews/6173.rss">Should I post previews?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
