<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for an old song</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008</link>
    <description>Hey... It&#39;s been almost 4 years since i touched this site but I&#39;ve come back for some help...

I recently had memories of an old song I can remember from when i was involved in this community, it was a lofi song posted by blackocean and was called something along the lines of &quot;Brighter Days&quot; or something like that.
I remember really liking the song but as I&#39;ve looked back to try and find this song again, I have no luck so the song must have been deleted from soundcloud.
I can also remember the song being played in the back of one of Produk&#39;s auxy tutorials on youtube, but I cannot locate that particular video either.

If anyone has any clue on where this song is or if it still even exists anywhere, I would love to hear any infomation anyone might have.

Thanks</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Random</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for an old song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[XXAR]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sadly I don’t know why but he left the community and deleted his Soundcloud account<br>
I also have been listening to blackocean back in the days when he made a lot of unique songs one of them is “Crimson” and since he left I also couldn’t find it other than the demo of the song and remixes.<br>
I hope you find it soon. The mods might help you</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-22008-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008.rss">Looking for an old song</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for an old song</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TROPTA]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey… It’s been almost 4 years since i touched this site but I’ve come back for some help…</p>
<p>I recently had memories of an old song I can remember from when i was involved in this community, it was a lofi song posted by blackocean and was called something along the lines of “Brighter Days” or something like that.<br>
I remember really liking the song but as I’ve looked back to try and find this song again, I have no luck so the song must have been deleted from soundcloud.<br>
I can also remember the song being played in the back of one of Produk’s auxy tutorials on youtube, but I cannot locate that particular video either.</p>
<p>If anyone has any clue on where this song is or if it still even exists anywhere, I would love to hear any infomation anyone might have.</p>
<p>Thanks</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-22008-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-an-old-song/22008.rss">Looking for an old song</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
