<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278</link>
    <description>Hey, y&#39;all! I figured it would be cool if we would talk about the starts of our musical paths, and the passion that made us the producers we are. I, personally, always had a knack for noticing detail, even as a kid as young as four or five. It was cute, actually. At five years old, I associated every musical key with a different color, which I assume made adults around me scratch their heads. I heard everything in the music and heard more as I grew older. Since that age, I always loved percussion and for a few years I would always be seen tapping on any surface with two pens or anything of the sort. 13 years later... I guess I&#39;m a tad bit better with a little bit more experience lol
Hopefully getting a studio in my room this year so gonna have loads of opportunities to explore the musical world even further
Really curious about you guys tho
What made you the music legends you are?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:47:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trojanian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/46</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-46</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DHO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My birth. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/45</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-45</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trojanian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Damn. A living music legend. I like. And wow! I thought I was the only one too lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/44</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-44</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[GrandpaMusic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So I see I’m not the only one to associate pitches with colors as a kid. I never would have guessed.</p>
<p>My experience with music began with toy instruments, of course. The earliest I took up actual instruments was with a plastic recorder. By around 2nd and 3rd grade, I got familiar with percussion and string instruments like xylophones, glockenspiels, guitars, pianos, etc… In 4th grade we had class recorder sessions, with recorders made of genuine wood. In 5th grade I took up the trumpet, to which I carried on with all throughout middle and high school. In seventh grade, I was introduced to GarageBand, but I didn’t learn how to use it until a year later, when I was rewriting a bunch of Eiffel 65 songs. My first ever song of my own was made in GarageBand, released onto YouTube when I was a freshman. Then I discovered Auxy sophomore year, and for the while I was using it more than GarageBand. As a junior, I’d go on to play in our school’s pit orchestra for two musicals; Side Show and Les Miserables. At the end, I won four awards, including a letter, recognition for contribution, the jazz spirit award, and recognition for outstanding trumpet solo at a university jazz fest. I became a jack of all trades for music. And I still practice to this day.</p>
<p>Edit: One thing I forgot: My first experience with composing music came from a nifty DS game called WairoWare DIY. I got this game when I was 9 years old. It can’t do as much as what I use now, but I still play around with it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/43</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-43</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[icelight]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hehe <span class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/42">spoiler</a></span></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/42</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 23:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-42</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[obexg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What do you mean?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/41</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 23:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-41</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AnirudhKhanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>i was living a normal 9 year old life</p>
<p>but everything changed when</p>
<p><strong>the fire nation attacked</strong></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/40</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 23:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-40</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trojanian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks man I appreciate</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/39</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 21:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-39</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Gotta start somewhere <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> there’s plenty of folks on the Audiobus forums in their 40s, 50s and 60s who are just cracking into mobile production. It’s totally cool</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/38</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 21:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-38</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[El1011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ayy legal adult gang</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/37</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 19:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-37</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trojanian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>18 year old wimpy me being all cool and starting this thread and then seeing how inexperienced I am compared to you guys​:joy:<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/36</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 02:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-36</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HYDRANS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I guess I’ll post my story now because it was fun to read everyone else’s</p>
<p>About 3-4 years ago, I loved to use music apps such as Medly, (Green logo) Auxy, and GarageBand. At the time, I had no musical training, and it was just something I did for fun. I never really finished any “tracks” at this stage, all I did was mess around with features of the apps. A few months later, my phone got stolen and I never reinstalled any of the apps.</p>
<p>About a year later (summer of 2017) I was browsing through the app store and I saw a section for music apps. I looked through a few of the recommended apps and I recognized the name Auxy but it looked a lot different. I downloaded it on my phone and for about a year, I was still just playing around with the app, but a few things had changed. First of all, I was more experienced with music since I had been taking drum lessons for a while now. Second, I was starting to become interested in electronic music, which helped give me inspiration for my tracks. <span class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/35">spoiler</a></span> A year later, I finally decided to post a track.</p>
<p>I created the alias “HYDRANS” after about a month of trying to decide a name and then I posted my track “oceans” as an entry to the Auxy summer tournament of last year. I lost in the first round to phluze, but the track reached 100 plays (It was a lot at the time). I posted my first EP that summer and a string of singles came out afterwards, the most popular being “wind.” At this point I had no idea what genre fit me, but I was pretty consistent with releases.</p>
<p>Over the course of the summer, I had worked on trying to be a part of the community, and I finally decided it was time to attempt to get a release with a label. I had an unfinished track called “Insomnia” that I wanted to send to an Auxy label. I will forever be grateful to <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/stereofield">@stereofield</a> for giving me feedback and accepting this track for his label (Frontier) because (at the time) this was a big deal for me and I think it was the first genuinely good track I ever made. It’s still one of my favorite tracks almost a year later.</p>
<p>After this, I started growing in popularity and continued to make releases. I started getting reposts from Auxy Collective on most of my releases and attention/reposts from the Auxy account. In October I started posting tracks from my Insurgency LP, in November I had my second release with Frontier (pass me by), and in December I had another label release. At this point, I was an active member of the community.</p>
<p>In February, I had a release with Ethereal Sound planned, which I was really proud of. The track’s release date got delayed a few months and I had no releases planned for the whole month. (You can still listen to the track, “delirium,” on my alt account. The track was never released on Ethereal.) I was getting kind of bored with Auxy, and after finishing up my track “paradox,” I decided to spend the whole weekend producing with FL (after taking a year to learn the basics). The product of this was “variable,” a track that was heavily influenced by my new favorite label, Phuture. <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/arimyth">@Arimyth</a> (the owner of ethereal sound) contacted me about having variable be the debut release for an ethereal sublabel (Tesseract) and I said yes.</p>
<p>After this, I started improving my FL skills and continued to make experimental bass music. I had a string of releases on my own page along with a release on a Phuture sublabel. Recently, I posted my “salvaged materials” EP which (in my opinion) is my best work yet. Hopefully I will continue to improve even more in the future!</p>
<p>P. S.<br>
Even though FL Studio is now my main DAW, I recently started an alt account for posting my Auxy songs.</p>
<p>Congratulations if you read this far! Writing this post brings back a lot of memories of my early days in the community.</p>
<p>Note: It’s almost been a year since I joined the Auxy Collective community, which was when I really started to become active in the community.<br>
I’m really glad that I found this awesome community, and my music skills would never be at the level they are now without everyone here!</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/35</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HYDRANS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this brings back so many memories</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/34</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 01:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HYDRANS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>did you ever post that collab with drevm?</p>
<p>I want to hear what your music sounded like in 2017 lol</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/33</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 01:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[foryou]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t remember all of the details, but back in 3rd grade I was messing with GarageBand on my parents’ computer, and it never became anything serious. In 6th grade I got back into making music, and made a SoundCloud (that has since been deleted). Most of my stuff was made with GarageBand loops because I really had no idea how to actually produce at the time. I kept this up until about 2016, when I joined a community called Tanoshii Collective. They convinced me to download Ableton and actually learn production. So I did. I bounced around a couple aliases, and worked with mostly samples, until the summer of 2017, where my music began getting a little bit more recognition. My song “deicide”, released under the name brxken drevm, reached 5k plays, and I got a chance to collab with DREVM, a big name in the experimental bass music community. I started making lofi hip hop around the same time. In the fall of 2017, I decided to come back to making music with Auxy (an app I had previously used in 2016 when the original version was still out) as a side project. With help from <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/stereofield">@stereofield</a>, I decided to go under the name <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/vectr">@vectr</a>. I had some success with that name, until February of 2018, when I caused a lot of drama that caused me to start over my musical journey. I came back under the name “surf”, and started making more music in Auxy. In June of 2018, I transitioned back into using Ableton on my “surf” account, which was previously only used for Auxy music. In September 2018, I rebranded and named myself “sei”, which means “life” in Japanese. Since then, I’ve had more than 38k total plays on SoundCloud alone, with my biggest song “midnight conversations”, featuring my friend Chloe, getting posted on The Bootleg Boy’s YouTube channel (1.8 million subscribers). The video for the song has over 50k views, 10k on SoundCloud, and 9k on Spotify. I’ve come a long way since my early days on GarageBand, and I’m only just getting started. Thank you all for welcoming me into this community, because all of you that have supported me along the way mean so much to me. You help me fulfill my dreams. Thank you all!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 01:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[foryou]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>dang bro they can’t handle the suspense, it’ll end ‘em</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/31</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-31</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[crystldawnmusic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <div class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/30">spoiler</a></div>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-30</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JacobJustus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I was talking to this random guy at church and he asked me “do you play an instrument”, and I was like “my parents are forcing me to play piano so yes”. He had a blank emotion on his face and then asked me “Do you know what GarageBand is?” What I was thinking: Who the heck would come up with that name. My response: no I haven’t sounds interesting, what is it?!<br>
“You can connect a keyboard to it and play a bunch of cool sounds. Little did I know that my adventure had begun. That was 6 years ago.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trojanian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m thoroughly enjoying this thread. Maybe I should cheesy, but this is a really cool way to connect.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JacobJustus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>lol that’s exactly how I started. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[carlosesparza]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is fun to read everybody’s different path <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>mine is also circuitous. i started learning piano after i discovered i could figure things out by ear at age 7 (the theme to the TV movie: The Death of the Incredible Hulk). this didn’t lead to much until 3 years later i was given a guitar. at this time i was really into progressive rock, and learned to shred over the next couple years, until i was introduced to Richard D. James in 1995. i started tracking using Fast Tracker II, and slowly learned to make electronic music (which i found infinitely harder than shredding).</p>
<p>by 2004 I had developed a style that felt like my own, and from then on i’ve been sporadically ‘releasing’ music (to my friends, basically).</p>
<p>in 2009 I started an orchestral post-rock / ambient electronica band, and we started releasing music sporadically to our slightly larger group of friends . . .</p>
<p>I found Auxy a couple years ago now, and have made a few of my best tracks in it, which drew me into the disco here . . .<br>
Starting a couple months ago I’ve started trying to get serious about this whole thing. I have a moderately successful career as a graphic designer, but music is where my heart is. Love the community here in the auxy boards and am learning a lot!</p>
<p>Thanks for reading <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HELIXX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It was the summer of 2014. I was 12 years old. I was watching a pewdiepie video and it had a skrillex song in it. I never heard anything like it. I spend hours trying to figure out what the song was. Eventually I found out it was called KILL EVERYBODY. I checked out some of his other songs and I was blown away by all the cool sounds. A few months later I saw a video of skrillex djing and I thought it looked really cool so I wanted to do that. Ever since then I’ve been a dj/ producer. If it wasn’t for that video I wouldn’t have discovered skrillex and I wouldn’t have been making music</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[obexg]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I use GarageBand mostly for fun and when I do, I do experiment with the loops. I have never posted songs on SoundCloud that have GarageBand loops in them. If I’m posting from GarageBand, I’m usually posting it from there because I added vocals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think I should rerelease my GarageBand songs</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 21:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>What started your musical journey?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Propellerhead’s Figure was featured to as a “Free App for the Week” in December 2013. This introduced me to SoundCloud for the first time, and soon enough, there was a Figure community.</p>
<p>After using Figure for an hour, I made my first 5 loops, all of which are deleted and lost. A user had a remix link to one of his Figure loops. I went to go remix it and upload it to SoundCloud. Literally overnight, it became one of the well known remixes of that specific loop–even the original poster praised my success.<br>
(<a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/dionysus-3c-rush" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/dionysus-3c-rush</a>)</p>
<p>Since that day, I’ve continued to make loops through Figure, all of them deleted off from my SoundCloud because of the 2 hour limit. A new app appeared in the App Store and looked more professional. It was known as AOXY.</p>
<p>Using AOXY was a whole new experience for me, I’ve never used any app before with a piano roll, little did I know, this will eventually be used by some professionals.</p>
<p>What started my love for Trance was back in 8th grade when I had feelings for this girl, but then ignored me. Going through Pandora and listening to artists like Above &amp; Beyond. I’ve slowly become inheriting the genre. During that time, a paid app called Auxy for iPhone appeared on the App Store. Excitedly, I bought the app.</p>
<p>I’ve seen and used AOXY grow into what it is today. Here we are, in a community forum discussing how we started our music journey.</p>
<p>All of this started 7 years ago</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278/22</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 20:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16278-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/what-started-your-musical-journey/16278.rss">What started your musical journey?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
