<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Changing distributors?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966</link>
    <description>Been mulling this over for a hot minute, but figured I&#39;d ask here first since I know many of you have experience with it.

For one, re: Distrokid, it&#39;s 20 bones a year for one artist, I presume (or think I read here) there&#39;s other options for multiple artist accounts. What does that run, on average?

How fast is the turn around for upload to release? Any involvement with support?

Now the million dollar question: Does anyone have experience with switching distributors? I have a small handful of releases through Amuse, I&#39;m wondering what the deal is with changing. I know I could just put new releases through a new distributor, but would be more interested in a &quot;single pane of glass&quot; so to speak. 

I&#39;m certain there&#39;s not a way to migrate releases, but what ends up happening if you use two? How does it appear in stores? If you were to remove all releases from a distributor does it remove them from stores? What happens to people who already purchased something?

Anyway. That&#39;s all I got - any advice welcome. :point_right: :point_left:</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 18:46:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Changing distributors?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Coolio.</p>
<p>It actually pushed me to get my stuff moving across.</p>
<p>Got everything ready in Drafts on Level, and I’ve already started the deletion process on DK.</p>
<p>Fwiw, if it’s just two artists you need, then DK might not be a bad option. There are a bunch of tools, metrics, etc… that might come in handy if you’re being pro-active with promotion etc…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/5</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 18:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-20966-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss">Changing distributors?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing distributors?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Awesome man, this is all very good info. Just kicking some ideas around in my head, a two artist dealio might work ok. I’d suspect you can probably upgrade. Hadn’t heard of Level Music, going to keep that in my back pocket as well. I did find an article on Amuse’s site about migrating <em>to</em> them, I suspect if I follow that in reverse it would work for migrating <em>away</em> lol (and in fact, pretty much matches everything you wrote above).</p>
<p>And yeah, I’m not too assed about delays or gaps of availability lol. But good to know!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/4</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-20966-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss">Changing distributors?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing distributors?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fwiw, I’m just pulling the trigger on the takedowns on my Distrokid releases.</p>
<p>Might be quicker than it says on their support pages.</p>
<p></p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346.png" data-download-href="/uploads/short-url/gP3JYXjVCtXDENvte57256A3EJo.png?dl=1" title="image"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346_2_690x456.png" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="gP3JYXjVCtXDENvte57256A3EJo" width="690" height="456" srcset="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346_2_690x456.png, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346.png 1.5x, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/3X/7/5/75e861f81b6b1112d3a539bfb78b475033b77346_2_10x10.png"></a></div><p></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/3</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 17:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-20966-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss">Changing distributors?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing distributors?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ThoughtfulNoise]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Bumping releases across manually should be relatively simple.</p>

Steps… <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/2">(click for more details)</a>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
<strong>Distrokid…</strong></p>
<p>I’ve got some older stuff on a 2-artist Distrokid account, and have been meaning to move it out for a while.</p>

Distrokid pricing… <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/2">(click for more details)</a>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
<strong>Level Music…</strong></p>
<p>For more recent stuff, I’ve used <a href="https://levelmusic.com/pricing">Level Music</a>.<br>
$20/y for 5 primary artists. (I’ve used two so far, but plan to use more, especially as I plan to bring across my Distrokid releases.)</p>
<p>Interface is easy, you can set custom ISRC – which means you can replace tracks like-for-like.<br>
Similarly, you can identify if it a track’s been released before, and set the original release date.</p>
<p>If you’re aiming for a multi-artist option, it’s worth knowing that all the releases appear on a single ‘Releases’ page, i.e. no separate page for each artist, in case that matters.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>I’m certain there’s not a way to migrate releases…</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Fwiw, Level Music lists ‘catalog transfer’ as part of the service, but I haven’t tried that yet and don’t know how they handle it.<br>
I couldn’t find any info in their support section, so you might need to reach out with a support question. (Consider reaching out on Twitter. It might be easier/quicker).</p>
<p>(tbh, I’ve had some issues with their support in the past, but nothing catastrophic. Just annoying.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>what ends up happening if you use two?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>If you attempt to release an existing track on a second distributor, using the original ISRC… don’t know.</p>
<p>Otherwise, you can release different tracks for the same artist. If there’s more than one artist on spotify, etc… with the same name, they’ll typically show them all and you identify the one that’s you.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>How does it appear in stores?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Only difference might be if you’ve used an auto-generated ISRC on the newer tracks. Some distributors use certain character sequences in their generated ISRC codes. Listeners won’t notice/care.</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>If you were to remove all releases from a distributor does it remove them from stores?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Yup. Functionally, they use a subscription-like model. They keep it up for as long as you subscribe, and serve as the recipient for all royalties, payments, etc…</p>
<p>Fwiw, Distrokid offers a ‘Leave a legacy’ service…</p>

Details <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/2">(click for more details)</a>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<aside class="quote no-group">
<blockquote>
<p>What happens to people who already purchased something?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>For subscription services, the tracks might disappear temporarily in the time between the old one being taken down and the new one going live. If it’s saved in a playlist, it’ll be greyed out until it is available again on the service.</p>
<p>For downloads, no difference. They’ve bought the download. They’ll still have it on their machines/devices.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 16:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-20966-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss">Changing distributors?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Changing distributors?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Been mulling this over for a hot minute, but figured I’d ask here first since I know many of you have experience with it.</p>
<p>For one, re: Distrokid, it’s 20 bones a year for one artist, I presume (or think I read here) there’s other options for multiple artist accounts. What does that run, on average?</p>
<p>How fast is the turn around for upload to release? Any involvement with support?</p>
<p>Now the million dollar question: Does anyone have experience with switching distributors? I have a small handful of releases through Amuse, I’m wondering what the deal is with changing. I know I could just put new releases through a new distributor, but would be more interested in a “single pane of glass” so to speak.</p>
<p>I’m certain there’s not a way to migrate releases, but what ends up happening if you use two? How does it appear in stores? If you were to remove all releases from a distributor does it remove them from stores? What happens to people who already purchased something?</p>
<p>Anyway. That’s all I got - any advice welcome. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/point_right.png?v=9" title=":point_right:" class="emoji" alt=":point_right:"> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/point_left.png?v=9" title=":point_left:" class="emoji" alt=":point_left:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 12:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-20966-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/changing-distributors/20966.rss">Changing distributors?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
