<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279</link>
    <description>Well..

Here we are. 3 months later, and my music has improved a lot, and I couldn&#39;t have brought myself through this amazing experience without all of you. I&#39;ve branched into many different genres such as trap, future house, future bass, and more. And-


Enough with the sloppiness just look at my [microbe](https://soundcloud.com/vulture-x/microbe-vip)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 01:57:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Ninjendo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I want to say this. There is TOO MUCH ATTACKKKKKK! A bit of lowpass and volume reduction can help. I like the piano chords and after the 2:10 minute mark with the, correct me if I am mistaken, Hour and piano sounds awesome. The “chorus” part of the song sounds a bit bland. It doesn’t grab my attention as much which is what I’m trying to say. Overall, the idea is great but I do agree with some points with <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/kip">@kiP</a>, the execution of the song can be better. I know you were trying to remix one fo your first songs, which I think is a fun idea to do, but in terms of refining your skills in production, you might want to practice a bit more to improve and move on to the next step. Like what <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/akabillposters">@akabillposters</a> said, We are all still learning and growing!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-9</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>the groan is blob in this formation</p>
<p>2 2 1 2 2 1</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/8</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 21:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like it, I’ve listened three times at this point.</p>
<p>I agree with <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/kip">@kiP</a> on a few points. The intro part doesn’t blend into the piano very well, it’s definitely abrupt. It might be too loud, if you left it filtered I think it would help. Maybe leaving it filtered and then automating piano volume to come in as that synth sound drops out maybe with delay turned up all the way for the last bar. I dunno, there’s a few ways you could slice it.</p>
<p>I’m not too concerned about drops or whatever, I can see how it’s disappointing if that’s what someone was expecting but I wasn’t necessarily. With that said, as a really thick, moody filtered piece I really enjoyed it. Sometimes that’s just what the Dr. ordered <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>The chord progression is solid, grabbed my interest immediately. At 1:06 I’m hearing this low exhaling sound almost like a groan, I don’t know if it’s just me or my headphones but it’s awesome, if that was unintentional good job if that was intentional I don’t know what you did to make that to happen but it’s genius.</p>
<p>For my tastes, the end is too abrupt. I think everyone would have different opinions there.</p>
<p>Anyway, overall I like it. I realized now the exhaling sound is another bass you bring in towards the end of the pattern, or maybe another lower note. It’s awesome.</p>
<p>Keep it up, take a break if needed but keep at it for sure I’m keeping an ear out</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/7</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 10:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well</p>
<p>I find it harder and harder to produce every day,thinking of h i a t u s</p>
<p>And btw <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/kip">@kiP</a> the song I remixed was my old one, it’s pretty trash so yeah<br>
<a href="https://app.auxy.co/projects/K-6DWfIbcyt9oUw9iz9qEw==" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://app.auxy.co/projects/K-6DWfIbcyt9oUw9iz9qEw==</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/6</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 08:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Aqzi" data-post="4" data-topic="5279">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/aqzi/40/15298_2.png" class="avatar"> Aqzi:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>bye</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Clearly the feedback bothered you, but three important things to keep in mind…</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>It may have felt harsh, but honest feedback is the only kind worth hearing, and…</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The reason it’s probably as direct as it was is because <span class="mention">@kiP</span> respects you and respects your music enough to hold it to ‘next level’ standards. You’re clearly growing as a music maker because you have more experience and you’ve developed your writing and production abilities - and it shows in your music. That’s a good sign that things are moving in a good direction.<br>
Be glad that you’re held to higher standards. The day you aren’t is the day others have stopped respecting you or your music. It’s also likely to be the day you stop growing as a music maker. Which brings me onto…</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><span class="bbcode-u">All of us</span> are still learning and still growing. Every single one of us.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=10" title=":+1:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":+1:"> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=10" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji only-emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
p.s. Worth reading…</p>
<p><a href="https://blog.landr.com/ask-feedback/" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">LANDR Blog: How To Ask For Feedback and Use it to Make Better Music</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/5</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 08:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>k thanks</p>
<div class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/4">spoiler</a></div>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/4</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 06:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Keep in mind while reading my review that I am listening without headphones, and if you think this song is a lot better with headphones, or there is a certain part I criticized that sounds way better with headphones, let me know and I’ll listen again tomorrow. Also keep in mind that this is not intended to be hurtful or offend you, this is all constructive criticism mixed with some of my own personal opinions. If you don’t agree with something, than that’s fine, but maybe you should at least try a suggest I include.</p>
<p>Ooh, the intro sounds kinda like the Bojack Horseman intro, I like that. As much as I like it with less lowpass, I don’t really like it as much when it’s fully faded in. It’s really obnoxious and in your face kinda. Some might disagree. The melody of this part I just don’t get, and nothing in me wants to get up and move to this because they’re slightly confused how to move to this. Really odd transition into the piano, it just feels really out of place. It struck out of no where. It was especially surprising with not knowing when the first run stopped or began. I really like the chords, nice! The buildup scene has got a lot of cool sounds playing around, and it builds up nice and smoothly. The drop is kind of a let down, imo. The main tune doesn’t have much support, and doesn’t give off an “epic” or “big” vibe that the buildup anticipated. And the snare. Oh, the snare. As cool and funky as it sounds, it’s just so out of place. It doesn’t fit the song and even sounds a Little’s offbeat because of the weirdness, even though it’s not. 2nd part of the drop is still meh, the only change other than the hats (which isn’t the best hat choice imo) is the piano dropping down a scale, which makes it sound weaker. After the drop: once again, I like the chords. I wish they could be more implemented into the drop, though. One thing I’ve noticed is that the progression and the drop sound like they come from multiple songs. The 2nd buildup and drop are the same as the first, which sounds repetitive. You should switch it up. I like the quick and dramatic ending.</p>
<p>In conclusion: Good song, cool effects, good ideas, but poorly executed. I hope you can agree with my feedback and take it in to make your next track even better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 06:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Microbe VIP - Vulture</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well…</p>
<p>Here we are. 3 months later, and my music has improved a lot, and I couldn’t have brought myself through this amazing experience without all of you. I’ve branched into many different genres such as trap, future house, future bass, and more. And-</p>
<p>Enough with the sloppiness just look at my <a href="https://soundcloud.com/vulture-x/microbe-vip">microbe</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 05:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5279-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/microbe-vip-vulture/5279.rss">Microbe VIP - Vulture</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
