<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>- BOUNDLESS - EOHR X INDI [Generic Auxy Bass]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982</link>
    <description>https://soundcloud.com/eohr/boundless-eohr-x-indi

This track started out as a project file literally named &quot;Generic Auxy Bass&quot; after a discussion on the Disco about genres (https://disco.auxy.co/t/auxy-bass-future-bass/7747) and how wubs are the defining feature of a lot of Auxy music from 2016-2018 or so. I wanted to recreate that as accurately as possible, so I went into the Changes demo. (If you haven&#39;t heard it, Changes by Austin Haga is one of the most essential Auxy tracks of all time, alongside Kleuren by Conux and Stratosphere by OTZSIL. Kleuren and Changes, as well as a lot of Produk&#39;s stuff are really more defining of the Auxy Bass genre.) I figured out the bass he used to get the insane weight and low-end texture to the wubs was Needy. From there, I just copied techniques I&#39;d seen or heard other Auxians use in tracks, videos, and demos.

Eventually I became stuck, with nothing but a drop that, although it sounded cool, didn&#39;t really have much in the way of the rest of the song to support it. I sent the project file (&quot;Generic Auxy Bass&quot;) to @INDIR3CT because I knew he could give me some advice on what to do with it. Little did I know, he would turn it into a full-blown track with an intro and build, plus a little melodic theme I would never have thought of.

I took what he sent over and only had to modify it a little before it was ready to release. However, it always felt like something was missing, and I never knew what that was. It&#39;s been almost a year since the original was created, but I think it&#39;s time to show you all what we put together. I&#39;m really happy with it, and I think it&#39;s a cool send-off to the years where this genre of &quot;Auxy Bass&quot; really dominated. I have to say, with the updates (5 and 6), this app has become much more versatile, and it is very noticeable in the music people put out nowadays compared to a few years ago.

Here&#39;s to more good times with Auxy and the community [spoiler]which definitely isn&#39;t dying :grimacing: :grimacing:[/spoiler].</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 14:32:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>- BOUNDLESS - EOHR X INDI [Generic Auxy Bass]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eohr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/eohr/boundless-eohr-x-indi" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/eohr/boundless-eohr-x-indi</a></p>
<p>This track started out as a project file literally named “Generic Auxy Bass” after a discussion on the Disco about genres (<a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/auxy-bass-future-bass/7747" class="inline-onebox">Auxy bass &gt; future bass</a>) and how wubs are the defining feature of a lot of Auxy music from 2016-2018 or so. I wanted to recreate that as accurately as possible, so I went into the Changes demo. (If you haven’t heard it, Changes by Austin Haga is one of the most essential Auxy tracks of all time, alongside Kleuren by Conux and Stratosphere by OTZSIL. Kleuren and Changes, as well as a lot of Produk’s stuff are really more defining of the Auxy Bass genre.) I figured out the bass he used to get the insane weight and low-end texture to the wubs was Needy. From there, I just copied techniques I’d seen or heard other Auxians use in tracks, videos, and demos.</p>
<p>Eventually I became stuck, with nothing but a drop that, although it sounded cool, didn’t really have much in the way of the rest of the song to support it. I sent the project file (“Generic Auxy Bass”) to <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/indir3ct">@INDIR3CT</a> because I knew he could give me some advice on what to do with it. Little did I know, he would turn it into a full-blown track with an intro and build, plus a little melodic theme I would never have thought of.</p>
<p>I took what he sent over and only had to modify it a little before it was ready to release. However, it always felt like something was missing, and I never knew what that was. It’s been almost a year since the original was created, but I think it’s time to show you all what we put together. I’m really happy with it, and I think it’s a cool send-off to the years where this genre of “Auxy Bass” really dominated. I have to say, with the updates (5 and 6), this app has become much more versatile, and it is very noticeable in the music people put out nowadays compared to a few years ago.</p>
<p>Here’s to more good times with Auxy and the community <span class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982/1">spoiler</a></span>.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-17982-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/boundless-eohr-x-indi-generic-auxy-bass/17982.rss">- BOUNDLESS - EOHR X INDI [Generic Auxy Bass]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
