<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>She - Hern [Experimental]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/she-hern-experimental/21180</link>
    <description>New single that may or may not be part of an upcoming project idk we&#39;ll have to see. I&#39;ve returned to my heavily sample-based and distorted style, as opposed to the style that I implemented on my last album.
In addition to returning to a style I&#39;ve previously worked with, I also am working to push myself to limits of distortion, noise, and chaos that I&#39;ve not reached before. This song has sections like that, other songs I&#39;m currently working on have that even more so. So, stay tuned for new stuff after this.

Anyway, here&#39;s the track link (Runtime = 5:07):
https://soundcloud.com/hernmusicofficial/she

Hope you guys enjoy, constructive criticism is welcome as always.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 18:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/she-hern-experimental/21180.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>She - Hern [Experimental]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hern-Meridian]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>New single that may or may not be part of an upcoming project idk we’ll have to see. I’ve returned to my heavily sample-based and distorted style, as opposed to the style that I implemented on my last album.<br>
In addition to returning to a style I’ve previously worked with, I also am working to push myself to limits of distortion, noise, and chaos that I’ve not reached before. This song has sections like that, other songs I’m currently working on have that even more so. So, stay tuned for new stuff after this.</p>
<p>Anyway, here’s the track link (Runtime = 5:07):<br>
<a href="https://soundcloud.com/hernmusicofficial/she" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://soundcloud.com/hernmusicofficial/she</a></p>
<p>Hope you guys enjoy, constructive criticism is welcome as always.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/she-hern-experimental/21180/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/she-hern-experimental/21180/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 18:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-21180-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/she-hern-experimental/21180.rss">She - Hern [Experimental]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
