<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Neon Knights - by Toothfairy Stardust</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/neon-knights-by-toothfairy-stardust/5065</link>
    <description>https://soundcloud.com/toothfairystardust

Hello Auxyfriends!

I&#39;ve made an uptempo instrumental track with some videogame and 80s touches to it. 
I&#39;m about to finish 3 tracks for a release. I&#39;m in the middle of finishing the details for the songs and trying to mix at the same time to get a feel for the final thing. If some of you can listen and give me some constructive feedback on what I can do better in the mix, or what I&#39;m doing right, it would be super helpful. Im not much of a music mixer guy so go nutz.

Currently the project is exported from Auxy and set up in Pro Tools, so I have all the tools i need to get it good. The problem is that I&#39;m no so good :slightly_smiling_face: 

Hope you like the song as well!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 13:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/neon-knights-by-toothfairy-stardust/5065.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Neon Knights - by Toothfairy Stardust</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[ToothfairyStardust]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/toothfairystardust" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/toothfairystardust</a></p>
<p>Hello Auxyfriends!</p>
<p>I’ve made an uptempo instrumental track with some videogame and 80s touches to it.<br>
I’m about to finish 3 tracks for a release. I’m in the middle of finishing the details for the songs and trying to mix at the same time to get a feel for the final thing. If some of you can listen and give me some constructive feedback on what I can do better in the mix, or what I’m doing right, it would be super helpful. Im not much of a music mixer guy so go nutz.</p>
<p>Currently the project is exported from Auxy and set up in Pro Tools, so I have all the tools i need to get it good. The problem is that I’m no so good <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slightly_smiling_face.png?v=5" title=":slightly_smiling_face:" class="emoji" alt=":slightly_smiling_face:"></p>
<p>Hope you like the song as well!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/neon-knights-by-toothfairy-stardust/5065/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/neon-knights-by-toothfairy-stardust/5065/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 09:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5065-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/neon-knights-by-toothfairy-stardust/5065.rss">Neon Knights - by Toothfairy Stardust</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
