<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Looking for producers!</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081</link>
    <description>Hey guys!

My name is Simon, am myself using Auxy, and also building a electronic production/stock music online shop. First off, moderators, and I sorry if posting ”offers” like this is no allowed, if so please let me know how I can reach out with this idea in a different way.


So: I am looking for producers who would like an extra reason to keep producing, and also the opportunity to make money off of it.

I am also myself producing music for the online shop, but there just is no way that I have the time to produce a full music library myself, and also I want a wider variety off sounds. 

Check the website out and read a bit to understand my business model: **smhmusic.com** (It is not up and running for real yet, it is just a shell.)


So, this all sounds dry and boring. What I simple am looking for is more professional electronic tracks.

Deal:
If you LEND me your music (yes, you still own the music, no rights are taken away from you) you will earn 10 USD (payed to you through Paypal) everytime your track is bought while it is in the shop, meaning 10USDxBuy. 
If you don’t want it in the shop anymore, just simply let me know and I take it down.

Lend me 1 track, sure, but lend me 50 and of course the chances of earning some money is bigger. Maybe you already have tons of tracks laying around that you don’t know what to use for? Send ’em my way! 

The only catches are (if you would call it that) that while the music is in the store it is only to be used for that purpose, and it can not be used/sold somewhere else. So while in the store, you are not free to use it somewhere else at the same time. This is obvious, since that would just create competition against the track itself. 

Another catch could be that you could end up putting time into making music and end up not earning any money since it didn’t sell. We both hope it will, but of course I can’t guarantee that. But hey, making music for no money is nothing new - it’s already what most of us are doing. That is why I created this opportunity, to be able to make some money off of our hobby. 


IF you are interested, please PM me, with your questions, and also some link to your music so I can hear your style.


Once again, I hope this doesn’t come off as shameless business spam, I am myself a true Auxy fan and user, and thought I would reach out to you guys too, since there is so much talent here.
And how cool wouldn’t it be if this became a thing and using Auxy actually led to us making money as professional music producers? 


(Of course any questions are welcome right here in the thread too.)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 11:34:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Trey]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to the shark tank.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/47</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 11:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-47</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is to be used for just as you previously said it looked like I WASN’T planning on: just like any stock mysic library, commercials etc. Feels like I have answered this question of yours a few times now.</p>
<p>The second question I won’t answer, since you are making the point that I know nothing about the stock music business. But just because my first attempt at my own stock music store isn’t all that it could be doesn’t mean I don’t know the basics of the business.</p>
<p>Why not include music on other commercial platforms? Because coming down with a good licence deal for everyone included would be too complicated, since the artists music would be too valuable, to much of ”their darlings”. I just look at myself: if my own song, under the name of Simon M Harris, was to be used somewhere I would like a waaaay better deal than selling it off cheap as the music in a stock music store does. I would want a much more complicated license deal ensuring tht my music was only used for things that benefited myself and my brand, since it would all be connected straight back to me.<br>
That’s how I feel about it, and so I want to seperate artists ”real” music from thing, and only have music intensed ONLY for this purpose.</p>
<p>I also just want to once more address the question: why should an Auxy producer choose SMH over the bigger ones? I am not saying they should. I thinking is just that I am a simole guy just like you guys here, I thought of just opening up the opportunity for whoever here wanted a simple deal and a fun way to put their music to use. If the same people was anyways going to go through the bigger machines and was planning on that, then of course this is not interesting. This was just a smaller thing where you can actually talk directly to the guy who’s gonna put your music out there.</p>
<p>By the way, I have already gone through these questions X times in my mind, even though you make it seem as though I had never thought of them. Even if the results of my planning might not be the best, please trust me I have atleast planned and thought this through alot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/46</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 01:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-46</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_spedgetti]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s would be really cool to share my music out there more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 22:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-45</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_spedgetti]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This seems really cool. I’m interested</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 22:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-44</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Giving these a read on the way home.</p>
<p>Truth told, I’m more interested in this than “making it big” – I love producing, I love writing music, it’s something I (and I suspect most of us here) <em>NEED</em> to do. It’s just in my DNA.</p>
<p>But I don’t care if my name is on it really. And if it can make a few bucks for beer or gear then cool. Plus, getting to see where someone used your tune ( as long as it’s not a sexist, racist, homophobic political hate group <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/frowning.png?v=5" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"> ) would be pretty damn neat, even if you can’t tell anyone you wrote it.</p>
<p>To this end I’m actually starting a new project <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> it won’t be popping up around here though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 19:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-43</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s worth looking into.<br>
I’ve worked with both stock music and commissioned music for projects.</p>
<p>‘Freelance composer/producer for hire’ may not be the coolest musical pathway, but it can be reasonably lucrative if you can develop relationships with ad agencies, etc…<br>
(Obviously, you’ll get more commissions if you’re not working in only one genre.)</p>
<p>And it’s still ‘making music for a living’, which can’t be bad.</p>
<p>Not typically huge figures, per commission, but £1000-2000 for a 90-sec piece wasn’t unusual.</p>
<p>Even if only as a side-project, the figures are good for some substantial extra income - certainly enough to pay for this musical habit we have.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Fwiw, a couple of articles on the stock route…</p>
<p></p><aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <img src="https://assets.guim.co.uk/images/favicons/46bd2faa1ab438684a6d4528a655a8bd/32x32.ico" class="site-icon" width="32" height="32">
      <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/money/2017/jun/10/make-music-income-stream-compose-stock-music" target="_blank" title="06:00AM - 10 June 2017" rel="nofollow noopener">the Guardian – 10 Jun 17</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    <div class="aspect-image" style="--aspect-ratio:690/362;"><img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/4257334d9b05357fd3c0f40cdd8a773ae3ac9834/0_68_2304_1382/master/2304.jpg?width=1200&amp;height=630&amp;quality=85&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;overlay-align=bottom%2Cleft&amp;overlay-width=100p&amp;overlay-base64=L2ltZy9zdGF0aWMvb3ZlcmxheXMvdGctZGVmYXVsdC5wbmc&amp;s=72627ae1b20264679ffe643b926dedb7" class="thumbnail"></div>

<h3><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/money/2017/jun/10/make-music-income-stream-compose-stock-music" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Like to make music? Turn your tunes into an income stream</a></h3>

<p>Meet the stock music composers who can make up to £30,000 a year by writing and selling the soundtracks to our digital lives</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<br>
<aside class="onebox whitelistedgeneric">
  <header class="source">
      <a href="http://soundphenomenon.weebly.com/blog/my-first-month-selling-stock-music-and-audio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Sound Phenomenon - Custom Music and Audio</a>
  </header>
  <article class="onebox-body">
    

<h3><a href="http://soundphenomenon.weebly.com/blog/my-first-month-selling-stock-music-and-audio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">My first month selling stock music and audio</a></h3>

<p>Roughly a month ago I began writing music for stock music websites. This opportunity arose as I had a couple months break in my composing of concert music and had a chance to finally pursue producing...</p>


  </article>
  <div class="onebox-metadata">
    
    
  </div>
  <div style="clear: both"></div>
</aside>
<p></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 18:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-42</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The site’s not finished yet, so I’d presume none yet.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 18:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-41</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Produk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>how much traffic does your store get to make this worth it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 15:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-40</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure. I understand.</p>
<p>So, if I may strip it back to those three questions…</p>
<p>What exactly are the tracks licensed on SMH meant to be used for?<br>
Why do you think people/companies license music from stock libraries?<br>
Why not accept tracks that are on Apple Music, Google Play, Spotify, etc…?</p>
<p>I honestly just want to understand and I think having clear answers in your head for those questions could help you solidify the idea and push it forward.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/39</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-39</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This whole thing is pretty fascinating, even beyond the scope of SMH music.</p>
<p>So, we’re probably talking shorter pieces. Non vocal I’d imagine. It’s almost like being a studio / session musician which is something I’ve always pondered… no? Sort of? I could buy into something like this…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-38</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you get B-grade stuff out of 5 hours recording and mixing, that’s you.</p>
<p>Hey akabillposters, I appreciate that you are trying to help me (I hope) but it all ends up being you putting me against the wall and me having to defend my purposes.<br>
I understand how it makes me look to not give response to all the critisism, but I’m still not all that interested in having this conversation like this.</p>
<p>So sincerily thanks for your input, you obviously seem to know what you are talking about, probably way more than me, but I am not out to win business man of the year either.</p>
<p>So that’s that, this is my thing - if my web site is not thought through enough and you called me out on it, so be it, it’s all fine by me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-37</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
<p>If they would want THAT to be able to be used as commercial music, and would want license for THAT, that would not be done through SMH.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I understood that.<br>
Which brings us back to the questions…</p>
<p>What exactly are the tracks licensed on SMH meant to be used for?<br>
Why do you think people/companies license music from stock libraries?</p>
<p>(Why not accept tracks that are on Apple Music, Google Play, Spotify, etc…?)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>…the time to make a track (let’s say 4,5 hours)…</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, yeah, the B-Grade stuff, imo.<br>
(I guess that’s fine if you’re banging stuff out aimed at stock, but…</p>

…as I said earlier… <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/36">(click for more details)</a>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Now, it’s possible that I’m missing something here.<br>
But, from what you’ve said so far, it just seems to me that there are some massive gaps in the thinking.</p>
<p>Even the fundamentals, like what uses the tracks on your site are being offered for, are very unclear.</p>
<p>Sorry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/36</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-36</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see how that was misunderstood, but I wasn’t talking about the music they offer to SMH Music, I was talking about their OTHER music, their OWN music. If they would want THAT to be able to be used as commercial music, and would want license for THAT, that would not be done through SMH.</p>
<p>As for the fees eating the price I am not going to run down a full list here, you would just have to trust me. In the end there would be more money for the producer than for me. Not much more, but more.</p>
<p>And no, the time to make a track (let’s say 4,5 hours) would maybe not be what I would spend on every track to host it, but in the long run to keep the site going and doing support and moving the website forward it would still ammount to a reasonable ammount of work.</p>
<p>I want to keep the prices low, and be able to work with using discount codes and affiliate ”finder fees”, so to increase the wage to the producer would ultimatily lead to too expensive prices which wiuld lower the chances of customers. I actually want the tracks to cost 19USD, and am thinking of changing it to that. I would probably stick to 10USD though. That is the price that I offer to the producers, no matter what. No matter what I decide to change the price to.</p>
<p>/Simon</p>
<p><a href="http://simonmharris.com">simonmharris.com</a></p>
<p><a href="http://finautsikter.se">finautsikter.se</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/35</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=pseudonym" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=pseudonym</a></p>
<p>(Use is optional)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/34</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightOwl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah I understand that now.  Do you name the artists who make the tracks on the site?  Personally, I wouldn’t want to be named for this just because I would like to keep the music I release on my own separate from the music I would put out for this purpose.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/33</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="http://smhmusic.com" class="onebox" target="_blank">smhmusic.com</a></p>
<p>smh</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/32</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="29" data-topic="10081">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/simonmharris/40/20_1.png" class="avatar"> simonmharris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Why are you saying it is not recommended for commercial use?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Because…</p>
<aside class="quote no-group" data-post="15" data-topic="10081">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/simonmharris/40/20_1.png" class="avatar"> simonmharris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Producers who want to make their music available for wider use, eg commercials etc, will have to look elsewhere. This is not that thing.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>What exactly are the tracks licensed on SMH meant to be used for?</p>
<p>Why do you think people/companies license music from stock libraries?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/31</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-31</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="16" data-topic="10081">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/simonmharris/40/20_1.png" class="avatar"> simonmharris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>With all the money going away to fees of different sorts</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’d be curious to know more about the fees you mention.</p>
<p>Hosting and bandwidth, sure. But that’s not likely to amount to more than a few cents per tracks per year, at least until you’re attracting good traffic.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The producer will absolutely make more than me for each sold track…</p>
</blockquote>
<p>If it’s really going to cost you more than $5 to host and market each track, something’s wrong.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>once a track is produced and published the job for the producer is done, while the job for me is more constant, and continues.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sorry, but I honestly expect that the producer will be putting more time and effort into each individual track than you will by hosting and marketing it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/30</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-30</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Why are you saying it is not recommended for commercial use? That is one of the biggest purposes, the purpise 100% to be a stock music library. What part in my information do you say points to it NOT being just that?</p>
<p>/Simon</p>
<p><a href="http://simonmharris.com">simonmharris.com</a></p>
<p><a href="http://finautsikter.se">finautsikter.se</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What would a ghost production site be?</p>
<p>This thing is is just a simple webshop that will sell tracks as royalty free production music, a shop where people in advertising or entertainment, or what have you, will shop for background music etc, free to the use that music without having to pay royalites, just paying once.</p>
<p>It will be original music found nowhere else, the services are cheaper than most other places and offering a simpler license the buyer can work under.</p>
<p>Makes sense? Do you know what stock music is?</p>
<p>/Simon</p>
<p><a href="http://simonmharris.com">simonmharris.com</a></p>
<p><a href="http://finautsikter.se">finautsikter.se</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s not for that, as the buyers can’t claim the tracks as their own work.</p>

Side-note… <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/27">(click for more details)</a>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
It is an unclear offer, though.</p>
<p>It’s supposedly a stock music library, but won’t/can’t/isn’t recommended to be used for situations that stock music libraries specifically exist to service (e.g. commercials, movies, etc…).</p>
<p>I’m not sure what simonmharris intended the tracks to be ‘used’ for.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/27</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 12:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NightOwl]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m just confused about what this service actually is.  Is it some type of ghost production site or what?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/26</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 12:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks man <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> Appreciate it!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/25</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 10:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="21" data-topic="10081">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/simonmharris/40/20_1.png" class="avatar"> simonmharris:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>When I say ”exclusive” I am saying tracks that you can only find in this store, nowhere else. I am not saying 25USD to buy a track exclusively.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Then, as said, it <em>is</em> licensing – particularly as you don’t limit how it can be used (i.e. fine for use in commercials, film, etc…).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>You put your music where you yourself think the best chances of revenues are, don’t you? What and how to think there is up to you.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Absolutely. Just saying you’ve not really said anything that could form a reason to pick SMH over the alternatives.</p>
<p>(Not trying to be an ar*ehole. I want you to succeed. I’m just trying to nudge you to do the kind of hard thinking that would need to go into it first, to improve your chances of succeeding.) <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=6" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/24</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 10:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Looking for producers!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[simonmharris]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yes, thanks for the tips.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081/23</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 10:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-10081-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/looking-for-producers/10081.rss">Looking for producers!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
