<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992</link>
    <description>Hey dudes. Just curious to hear what genres you guys like to produce, if I’ve missed any just let me know and I’ll fix it up.

(Note this isn’t about what genre you listen to- it’s about what you have produced and released)

[poll type=multiple min=1 max=20 public=true]
* House
* Deep House
* Progressive house
* Tropical House
* Futurebass
* Electro House
* Melbourne Bounce
* Bigroom House
* DnB
* Dubstep
* Ambient
* Chill
* Lo-Fi
* Trance
* Synthwave
* Trap
* Minimal
* Vaporwave
* Electro Swing
* Other
[/poll]</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:00:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AnirudhKhanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Honestly I just do deep house, FUTURE HOUSE (u forgot that), and trap. I also do futurebass occasionally</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/57">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/57</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-57</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[El1011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve done a lot of genres, most of them unreleased and just sitting on my phone/computer just gathering digital dust, but I think more recently I’ve found more of what I like to produce. That being dubstep, DnB, drumstep…that kind of stuff.</p>
<p>Also some genres missing:<br>
Glitch hop/ Moombachore<br>
Psy trance<br>
Breaks<br>
Hardstyle<br>
Happy hardcore</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/56">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/56</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 07:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-56</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FLB100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fan fact, google puts both Skrillex  and daft punk under EDM, even tog they’re both completely different genres</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/55">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/55</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 06:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-55</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>where’s hip hop on here?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/54">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/54</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 23:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-54</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="52" data-topic="3992">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/akabillposters/40/667_1.png" class="avatar"> akabillposters:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Does that stop ‘pop’ being a Genre?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Pop would be another, what I would call, “Phantom genre”. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/nauseated_face.png?v=5" title=":nauseated_face:" class="emoji" alt=":nauseated_face:"></p>
<p>When those who speak of their love for EDM, how is that making or showing it as a genre?</p>
<p>Personal opinion aside, given that the term EDM is used a lot in promos and events, we can assume that most people exposed to this term may associate the following music as EDM(as it is). The lack of awareness of the many(or a few) genres and sub-genres within EDM, those people will likely call the genre of whatever music EDM. This will eventually make EDM into a recognizable genre(as it might be today). But EDM isn’t practically a genre. It has no true sub-genres. If EDM fathers House(making house a sub-genre of edm), then what do you call the children of House… sub-sub-genres?<br>
To end, perhaps all genres were coined by no particular one person, but there is a logic to them.<br>
Oh, to answer your questions from your first post:<br>
Q: Is Pop a genre?<br>
A: No, it’s a term tagged to music that is currently popular. Future Bass would be Pop music currently in this community.<br>
Q: Is electronic a genre?<br>
A: Yes, it’s a “default” genre for those who tracks don’t fit in any genres or do not know what genre their tracks belong in.<br>
Q: Is EDM a subset of Electronic, Dance Music, or both (or neither)?<br>
A: No, EDM isn’t subset or sub-genre of EDM.</p>
<p>Good talk.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/53">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/53</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 18:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-53</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="51" data-topic="3992">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/alyen/40/1438_2.png" class="avatar"> Alyen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Very well said. Let say EDM as a genre, what does it add to the already existing pile of genres? I could see EDM working well with “consumers” who are look for dance music in particular. But EDM blankets a large amount of digitally created music, which is the issue for me.<br>
Let’s say you’re out partying and you hear a track that makes you want to create music like that. The track genre would be Jackin’ House, but the artist labeled it as EDM. So as you try to collect more reference material to better understand EDM, you quickly realize that all other EDM sound different than your target track</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The exact same argument could be made for ‘electronic’, ‘jazz’, ‘rock’, ‘pop’. Each of them are genres far more encompassing than the term EDM. Does that prevent them from being ‘genres’? I think you’d struggle to assert that it does. So, if we can accept that genre can be any distinction within music, from the ‘primary’ genres (e.g. rock, classical, pop, electronic, …) to the most granular, how is EDM, that sits somewhere in between, any different?</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>the artist labeled it as EDM</p>
</blockquote>
<p>How many artists do you know tag their stuff simply as ‘electronic’ or simply ‘house’. The tendency, especially amongst music marketing, is generally towards specificity - generally in service of highly targeted, highly tribal, groups.<br>
More descriptiveness allows <em>those who wish to</em> to hone in more quickly on the narrowest of distinctions.</p>
<p>However, just because ‘EDM’ is not the ‘most specific’ label that can be attached, it doesn’t stop ‘EDM’ being one of the labels that can be attached – no more than it stops ‘house’ being a genre.</p>
<p>Example:<br>
</p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708.png" title="image.png" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708_2_690x303.png" alt="image" width="690" height="303" srcset="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708_2_690x303.png, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708_2_1035x454.png 1.5x, https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708.png 2x" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/5/5ca531838226cbdbfdfcbb0c35968bc0aa9a0708_2_10x10.png"></a></div><p></p>
<p>Ask Chvrches, or any of their most dedicated fans what genre they are, there’s a good chance they’ll say ‘electro-pop’. Many Chvrches listeners would probably reject being calling it simply ‘pop’.<br>
If you asked a ‘pop’ fan if they liked Chvrches, a great many of them would say yes, because for them, they do fall within that genre.</p>
<p>Does that stop ‘pop’ being a Genre?</p>
<p>(fwiw, iTunes labels them ‘alternative’. Oddly, imo, Pitchfork refers to them as Pop/<em>R&amp;B</em>.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>As for EDM…<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/expressionless.png?v=9" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> soulless and useless.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=%22love+edm%22" rel="nofollow noopener"><em>…in your opinion</em></a>. Some will talk about their love of “EDM” with enthusiasm and excitement, because it refers to music that they find exciting and enjoyable.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
(None of this mentions the fact that EDM is, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2014/dec/04/why-music-purists-love-to-hate-steve-aoki-and-edm" rel="nofollow noopener">in some growing quarters</a>, coming to refer more specifically to the high-energy, positive vibe music of house rhythm-oriented producers such as deadmau5, Garrix, Steve Aoki and big room DJs-turned-producers.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Just to clarify, I’m saying that neither of us are entirely correct. In practice, things are always much muddier.</p>
<p>I’m not saying that EDM should replace the many, MANY sub-genres or be the <em>only</em> genre label used by music of a certain characteristic. Just that it has an established position and a useful role as a label used to identify music of certain shared characteristics — and that’s all that music genres are.</p>
<p>To my mind, to deny that is to deny the meaning of the word genre. And I don’t see why that’s a battle some are so keen to fight.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I’ll end on a quote from Chvrches…</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em>there is grey between the lines</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I’m done now. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=9" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/52">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/52</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 15:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-52</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/akabillposters">@akabillposters</a><br>
Very well said. Let say EDM as a genre, what does it add to the already existing pile of genres? I could see EDM working well with “consumers” who are look for dance music in particular. But EDM blankets a large amount of digitally created music, which is the issue for me.<br>
Let’s say you’re out partying and you hear a track that makes you want to create music like that. The track genre would be Jackin’ House, but the artist labeled it as EDM. So as you try to collect more reference material to better understand EDM, you quickly realize that all other EDM sound different than your target track. Same goes for die hard fans of particular styles, if artists start labeling dance music EDM, those fans will have a hard time finding the style they loved.</p>
<p>I understand what you’re saying but EDM has no place in being a genre… anything that could be tagged as EDM, most likely already have a proper name, which only creates confusion. The confusion can be seen when you see someone stating things like, “Trap vs EDM” or “I hate EDM, House is better”… when both (Trap, House) are EDM.<br>
After clicking on both your link, I’ve still haven’t seen EDM used as a genre professionally or not even in those links. The difference in names of genres being umbrella terms and EDM being an umbrella term, is that<br>
EDM: dance music<br>
Techno: Dark, robotic, hard sounds.<br>
House: Groove, funk.<br>
Trance: Hypnotic, melodic.</p>
<p>As you can tell, the proper names add way more dimensions to describe the music before it even hits your ears… As for EDM…<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/expressionless.png?v=5" title=":expressionless:" class="emoji" alt=":expressionless:"> soulless and useless.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/51">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/51</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 12:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-51</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="49" data-topic="3992">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/alyen/40/1438_2.png" class="avatar"> Alyen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>From my understanding EDM is an umbrella term for music made with electronics(digitally) that you can dance to(anything that could be played in a club or party setting).</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Why couldn’t that serve as the basis for something called a ‘genre’?<br>
After all, what is a ‘genre’ if not simply an umbrella term used to group together things that share certain characteristics?</p>
<p>It seems to me that there are no hard and fast rules that dictate what constitutes a definition for a genre.<br>
Some are technology-based, and more ‘outcome’-agnostic – e.g. Electronic. Some are more ‘outcome’-oriented, and more technology-agnostic – e.g. Pop</p>
<p>A good example might be Depeche Mode.<br>
In the UK, they’re probably considered part of ‘Electronic Pop’/Synth-Pop. In the US, they seem to be considered part of Rock (though the US does seem to use the term Rock more loosely than others, so…).</p>
<p>For me, it isn’t a case of clear lineages. EDM, imo, is both a descendant of ‘electronic music’ and ‘dance music’ (‘dance’ music, at least as use by most below the age of 50, has been somewhat subsumed ‘spiritually’ (albeit silently) into electronic, due to the weight of how much dance music is produced in recent decades.)</p>
<p>As someone who lived (and danced) through the early days of house and techno, it’s muddy, even to me.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>EDM… I’ve never seen it used as a genre</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I’ve seen it used many times exactly in the same way you’d use a ‘genre’…</p>
<p>e.g.<br>
<a href="https://soundcloud.com/tags/edm" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/tags/edm</a><br>
<a href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/4/4d327dc3f409ee1218cffe64d6d0683d5868db43.jpg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Spotify also appears to treat it like a genre…</a><br>
&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>The term EDM hasn’t went through such a process to be recognized as a genre, since it’s haven’t been claimed as a sub-genre by any professional</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There is no ‘Council of Music Elders’ who decide these things. They occur far more organically through a mixture of thoughts from vested listeners, such as makers, fans, journalists, etc…</p>
<p>I suspect that, despite whatever a decreasing number of ‘producers’ say or believe, EDM we’ll increasingly see EDM used as a genre. Defending the purist view is, imo, both pointless (because it’s defending <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Distinction_without_a_difference" rel="nofollow noopener">a distinction without a difference</a>) and also futile, because fewer and fewer people influencing these things are actually producers who care about a purist view of the term – and because it’s a useful descriptor and because there’s no down-side to it being used used as a genre.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I think, bottom line, it comes down to the question I asked at the start of this post…</p>
<p>What is a ‘genre’ if not simply an umbrella term used to categorise things that share certain characteristics?</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Anyhoo… <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/50">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/50</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 10:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-50</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/akabillposters">@akabillposters</a><br>
What would be the characteristics of a EDM genre track and if it’s a sub-genre where does it evolve from, in your view? From my understanding EDM is an umbrella term for music made with electronics(digitally) that you can dance to(anything that could be played in a club or party setting). Electronic/Electronica is a genre used to describe music that doesn’t fit in any other established genre. At some point, the genre House contained Techno and Trance as sub-genres… eventually they both grew big enough to be considered by (those who care to name styles) as its own genre with many sub-genres. The term EDM hasn’t went through such a process to be recognized as a genre, since it’s haven’t been claimed as a sub-genre by any professional(to my knowledge). So labeling the genre of danceable music as EDM, make as much sense as labeling music that contains a guitar “guitar music”.<br>
I’m not sure of the history of the term EDM, but I’ve never seen it used as a genre. I only see it being used as a genre by non-producers. Then again, it’s hard enough to find any information thoroughly explaining genres(&amp;sub) difference and how to properly identify them.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/49">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/49</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 08:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-49</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="42" data-topic="3992">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/alyen/40/1438_1.png" class="avatar"> Alyen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>EDM isn’t a genre</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I don’t get why is “isn’t”.</p>
<p>Is ‘Pop’ a genre? If not, what is it?<br>
Is ‘Electronic’ a genre? If not, what is it?</p>
<p>Is EDM a subset of Electronic, Dance Music, or both (or neither)?</p>
<p>If ‘electronic’ is a genre (which I currently consider/understand it to be) and (e.g.) DubStep is a (sub-)genre, then the one in between - ‘EDM’ - must surely be a genre/sub-genre too, no?<br>
People often refer to (e.g.) FB, DubStep, Big Room, Hardstyle, etc… as direct/indirect genres/sub-genres within EDM, so why wouldn’t EDM be considered as a genre/sub-genre?<br>
( I wouldn’t classify any of those as direct, first-generation offspring of ‘Electronic’.)</p>
<p>To me, it’s like saying that Jazz isn’t a genre because bebop, hard jazz, free jazz, smooth jazz, swing, ragtime, nu jazz, etc… all exist.<br>
Or saying that House isn’t a genre because of the many sub-forms of House that exist.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I know there are some genre purists who would argue the toss between genre and sub-genre, but I can’t think of a reason or situation where it doesn’t make sense to consider EDM as a genre (or sub-genre) of some type.</p>
<p>Happy to have someone explain to me why I’m wrong. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=6" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/48">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/48</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 06:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-48</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like tropical house a lot but I have only made 1 song with it</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/47">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/47</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-47</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MR_ANDERSON]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>cool. That was sort of what I was guessing</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/46">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/46</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-46</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with <span class="mention">@NYC</span></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/45</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-45</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Kerfuffle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>where’s LaserBass? <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/44</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-44</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>True</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/43</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-43</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s just that EDM isn’t a genre.<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/sweat_smile.png?v=5" title=":sweat_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":sweat_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/42</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-42</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oh, don’t worry. I’m fairly certain that my songs aren’t edm (except for a few)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/41</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-41</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>EDM sums up a large spectrum of genres</p>
<p>Your stuff reminds me of house and future bass though</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/40</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 02:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-40</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MR_ANDERSON]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not sure what category most of my stuff fits into…actually, if anybody wants to listen to my music and tell me what genre it is, that’d be great. I’ve never really known. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/laughing.png?v=5" title=":laughing:" class="emoji" alt=":laughing:">   I guess I just make music, and thats all it is</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/38</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-38</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="18" data-topic="3992" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/notmiles/40/3685_1.png" class="avatar"> NotMiles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Idk. I just slap an “electronic” tag on my songs and call it a day.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Just whatever you do, don’t call it EDM.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/37</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-37</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like it that way too</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/36</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-36</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="18" data-topic="3992">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/notmiles/40/3685_1.png" class="avatar"> NotMiles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I just slap an “electronic” tag on my songs and call it a day.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I’m the same with bolting “-jazz” or “electro-“ onto something. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I’m rarely 100% certain that I’ve tagged a track using an accurate genre.<br>
My tracks are real mutts - but I kinda like it that way.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey, <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/azureonyx">@AzureOnyx</a> and <span class="mention">@shanebrownofficial</span>, are you producing Vaporwave in Auxy? Not really my genre, but I’d definitely be interested to hear that.</p>
<p>Could you share a link or two here (or PM them to me)? <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 08:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>NO HIP-HOP HERE. I’m ashamed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 03:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>[POLL] Top Produced Genres</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m not surprised that Future Bass is the most created genre</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992/32</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 04:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-3992-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/poll-top-produced-genres/3992.rss">[POLL] Top Produced Genres</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
