<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276</link>
    <description>https://app.auxy.co/projects/hl-v_-RSonUGVuLiyCt0BQ==</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 07:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Phoenix]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Nice job bro the track has a lot of potential<br>
I fixed up a few parts and added my touch hope you enjoy</p>
<p><a href="https://app.auxy.co/projects/MuxUVagnQlf_D-Jmis6beA==" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://app.auxy.co/projects/MuxUVagnQlf_D-Jmis6beA==</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 07:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dj_Gravitas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I have listened to a few of your Songs. I just love them and I have followed you. And surely I would want feedback from you for any progressive house Track I make. Thanks for such a generous offer.  Have a nice day!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 07:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="Dj_Gravitas" data-post="3" data-topic="5276">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://avatars.discourse-cdn.com/v4/letter/d/57b2e6/40.png" class="avatar"> Dj_Gravitas:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Usually I make Progressive House</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I love you <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/heart.png?v=10" title=":heart:" class="emoji" alt=":heart:"></p>
<p>If you ever want private feedback on a progressive house track, hit me up! <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grinning_face_with_smiling_eyes.png?v=10" title=":grinning_face_with_smiling_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":grinning_face_with_smiling_eyes:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 05:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zeph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see a big block of text… I upvote.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 04:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dj_Gravitas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank You Kip For your Honest feedback. It was actually the first time I actually tried making a Future Bass Track. Usually I make Progressive House or Future House kinda’ stuff but still having an honest feedback is very essential to keep evolving your style and making it better as you go on. So thanks again.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 04:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Not listening with headphones right now, so if you recommend it let’s me know and I’ll re-review your track.</p>
<p>Before I even get into the track, though, I would highly suggest getting soundcloud and posting on there. That way more people would be willing to click the link and check it out. It also shows how much you’re growing as an artist.</p>
<p>Alright, getting into it, flag kind of gives a really hard punch at the beginning that should be softened. It’s also just overall very strong of a bass, and maybe should be turned down. It’s a little hard to review the bass though without headphones. Next up, I don’t think Corn is he best instrument to go with, especially for the intro. Though, I do like the melody. The transition from 2nd to the 3rd scene is good. 3rd scene sounds great! I’m not a big fan of otter for a couple reasons, but you make it work well. Maybe layer it with another’s good synth like silk (if you have the AP)? The melody sounds better layered but I’m still not a big fan of the corn. Also, switch up the beat a bit, instead of having the same 1-bar beat. Scene 7: The downward sweeper starts a little too loud, especially transitioning into a calmer scene. Also, the snare-claps from Dollar used to build up sounds bad because of the clap. I’d take it out and layer with a different clap or snare. Also, something that I suck at, is that the pattern the snares use when rolling up in the buildup is poor, and they only build up for 1 bar, which sounds to quick and uncomfortable. The drop is great, it really progresses from the prior scene and makes the song feel huge. I love the bass and how it stops with the snare, it’s something I love to hear in music, and something I need to do more. The sweeper at the 2nd scene in the drop is just unnecessary. Also, one very important thing I’ve noticed is that the same melody runs throughout the whole song, maybe change it up at one point, or have it stop for some scenes, or make the intro introduce it later on, or something. After the second scene in it, the drop does not switches up or progress an de it just sounds repetitive and boring. After the drop, the melody finally changes! Yes! And it still sounds good! One thing that I notice in a lot of songs is that the first melody is good, but then he second one they introduce is just sad. After that nice moment of refreshing my mind with a new melody, it goes steaight back to the old melody, and the same buildup from before. And the drop is the same, too! Not good! Like with buildups, I’m not good at 2nd drops, but at least try to make it different from the first. Even if it’s the same tunes but in different order. Nice dramatic ending, but why is the kick invisible and giving ducker to strain? Doesn’t sound good. Also, something else would probably sound better in place of Strain, like maybe otter (or again, Silk, if you have it).</p>
<p>Other than what I mentioned, it’s a good song with a great tune! Most of your errors were small, but we all know small problems come together to make big problems. Your song could sound so much better taking in my feedback for consideration. Take your time!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 05:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dj_Gravitas]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://app.auxy.co/projects/hl-v_-RSonUGVuLiyCt0BQ==" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://app.auxy.co/projects/hl-v_-RSonUGVuLiyCt0BQ==</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 03:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5276-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/untitled-dj-gravitas-project/5276.rss">Untitled - DJ_Gravitas [Project]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
