<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837</link>
    <description>Whenever I try to sing to some of the stuff I make, the sounds that escape my lips are utterly horrible -- some sort of moaning to the tune that is already there. Anyone have any tips on how you prepare a track that&#39;s intended to have vocals?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 11:58:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Check out this video…</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="63" data-topic="2333">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/akabillposters/40/667_1.png" class="avatar"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/post-writing-and-production-tips-links-embeds-only/2333/63" rel="nofollow noopener">Post writing and production tips (links &amp; embeds only)</a>
</div>
<blockquote>
<p>More insights into how Ed Sheeran’s Shape of You started and came together musically and lyrically.  (I know I might bang on about this track, but it’s a ridiculously successful track with lots said about from a writing and production POV, so it’s a really good case study.)  In this video, there’s also a glimpse of a pretty sweet counter-melody that never made it into the final track.)</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/7</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 11:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew_Adams]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/akabillposters">@akabillposters</a> has a ton of great advice. I would also add that something I like to do is make a lead (to represent the melody) in Auxy, and then get rid of it when you’re ready to record the vocals.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 18:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My approach would be to start with lots of passive and active listening. (Links below.)</p>
<p>The aim is to become so familiar with the music that melodic ideas start to come naturally – as naturally as singing along to any other piece of music.</p>
<p>So, sing along to it, whether you have lyrics yet or not. Hum, whistle, yodel, whatever you’re most comfortable with.</p>
<p>If you have the lyrics, then play around with different takes on that.</p>
<p>Experiment, but be mindful of ‘phrasing’. (Link below)</p>
<p>Aim to create a pattern of phrasing that complements the rhythm of the music. e.g. If your music is heavily syncopated, then you might want to use syncopated vocal phrasing to double down on that – or go with a less syncopated vocal to balance it out.</p>
<p>You might want to echo/reflect certain details in the music – e.g. if you use <a href="http://www.edisoft.com/blog/2011/12/13/what-is-a-musical-run/">runs</a> as part of the character of the music, you might want to have runs in the vocal melodies too.</p>
<p>(* Ideally, music, lyrics and vocals come together as part of a single process, rather than – e.g. <em>'I’ve written a dark track, so <em>I guess</em> I should now think up some dark lyrics</em>’. It’s not always how things go in reality, but that’s the ideal – that everything is created authentically from the same starting vision.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
In terms of ‘getting it down’, again don’t be afraid to use your own voice. It might sound rough, but it’s likely to be the musical tool you can use most expressively — and expressiveness is what you’re after.</p>
<p>I use the <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/music-memos/">Apple Music Memos</a> app, even for recording ideas for musical licks – again, singing, humming and whistling along as I play the track over and over in the background, when I’m working on a track.</p>
<p>Unless you’re a virtuoso and can play a melody as naturally and as effortlessly as you can think of one, using an instrument for the guide vocal melody can be difficult, as it can be hard to distance yourself from trying to make it sound ‘right’ in the mix…</p>
<p>…there’ll also be a lot of work to emulate the expressiveness of a vocal in Auxy too.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Importantly, don’t rush it. Enjoy it.<br>
But, remember, <a href="https://blog.landr.com/5-signs-perfectionism/">it doesn’t need to be perfect</a> – it’s a guide.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Once you have the main vocal melody down, passively and actively listen to that for a while (hours, days, weeks, whatever feels right) – as ideas will start to come for harmonies or alternative melodies.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
<a href="https://makingmusic.ableton.com/active-listening">Ableton: Active Listening</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ndra6fWI0fc?autoplay=1&amp;feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ndra6fWI0fc</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cN0IqiZD-6s?autoplay=1&amp;feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">https://www.youtube.com/embed/cN0IqiZD-6s</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UWwopW5YuX0?autoplay=1&amp;feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">https://www.youtube.com/embed/UWwopW5YuX0</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheRealJFalc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Usually, the melody follows the chords of a song to some extent with variations between chords to spice things up a bit. You’d need to make sure that the notes are: in chord and key and also whether or not it’s taking too much away from the rest of the song.</p>
<p>I wonder how spoken word fits into all this though.</p>
<p>(edit: Just listen to the guy below me, he knows what he’s talking about)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/4</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool, there’s some good advice. And I was thinking of making “Demos” so I won’t be judged too harshly for being born to a family of awful voices. Just truly awful…</p>
<p>Anyway, how do you usually go about writing the melody of the vocals? Would you throw in a piano track as a guide for what sounds good?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 11:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Five (and a half) quick tips…</p>
<ol>
<li>Leave space in the music for vocals - i.e. avoid having other leads or counter-melodies active in the vocal range where vocals are present. They could end up competing for attention and muddying the listening experience.</li>
<li>Be cautious about using vocal melodies that have complex, fiddly or large jumps p (unless you’re making that part of the hook)</li>
<li>Keep lyrics structurally simple. Few things scream badly written lyrics (or poor vocal interpretation) more than cramming words into parts of a bar - throwing the pacing rhythm/ pacing off - because music and lyrics were written in isolation from each other.</li>
<li>Understand the message of every line. It’s not about being overly affectatious, but making sure the key elements of the story the lyrics tell is being communicated. (I’ve seen this one get sacrificed because of point 3.)</li>
<li>Remember there are two parts to any vocal (and vocalist): the style (delivery/performance) and the voice. Both need to be right.</li>
</ol>
<p>5.5. If in doubt or if you’re not doing the track justice, put down your own vocal as a guide - and then get an experienced (and capable/talented) vocalist to put down the final version. They might (arguably should) also be able to spot issues with all the above points.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
(To clarify, ‘experienced, capable and talented’ doesn’t necessarily mean ‘can sing like Ariana Grande’. The perfect vocal for a track really depends on the track. Sometimes ‘imperfect’ is what makes it perfect. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 08:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to make music fit for lyrics?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Whenever I try to sing to some of the stuff I make, the sounds that escape my lips are utterly horrible – some sort of moaning to the tune that is already there. Anyone have any tips on how you prepare a track that’s intended to have vocals?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-5837-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-music-fit-for-lyrics/5837.rss">How to make music fit for lyrics?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
