<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233</link>
    <description>Good ol’ power electronics. Over saturated bass, sound clipping, dirty distortion, and just a racket in general. 
It’s ugly, much like the title (German) Weltschmerz - direct translation: world pain. But German is way more complicated so it’s more a general despair and angst.
https://soundcloud.com/devoidofjoy/weltschmerz</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 07:25:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wagneric]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What gets me with Gobekli Tepe is its age and symbolism, and the fact that it’ll take another century to uncover all of the circles, whereas Stonehenge is just one, and far newer.  I just read that its builders were evidently farmers who had travelled from near Turkey, so maybe there’s a direct lineage between the two.  The pyramids in Egypt (and those crazy-huge/ultra-precise boxes at Saqqara - I devoted a track to them), and the earthquake-proof architecture in Peru are a different mystery in terms of their engineering prowess. I saw a little in Mexico as well.  I want to learn how they did all that so I can build megaliths in my yard (seriously).</p>
<p>I recently happened to observe that a given star’s twinkling is completely different over the distance between two eyes, which surprised me.  While it wouldn’t be fun to have to fend off dire wolves and such, it would sure be nice to be able to devote one’s being to simple and true observation and realization, finding ways to pass along knowledge and awareness directly.</p>
<p>What Auxy is lacking the most for me, in terms of quality, is proper EQ – either individual instruments or final mastering.  The defaults don’t work well for most of the genres I like to play with and I end up low-passing things to reduce harshness, but then the clarity suffers.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 07:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks bud, you’re probably one of a small group that can probably stand most of my stuff here lol <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=9" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"> I never venture into the trap or future bass realms so most just pass my stuff up. Given your listening history I doubt anything I make is gonna be too harsh for ya by any stretch of the imagination.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hm… gobekli tepe used to have me enamored but as I’ve mulled it over more and more throughout the years I don’t find it to be anymore or less note worthy than stone hinge or the pyramids. 12,000 years seems like a very long time but given humans have be making hand axes well upto 250-300 thousand yrs ago, I’m guessing a lot of info leading to gobekli tepe is forever lost (I will say with out the need to fund your lifestyle with capitalism you’d have a lot more time to establish cosmological understandings than the average light polluted city dwellers of today.) The hinges of the Amazon intrigue me though, not nearly as old but very befuddling with the whole not knowing what Amazonian populations actually were in the past.</p>
<p>I agree about Auxy though, it is a good sketch book for sound, I never feel as though anything is an actual finish product when I finish a track up, still too many restrictions and I don’t ever think I can get the quality completely to my liking. Could just all be ignorance on my part there though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Dadmother]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I love both of the visceral essence of your power electronics music as well as the educational and insightful nature of this whole topic thread. It’s always a personal joy to see one of your tunes come up in the feed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/5</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 01:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wagneric]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I took German in highschool and regret I didn’t get further.  Language is fascinating, and frustrating.  My biggest history question revolves around Gobekli Tepe in Turkey: 12000 years ago, what language was being used to plan and execute 1500 years of precisely-aligned megalithic construction cycles that appear to reflect knowledge or at least observation of precession… before pottery, writing, agriculture, etc.? Was there music?</p>
<p>It’s great that you’re experimenting.  Insufflation is sounding more refined, more classically industrial?</p>
<p>Some of my music has been called epic, but — as on paper — I just like to doodle until all the available space is used up.  In my perfect universe I’d be able to write for machine shop, freight train, small earthquakes, orchestra, and piles of electronics and keyboard instruments — anything that makes sound.  But Auxy is an okay sketch pad/proxy for now.  Just need a proper looping situation, as discussed; with full feedback, fed from a mixer, you have infinite multitracking.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 18:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah German is a rough language to translate from. Even though English is of a Germanic orgin with a heavy mix of Nordic, Latin, and a bunch of minor sub-languages I’m sure if trace back as close to protolanguages.<br>
But the Germans still make up words with new meanings that are more precise and niche than what translates to English. I blame philosopher; Hegel, Heidegger, Wittgenstein, etc… I’ll give it a gander this weekend.<br>
I’m not sure where I’m going sounds wise in recent, it’s been all over the place different bpm’s, using instruments new to me. But I think I’m striving for a bigger more epic sound essentially.<br>
This is the last I’ve put much time into recently. I’ve got a busy schedule coming up so I’m not sure how much I’ll get done this next few weeks.<br>
</p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BP8hbt8TgCg?autoplay=1&amp;feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">https://www.youtube.com/embed/BP8hbt8TgCg</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 17:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[wagneric]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I like this.  You’re returning to elemental form in a way.</p>
<p>Since we’re apparently operating on different subcarriers of the same wavelength…</p>
<p>I’ve long been obsessed with a particular piece of “classical” music, that I grew up hearing my dad playing from day 0 (or negative for that matter).  The composer included some German text in the score, and I recently asked a German speaker to read it informally, recorded with my phone.  I ended up deconstructing the speech in purely acoustic/musical terms and then putting it back together again, and here’s the result in case you’re interested.  The translation from Wikipedia (which I’m told could use some help) is in the description, and if you read it I’d be curious what you think.</p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/wagneric/20190412-schufan-schlegel-am-r1" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/wagneric/20190412-schufan-schlegel-am-r1</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Good ol’ power electronics. Over saturated bass, sound clipping, dirty distortion, and just a racket in general.<br>
It’s ugly, much like the title (German) Weltschmerz - direct translation: world pain. But German is way more complicated so it’s more a general despair and angst.<br>
<a href="https://soundcloud.com/devoidofjoy/weltschmerz" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/devoidofjoy/weltschmerz</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15233-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/weltschmerz-devoid-of-joy-power-electronics/15233.rss">Weltschmerz - Devoid of Joy (power electronics)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
