<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082</link>
    <description>I’m hoping to put some tracks on Spotify sometime soon, most likely using Amuse. 
Anyone have any opinions on whether it’s better to release singles as you finish them, or wait and release an EP/Album?
I feel like it probably doesn’t matter, but maybe you can think of something I haven’t thought of.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 22:20:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[aUstin_Haga]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you don’t have more than one lined up and don’t create tracks very fast, releasing as singles can both potentially increase each individual track’s popularity and make it seem like you’re more active as opposed to taking a really long time to get 4+ tracks lined up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 22:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-21</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Cool, thank!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/20</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 16:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-20</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group quote-modified" data-username="NickElle" data-post="18" data-topic="6082">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/nickelle/40/10854_2.png" class="avatar"> NickElle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m just being an idiot.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>But, let me finish with again apologizing for the negative vibes, and for generalizing things. Please forgive me.<br>
No hard feelings, I hope?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Nono.<br>
Hey, certainly no hard feelings and nothing to apologise for, imo.<br>
S’all good <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=10" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>I did kinda give you both barrels for the ‘argument’ statement, when I shouldn’t have. It’s just that I’ve had that word levelled at me in an accusatory way multiple times here - invariably due to a misunderstanding of my straight-talking, often wordy writing style - which, I understand can sometimes feel like a barrage.</p>
<p>I’m just not a fan of having my intentions assumed wrongly - and negatively. <span class="hashtag">#triggered</span> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=10" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Thanks for inputting. It’s always good to have more experience and knowledge available on this forum.<br>
Glad you’re here.</p>
<p>As mentioned, I’ll get back with my friends input.</p>
<p>More insights = a more accurate overall picture. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=10" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/19</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-19</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m sorry for thinking you were arguing.<br>
Please forgive me.</p>
<p>You’re right for asking smart questions.<br>
I’m just being an idiot.</p>
<p>Yes, I did make a generalization on saying ALL label do that.<br>
I also made an assumption that you’d be submitting to an Electronic label. That’s usually how the music business works for Electronic, but I am not 100% certain in Pop music.<br>
I do know that major labels take “unfinished” aka old tracks that artists have and basically rebrand the track and release like new, so you are right on that point, but most Electronic labels are not owned by majors.</p>
<p>But, let me finish with again apologizing for the negative vibes, and for generalizing things. Please forgive me.<br>
No hard feelings, I hope?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/18</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-18</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok, let’s get one thing straight. I wasn’t arguing with you.<br>
That may have been how you were coming at it, but it wasn’t how I was coming at it.<br>
It’s possible to have a conversation about differing viewpoints without it being an argument.</p>
<p>(I’m not sure why that seems such an alien concept on this forum, and it gets quite tedious to have that word trotted out as often as it is. The fragility of this place can be quite frustrating.)</p>
<p>But hey… moving on.</p>
<p>I assumed it would be clear that I have no direct experience in the music industry. After all, I was the one asking questions while avoiding making any broad categorical assertions about how the industry does or doesn’t work.</p>
<p>I’m largely going by what I do know about commercial businesses (having worked in marketing for years) - plus what I pick up from friends and acquaintances who are music producers and composers in the music business.<br>
Additionally, I know of examples where ‘released’, yet unsigned, material has later been picked up by a label and given a commercial release.<br>
(Basically, the thing you asserted doesn’t happen, well, I’ve seen that happen.)</p>
<p>As I started by saying, if it was such a hard and fast rule, I was surprised that it was never mentioned in a recent conversation with one such friend in the biz (signed to a label for her tracks, while also working as a professional composer, both for at least 10 years). In contrast to your assertion, she specifically proposed they be (finished up and) sent to her label contacts with a view to getting the tracks signed, all while knowing the tracks were already available on SoundCloud (because that’s where she went to hear them).</p>
<p>I did email her asking specifically about the point you raised and I’ll post here when she gets back to.</p>
<p>Still, you now appear to be saying that only “most” label contacts (that you know) only want unreleased material. Had that been the extent of your statement at the start, rather than implying that no label will be interested in tracks that have already been on SoundCloud, this whole digression could have been avoided.</p>
<p>Even so, I’d still genuinely like to hear your thoughts on my point about labels buying artist back catalogues - and what bearing it has on the topic being discussed.</p>
<p>Sorry if this seems like I’m going off at you. I’m not.<br>
I’m just trying to as clear as possible about where my impressions and understanding comes from - and why I was so sceptical about your assertions.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/17</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 01:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-17</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Okay, I’m tired of arguing, so let me ask you something.</p>
<p>Do you have any experience in the music industry?</p>
<p>Yes, I do have a release on another label that is not my own. I have no affiliation with the other label.</p>
<p>Ps. I have a list of tons of label’s contact info that I have collected over time, and most of them say they ONLY want unreleased, original (no remixes) and no illegal samples.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/16</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-16</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It simply sounds like odd business for a label to turn down a track that might be buzzy, simply because they weren’t there at the start.</p>
<p>If they could sign it, and take their percentage going forward, why wouldn’t they?<br>
Especially if the track is considered to have real commercial potential, but simply hasn’t reached a proper audience yet.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Not challenging you, but do you have material signed to a 3rd-party label?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/15</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-15</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just because it’s unsigned doesnt mean its unreleased. It’s not exclusive. The world gets to here it.<br>
If the track is out on any place, it’s not exclusive.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/14</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-14</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NickElle" data-post="12" data-topic="6082">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/nickelle/40/10854_2.png" class="avatar"> NickElle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>They might listen to and like your old stuff, but they won’t release it because they want exclusive rights.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>…which they would get, presumably. If previous stuff was unsigned, then they could get the exclusive rights for the back catalogue. Seems to me that the Rights wouldn’t be the issue.</p>
<p>Although on a different scale to what we’re talking about, the rights to back catalogues for popular artists are bought and sold all the time. So, it’s not quite as clear cut to say that ‘labels don’t want previously released material’.</p>
<p>If it’s unsigned, but still attracting buzz, I’m guessing they’d figure out a way to get their slice out of signing it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/13</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-13</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most of the time, labels only take unreleased content. They might listen to and like your old stuff, but they won’t release it because they want exclusive rights.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 23:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-12</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlaMeese]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree. Most of the stuff that I’ve put on Spotify have either been old tracks, because I just started releasing, or new tracks that come out on Spotify a week or two after SC. I plan on changing how I release things in the future, but for now I’m just releasing things that I would’ve release right away if I had been able to.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 22:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-11</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-username="NickElle" data-post="9" data-topic="6082">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/nickelle/40/10854_2.png" class="avatar"> NickElle:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>As far as “flipping” some of your tracks to send to labels, I don’t think that’s wise. Labels want exclusive, unreleased material. They don’t want rereleases because they lose money off of them, for the same reason as I said earlier.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Even if the track(s) in question have only been released on SC and have only attracted a couple of hundred plays? Is that going to bother them enough to say no?</p>
<p>My most played tracks barely nudge 200 plays, so it’s not as if the world’s already heard them. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=10" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I had a pro producer/composer friend/acquaintance check out my stuff on SC, primarily for feedback, but she suggested that with a little engineering, mix and mastering (which she offered to help me with), they’d be quality, release-ready tracks and she’d be happy and confident passing them forward to her contacts at labels.</p>
<p>Not saying you’re wrong, just that she never flagged it. I’ll bounce it off her to see what she says.</p>
<p>Now, to be honest, it’s not going to kill me to make everything on SC private. I’m not gonna be upsetting large numbers of listeners, let alone fans.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
[Edit…</p>
<p>Additional thought…</p>
<p>With labels, wouldn’t it be the case that they’ll take on the unsigned back-catalogue as part of the agreement that they get the future material?</p>
<p>Obviously, this isn’t reflective of the scenario that you’re pimping an unsigned and unreleased track around to the labels, but once you’ve got that relationship up and running?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/10</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 18:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-10</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t mean to sound critical, but yes, I do think SC releases are freebies. Not that they’re cheap music. They’re great. They’re just for free and not sold. Again, I’m not knocking this model of doing things. In fact, Bitbird (San Holo’s label) releases most projects for free, even though they’re making money on sales and streams.</p>
<p>Here’s an example of what I mean by planning: Say you’ve got 2 tracks you’re working on. One is a collab track that you are on, and the other is your own original music.<br>
You like the collab, but it’s not really your style, because it’s a combination of your’s and someone else’s, and the solo track is your “baby.” You slave over that track because you want it to be perfect.<br>
So, when both are done, which would you like to have a bigger release?<br>
The collab that doesn’t rep you as much or your "baby?"<br>
I’d release the collab on SC for free and my original for monetization.</p>
<p>As far as “flipping” some of your tracks to send to labels, I don’t think that’s wise. Labels want exclusive, unreleased material. They don’t want rereleases because they lose money off of them, for the same reason as I said earlier.</p>
<p>I agree with the demo thing, though.<br>
I released my music to be sold, but I uploaded little previews to SC and attached the “Buy Link” to it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/9</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 18:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-9</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d agree, in principle, but…</p>
<p>Most here will have reasonably extensive back catalogues of tracks on SC – and the desire to treat it all more professionally.</p>
<p>If it’s a bad idea to pull tracks off of SC and then ‘release’/monetise them elsewhere, then many here are gonna be kinda stuffed, having to ‘write-off’ their existing body of work as freebies/giveaways and then create a new body of work before they can step up to a more pro approach.</p>
<p>I certainly plan to flip some of mine to commercial release (after a little bit of production fix up and a proper mix and master). Although, I plan to push mine through a label, rather than ‘self-release’.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Besides, look at the SoundCloud charts and there’s no shortage of commercial releases - e.g. Post Malone’s Rockstar has 103M SC plays. Full track, not a preview. So… <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/man_shrugging.png?v=5" title=":man_shrugging:" class="emoji" alt=":man_shrugging:"><br>
(Presumably they’re making their commercial $SC via the ad impressions, so it’s not really a giveaway, per se.)</p>
<p>So, perhaps the SC plan should be to join <a href="https://soundcloud.com/you/premier">SC Premier</a>, which allows you to monetise track plays, etc…</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Aside to OP:</p>
<p>It’s worth checking out the options to attach ‘Buy links’ to a SC post (available in the Metadata tab when editing track info).</p>
<p>Consider posting a short (e.g. 30-sec) preview on SC, with a Buy link to the download site/page.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/8</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[phenylalanine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow! A lot of good points here. I guess I have some things to think about.<br>
Thank you <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slightly_smiling_face.png?v=5" title=":slightly_smiling_face:" class="emoji" alt=":slightly_smiling_face:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/7</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 17:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I don’t know if it’s wise to release them on SC before selling your projects.<br>
Releasing them for free in SC then putting out for money kinda weakens the punch of your music’s impact.<br>
Doing that is called a “rerelease.” It is helpful when you want to give new life into a track that is SUPER old (like years and years old), but  rereleasing a track that is new (even one that is a year old) will make your brand look like a spammer.</p>
<p>I would suggest planning on which singles, EPs, LPs to release for profit beforehand so your projects don’t end up shooting themselves in the foot.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/6</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BlaMeese]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s always a good Idea to put a few singles out ever once in a awhile but an album is also something you could be working on in the background. I release all my tracks on SC first before Spotify just to see what people like the best as a kind of test to see what I should put on Spotify.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/5</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m with <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/NickElle">@NickElle</a> on this one.<br>
I’d get the good stuff out there as soon as it’s ready.</p>
<p>My own playlists contain many artists who only had a single track released on Spotify when I added them - and yet, that one track has been out there, getting them exposure and finding its way onto playlists - which is where people most likely encounter them.</p>
<p>I’d recommend checking out the LANDR Blog. It has lots of useful and insightful articles about promotion, including how to approach getting your music onto playlists.</p>
<p><a href="https://blog.landr.com/?s=playlist" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://blog.landr.com/?s=playlist</a></p>
<p>There’s also the ‘digital’ factor. EPs and albums have become less important in the age of digital streaming. They’re still great for deepening a fanbase, making fans of a track into fans of an artist - or for establishing credentials as a ‘similar artist’ through which many listeners discover artists.<br>
But, it remains the case that music is increasingly discovered by mechanisms set up to promote single tracks.</p>
<p>One thing you can do is check through the releases of your favourite artist who had small beginnings, but who now get good play numbers.</p>
<p>Look for patterns.<br>
Did they start with an EP? (Were there guest remixers that might have helped feed across new listeners)?<br>
Or did they drop a series of singles and then an EP or album?<br>
Was that EP/album new material or mostly a gathering of existing materials?</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Re: Off-putting upload issues.</p>
<p>I’d suck up any First-World upload problems, rather make your future audience wait.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Bottom line, imo, don’t wait. Your starting strategy should be aimed at getting heard. That ain’t happening while you’re holding back on your first releases.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 08:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pinewoodog]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If you’re using Spotify, I would wait and put it in an EP or Album. In my experience, it’s better having less things to deal with. The less times you have to upload something the better. Maybe the tracks can be released as they are finished on SoundCloud?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 23:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NickElle]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think singles are best and all the while you’re working on an album. When the album is done, you set a release date, and put it out.</p>
<p>Using this method, you get both. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 23:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[phenylalanine]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m hoping to put some tracks on Spotify sometime soon, most likely using Amuse.<br>
Anyone have any opinions on whether it’s better to release singles as you finish them, or wait and release an EP/Album?<br>
I feel like it probably doesn’t matter, but maybe you can think of something I haven’t thought of.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 23:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6082-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/spotify-singles-or-ep-albums/6082.rss">Spotify: Singles or EP/Albums?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
