<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lightning Teaser - Zeph</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345</link>
    <description>*Creds to Austin and Goxenar for authorizing me to Sample/Remix*

Hey guys, just wanted to pop in and tease my upcoming release. I have been working on it for almost a *year*! It&#39;s pretty crazy how far the track has come as I have been learning and teaching myself some handy things. It&#39;s almost a completely different song than from when I worked on it the very first week.

Of course, beta testing for Henrik and Fredrik, work, and life in general have slowed down my production grind, but I am happy to finally be able to release a full blown track in almost 6 months of absence. I hope you guys that are a fan of dubstep, trap, riddim, etc. enjoy this track. I drew a lot of inspiration from Virtual Riot and Rickyxsan, they&#39;ve been killing it lately. 

This track has been through it all: lost work, lost samples, complete reworks, key changes, tempo changes, mass loop genocide, phone overheating, iCloud breaking, 7 different instrument packs, broken friendships, 2 jobs, multiple victory royales, and sleepless nights.

So without further ado, here is a taste:
https://soundcloud.com/zephsound/lightning-teaser
The full 5 minute release will be sometime in March

Yes, this is all Auxy... and just 8 fat drumkits filled with samples ;)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 20:08:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Work in Progress</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Lightning Teaser - Zeph</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zeph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yeah, I am excited as well. I’m just adding the finishing touches, I’m glad you liked it <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/smile.png?v=6" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/3</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 20:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-14345-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345.rss">Lightning Teaser - Zeph</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lightning Teaser - Zeph</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[anon34001995]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Yoo this sounds cool. I’m excited to hear the full track!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 19:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-14345-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345.rss">Lightning Teaser - Zeph</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Lightning Teaser - Zeph</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Zeph]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><em>Creds to Austin and Goxenar for authorizing me to Sample/Remix</em></p>
<p>Hey guys, just wanted to pop in and tease my upcoming release. I have been working on it for almost a <em>year</em>! It’s pretty crazy how far the track has come as I have been learning and teaching myself some handy things. It’s almost a completely different song than from when I worked on it the very first week.</p>
<p>Of course, beta testing for Henrik and Fredrik, work, and life in general have slowed down my production grind, but I am happy to finally be able to release a full blown track in almost 6 months of absence. I hope you guys that are a fan of dubstep, trap, riddim, etc. enjoy this track. I drew a lot of inspiration from Virtual Riot and Rickyxsan, they’ve been killing it lately.</p>
<p>This track has been through it all: lost work, lost samples, complete reworks, key changes, tempo changes, mass loop genocide, phone overheating, iCloud breaking, 7 different instrument packs, broken friendships, 2 jobs, multiple victory royales, and sleepless nights.</p>
<p>So without further ado, here is a taste:<br>
<a href="https://soundcloud.com/zephsound/lightning-teaser" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/zephsound/lightning-teaser</a><br>
The full 5 minute release will be sometime in March</p>
<p>Yes, this is all Auxy… and just 8 fat drumkits filled with samples <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-14345-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/lightning-teaser-zeph/14345.rss">Lightning Teaser - Zeph</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
