<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Is this a scam?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134</link>
    <description>So I was browsing my notifications when I saw this:  ![53%20PM|341x171](upload://bxbYC3byLrX0BwKlEsqkjxk3rrd.png) 
Have any of you seen this message before? I was just wondering, because if any of you guys had had the exact same message then maybe it would be a scam. Not sure if I should do what he says in case it&#39;s a scam and he somehow takes right to that song, idk just thought I would post in case.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:28:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sorry Jill Schroeder, going to make an example of you.</p>
<p>See below for steps on what to do. Remember, we cannot help you outside of Auxy disco. If there are concerns or issues on other platforms you must reach out to support on said services.</p>
<p><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/0/0d175ea76ec82626079f3e6961003637d0178319.png" alt="sc1" width="676" height="345"></p>
<p><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/2/2b68e234ea77ccee75a2ff69f8a4b706c5e81c09.png" alt="sc2" width="535" height="338"></p>
<p><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/6/6d19d61eb3892745fb144466ab7c0896c4df0356.png" alt="sc3" width="534" height="272"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blakkaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m pretty sure it’s legit.</p>
<p>I sent them my credit card details and now my track is <span class="hashtag">#3</span> on the Nigerian disco charts…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[HELIXX]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Scam</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 10:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="10" data-topic="12134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/anirudhkhanna/40/10185_1.png" class="avatar"> AnirudhKhanna:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>He soon deleted his comment</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>More likely his SoundCloud was taken down because multiple people who had received his comments reported him</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[joshuatuworldwide]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>don’t trust it<br>
report them and go, that’s what I usually do</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/24</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 06:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just remember I was talking about a small Soundcloud user in scope. We’re probably gonna go in circles, haha. Nice chatting industry with you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 22:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>(post withdrawn by author, will be automatically deleted in 24 hours unless flagged)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 19:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="18" data-topic="12134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/sunny/40/2869_1.png" class="avatar"> Sunny:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Just, how legit would you consider someone advertising their <em>facebook</em> page, over a website.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Go where the audience is.<br>
Some brands have FB engagement that massively outnumbers their website visits.</p>
<p>It comes down to what the brand is trying to do, who they’re trying to talk to and where that audience mostly hangs out.</p>
<p>No point spending budget trying to drive traffic to your website if you can reach the audience you’re after via an existing channel.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>getting your song into popular playlists is a humungous part of exposure on streaming services like Spotify. I have heard of success stories.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The major labels spend big bucks on playlist placement to prime the pumps on their major and upcoming artists. There’s a good chance the top played tracks in most genres on Spotify have enjoyed the benefits of paid playlist placement.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>it’s honest to god so rare to be picked up without putting yourself out there.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You’re conflating ‘being discovered’ with artists who have done nothing to promote themselves and have no audience.</p>
<p>That’s the stuff of Hollywood dreams.<br>
That is and has always been fantastically rare.</p>
<p>‘Being discovered’ these days more likely relates to artists who have built a modest following - at which point, a label, playlist or maybe even an algo ‘discovers’ them, spots the potential, puts some promotion behind them and puts them in front of a much larger audience.</p>
<p>That’s how ‘being discovered’ works these days.</p>
<p>Even most labels won’t touch you unless you’ve already established a reasonably sized audience.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/19</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-19</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t worry, I know how marketing works. I’ve dedicated papers to researching it, especially through digital media. In the <em>confines of this post and the spam mentioned</em>, I just don’t think it’s worth anyone’s time. By legit I don’t just mean official businesses. Some blogs are better at promoting than marketing businesses. Just, how legit would you consider someone advertising their <em>facebook</em> page, over a website.</p>
<p>I’m pretty rusty on the music scene (film degree over here), but I’m aware that getting your song into popular playlists is a humungous part of exposure on streaming services like Spotify. I have heard of success stories.</p>
<p>I stand by that no-one is discovered these days. Give me articles that say otherwise for hope, but it’s honest to god so rare to be picked up without putting yourself out there. What really happens is that an artist becomes aware of marketing devices and approaches producers or in the independent scene that would be playlist curators, not the other way around. Maybe it happens for artists who are already popular, but it won’t be happening to small soundcloud users.</p>
<p>So even if the marketing <em>in this post</em> seems relatively harmless, you gotta ask what they intend to gain by spamming soundcloud users. Usually you can figure it out by their tactics — and most of those awful pages these days are after acquisition, and they can only raise their value through numbers.</p>
<p>A legit business is legit interested in promoting so they can get a cut of the sales.</p>
<p>My phone is super tiny and cutting stuff so sorry if my side of the discussion is a bit choppy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/18</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-18</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="13" data-topic="12134">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/sunny/40/2869_1.png" class="avatar"> Sunny:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>It’d be a scam if they expect an artist to pay to be featured — it’s non legit exposure.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I think you need to update your thinking.</p>
<p>Marketing is a thing and that includes playlist promotion, which involves paying money for inclusion on prominent and popular playlists.</p>
<p>It’s how a large part of the mainstream music industry works these days - generally the more successful part, I’d wager.</p>
<p>You can dismiss it as ‘non legit exposure’ as much as you like, but it doesn’t detract from the fact that it’s called ‘the music <em>business</em>’ for a reason.</p>
<p>The owners of prominent playlists have built up a reputation and an audience through curation.</p>
<p>It may feel a bit back to front, but that’s music promotion. It’s sometimes gonna cost you money to get access to the bigger audiences.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/17</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-17</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[iammane]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>And this selection of electronic music has been sponsored by The Horde - to hell with The Alliance!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/16</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-16</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blakkaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I checked out the Facebook page. Seems harmless.</p>
<p>Just some dude/dudette reposting tracks on Youtube and putting together a weekly ‘radio’ show on Facebook.<br>
Gets about ~600 plays on FB…</p>
<p>Also streams World of Warcraft between radio shows, so you know it’s legit… <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/15</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-15</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I can’t find the comment anymore, I think he deleted it. His account is still there though.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/14</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-14</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’d be tempted to look up the facebook and go down the rabbit hole properly in my favourite type of research — figuring out scummy people.</p>
<p>As first glance; a scam, or misleading or bad marketing. It’d be a scam if they expect an artist to pay to be featured — it’s non legit exposure. If they legitimately like the song and the collegue (ugh) wanted to help em out, then not a scam.</p>
<p>I’d define a scam by misleading someone into paying money, right?</p>
<p>The expectation in this would be that they would pay in some way, whether it be parting with money, information (email, your contacts), or by spreading the advertising content (sacrificing your integrity).</p>
<p>I’d have to research them if I really really wanted to out them, but sometimes all people are after is your attention and being on their site — so I actively avoid their content so they don’t benefit (from ad revenue) at all with their bad tactics. So for both that reason and the fact that my computer is dying forcing me to mobile, yeah naaaah.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/13</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-13</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[El1011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s just bot spamming people for someone else to get likes on their own posts.</p>
<p>It might not be a “traditional” scam where u do something and get no benefit out of it, they might actually repost u (or not). But if you do like their post you could potentially put yourself on a list for other scammers or people who will spam you with stuff.  That’s probably a more hypothetical, extreme scenario tho lol.</p>
<p>I think it’s probably just a bot account to promote someone else’s page to sell ppl garbage or something and chances are they won’t actually repost you after you like them. They’re just trying to see who’s gonna bite and promote their stuff.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/12</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-12</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Question: Maybe I’m missing something, but what’s the potential scam?</p>
<p>If you posted it on their FB page, it still appears under your name, so hard for them to then claim it’s their track. Especially as the artist name is still embedded in whatever player is being used.<br>
So, no clear scam opportunity in that way.</p>
<p>From what’s been said so far, seems the only real question is ‘do you want access to their FB audience’?</p>
<p>Are there any other 3rd-party tracks posted on the FB page and, if so, what are their play numbers like?<br>
i.e. what’s the potential/likely bump you’ll get from posting to that audience?<br>
Do you think that giving their page a Like is a price worth paying?</p>
<p>Side-notes There’s presumably nothing stopping the FB page owner from (re-)posting on their page without your involvement, using a SoundCloud embedded share. So, it possibly speaks to their upfrontness that they’re reaching out to you.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I kinda disagree with <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/sunny">@Sunny</a>’s comment. Getting your stuff in front of multiple audiences is part of being ‘in it to win it’. And, for tracks and artists lacking a dedicated marketing budget, that’s the first step to getting traction, ‘discovered, you might say.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Bottom line, I’m not seeing the ‘scam’ here. Seems like any other repost situation (base day on what you’ve told us).</p>
<p>I might be missing something, so anyone who believes/suspects its a scam, please help me understand the nature of the potential scam.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/11</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 06:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-11</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AnirudhKhanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I already did with my song where he posted this, as well. He soon deleted his comment</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/10</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-10</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[R-JRDN]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They are most likely just trying to get likes on their facebook page.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/9</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-9</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[crystldawnmusic]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Definitely a scam. You could try writing back to them (wouldn’t recommend) and if they don’t respond, you know for sure it is. If they do respond, it…still is probably a scam.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/8</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Katki]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Most likely a scam.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/7</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AnirudhKhanna]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It is. This same post was posted on my song. I just ignored it. You can have a look at the conversation <a href="https://soundcloud.com/user-148462857/austin-haga-float-house-mix">https://soundcloud.com/user-148462857/austin-haga-float-house-mix</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/6</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 11:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>you bet. it’s unlikely in general that you will be “discovered” in today’s competitive market. gotta be in it to win it, my friend.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/5</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 11:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>most likely</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/4</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Is this a scam?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[FLB100]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>ye probably.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-12134-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/is-this-a-scam/12134.rss">Is this a scam?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
