<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197</link>
    <description>&lt;big&gt; Featured Auxy Artist #10: @AzureOnyx &lt;/big&gt;

![36%20PM|690x143](upload://coPI5gggWHzPMDs0pP6XmiX7FRM.jpg)

&lt;big&gt;A&lt;/big&gt;zureOnyx_ enjoys trance and DnB. He wants to &quot;_Create music that’s like no other. Maybe expand and recreate rules for musical genres._&quot;   He&#39;s sometimes outspoken in the forum about the direction of Auxy, but we won&#39;t hold that against him because his music sounds pretty good!    

**Where did the unique name come from?** 
&gt; My name literally means Blue Black Underscore. Azure Onyxscore. Basically my favorite color combo. 
&gt; The Underscore came from my old username LemonSpy_.  
&gt; LemonSpy_ was getting too young for my age and I wanted to change it. 
&gt; Underscore became my username for a month then changed it to Azure Onyxscore_ &lt;/big&gt;
&gt; &lt;small&gt;GTNerd30 ... LemonSpy_ ... Underscore ... Azure Onyxscore ... which is shortened to ... &lt;/small&gt;   &lt;big&gt;AzureOnyx_ &lt;/big&gt;

**Week starting: 5 Mar, 2018.** 
- Please listen to at least one of their tracks (or more) 
- Provide at least one Soundcloud comment / feedback about their music during their week. 
- Comment in this thread once you&#39;ve provided any feedback. 
- If you want people to comment on your week, remember to comment for others! 

Check out  their tracks here:  http://www.soundcloud.com/azureonyx/tracks 

If you want to be in the weekly draw [add your name.](https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-who-wants-to-be-involved/5518)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 05:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Random</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Reaper2.0]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My favorite so far is “Melody’s DNB.”</p>
<p>I also liked “Ni”</p>
<p>Your style is quite interesting…</p>
<p>(In a good way, I mean.)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 01:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-45</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>As for Azure’s Challenge, the challenge is like classic BTC, make a song with the provided tracks available. This one forces you to use the tracks as is, therefore, you can’t modify the loops.</p>
<aside class="quote" data-post="1" data-topic="3352">
  <div class="title">
    <div class="quote-controls"></div>
    <img loading="lazy" alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/azureonyx/40/14456_2.png" class="avatar">
    <a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/azures-challenge-remix-this/3352">Azure's Challenge, Remix this</a> <a class="badge-wrapper  bullet" href="https://disco.auxy.co/c/contests/10"><span class="badge-category-bg" style="background-color: #12A89D;"></span><span style="" data-drop-close="true" class="badge-category clear-badge" title="Post your contests and challenges here.">Contest &amp; Challenges</span></a>
  </div>
  <blockquote>
    <a href="https://app.auxy.co/projects/ssk-CaFlA1rEKtxi0QaB9Q==" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://app.auxy.co/projects/ssk-CaFlA1rEKtxi0QaB9Q==</a> 
Rules are simple, 
Any instrument that has a [!] marker cannot be deleted nor edited. Modulation is fine, patterns cannot be edited 
You can change tempo and key to the song. 
You can change the overall genre. 
This is just a friendly challenge. Feel free to remix and post any finished projects here!
  </blockquote>
</aside>

          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-44</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DontPartyWithGuns]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thought I did this week’s but I guess not.</p>
<p>All in all your stuff is really good. It has a clear structure, has instruments/sounds that work well together, and (ive already said this but) they sound good.</p>
<p>I think the only advice I can give is to pan less when you use it and to turn your basses down a bit (they’re a bit overpowering).</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-43</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Pinewoodog]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>That’s 1,146 words</p>
<p>That’s like a 10 paragraph essay</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-42</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok! I’m not very good at figuring out sounds <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-41</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the feedback!</p>
<p>As a side note, I never used Freak in any of my tracks. I’ve used Slope instead.</p>
<p>You mentioned that I’ve used Gossip in Fuzmiral. Like everyone who uses Auxy, I never used Gossip. Instead, fancy combinations thanks to layering.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-40</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really dig the retro vibes in Ni, super good!<br>
(Congrats on 150 followers <small>*wink</small>)</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 21:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-39</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The countdown is on… 8hrs left.</p>
<p>Still time to leave some feedback!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-38</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=5" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=5" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/joy.png?v=5" title=":joy:" class="emoji" alt=":joy:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-37</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/akabillposters">@akabillposters</a> gold medal material right here</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-36</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DHO]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I really love all your music honestly.  Nice work</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew_Adams]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey man! Was just looking at your profile, and you make some sweet stuff <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=5" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"> My favorite was Ni. I like the energy and specifically that fast bassline loop. Our Blue Snowflakes is great, too. Nice and flowing and the piano is cool. Maybe you could work on the drums a tiny bit more.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>AoM is really nice. Not really the genre I would listen to, but if it was the genre I liked I would sefinitely listen to it. I love the melodies, and I also love the chords. Really cool.</p>
<p>The preview of ni is awesome. I love the melody. I really liked the build. That riser was really cool. I also love the delayed bonk bonks (is it coin?) in the drop. I love the mysterious piano after the drop. Really cool. You are amazing at writing drums! Overall, very cool song.</p>
<p>Okay, melody’s Drum and bass. The drums are amazing. And I LOVE the chords coming in. What instrument is it? My guess is a low passed silk? Anyway, love that sound and those chords. Okay, the melody is coming in. I love it! Really cool! These drums are really epic. Love them getting faster. The use of piano is also epic. And I love the shifter snares. That break is awesome, with the symbol. Overall, I LOVE THIS SONG! Awesome <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=5" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
<p>Cerulean V5 is really cool. The strong tonsil is unique. Can’t wait for the full song!</p>
<p>The revolt is definitely what I’d listen to. Very heavy. It comes in so strong! The chords are really cool. And these drums, wow! Blew my mind. I can’t believe I’d never ward your music before! You are amazing.</p>
<p>You got far into the auxy tournament! And I love your semifinal entry. The piano is really nice and that hour is heavenly for me lol.</p>
<p>You auxy tournament round 3 blew my mind. I don’t normally hear the future pack being used a lot. This was wonderful. I love it.</p>
<p>Our blue snowflakes is imo one of your best. Maybe it’s just because I wouldn’t really listen to some of your others because I’m not a massive fan of the genres but this is totally what I’d listen to. I love the chords, the use of tiny. The piano is AMAZING, and as always I love these drums. This song actually brings back memories of a specific day to me so it makes this song to me even more special. The fast piano at 2:44 is amazing. Love it. And I will always love the piano with tiny I’m pretty sure, or something like that. Amazing. Lol how many times have I used amazing probably like 20 lol. The quiet chords at the end I also love. 10/10. I LOVE IT.</p>
<p>Your second round of the auxy tournament is top notch. The drums are awesome. Really groovy. I could dance to this.</p>
<p>OMG I LOVE YOUR FIRST ROUND ENTRY. Amazing again. This is definitely something I’d listen to. The instruments go so well together. 10/10 again.</p>
<p>I won’t do the WIP of cerulean because I already did another of it.</p>
<p>Your BTC 21 entry is awesome. The piano is mysteriously awesome. I love the I think it’s twig? Anyway, that’s amazing. The sudden ending is so cool.</p>
<p>To vanish from anguish is amazing. The piano is really amazing. The bass is awesome. I also love these drums. Very intense. Again, this isn’t really my genre but I can tell people who like this genre would definitely like this. Really cool.</p>
<p>Serket VIP is really awesome. I mean, REALLY AWESOME (darn autocorrect doesn’t work when you spam caps lol) anyway, this is awesome. Parts sound like a Mario kart track theme song. I love the instruments. This is awesome. The piano chords are really cool.</p>
<p>Azure’s challenge is epic. That beginning is very unique. What was the challenge? Really epic. As usual, the drums are top par. The piano is AMAZING. Just what I like.</p>
<p>Sapphire is really cool. I know this is your older stuff, but the quality is still very high. The chords are beautiful. The bass is a bit heavy for just piano but maybe it’s supposed to be I don’t know I’m not really one to know a lot about genres. The use of the future pack is amazing. I don’t know how to use the future pack effectively so when I hear it I love it. Sounds so amazing. I actually bought the future pack first because I thought the demo song sounded the coolest. Well done me lol. Anyway, this song is awesome. The piano melodies are really cool. The go with the song. I love the fast tempo as well. Awesome!</p>
<p>Fuzmiral is awesome. The chords are awesome. I don’t really like gossip, so I can’t say that I love the use of it, but I hear you have used it well and it still sounds good for me. Some of these sounds are unique. I can’t tell how you layered some of them. I really like it.</p>
<p>Your BTC 14 is very cool. Like your other songs, some parts are very mysterious.</p>
<p>I don’t really know what auxy christofffo vs azure onyxscore really is but I like it! The use of the future pack is amazing again. There are so many sounds and things going on in this! I love it.</p>
<p>Your remix of the calling is amazing. It’s been awhile since I heard this song, and it will always be amazing. I love what you have done to it. The drums are top notch. The build is amazing. Love what you did. The drums in the build are especially amazing. Awesome. The drop is awesome. I love how you used freak in it, rather than just the second drop. Overall, great remix!</p>
<p>Retro wave is awesome. The drums are awesome, like the other 50 billion times I’ve said. The chords are also cool. Maybe I’d use sweeper or something for the transition from the loud part to the quiet part. I love the clicks or snaps or what you call them. I love the fast melody. Can’t tell what instrument it is. Very cool. I love when you start to layer it. Music to my ears. Literally.</p>
<p>Leijon VIP is not really a genre I’d listen to not because of the beautiful piano but because of the strong bass. The piano is awesome though. You really like your piano don’t you?! The drums are really cool. The use of percussion is awesome. The hour is really cool. Great song!</p>
<p>How many cerulean songs do you have? I’m just gonna skip this because I’ve already reviewed your other one <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:">.</p>
<p>A lot of your other tracks are tracks ie already reviewed as VIPs or different tracks so I’m gonna stop here. I would’ve done this in comments in Soundcloud but all I have to do it is my iPhone so sorry. My favourite was our blue snowflakes. I loved it.</p>
<p>Anyway, your Soundcloud is awesome. I loved listening to your songs. Great job! <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:"><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=5" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
<p>Edit: OOPS OMG I DID WAY TOO MUCH FEEDBACK SORRY I GOT CAREIED AWAY OMG LOL SORRY</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok. Will start listening to ur songs now I have the time <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=5" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I agree with the many cerulean. It’s also like his own little signature sound. I find it awesome. It’s also very recognisable to tell when something is created by azure. And I find it really cool. Like for example my signature used to be having a big sub drop in my intros or like a cool chopped chord. But I don’t do that as much now. Sometimes though. I just use impacts and stuff like that tho I still do it. Depends on the track</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/31</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 11:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-31</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheRealJFalc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Happy to listen to this stuff again, just as amazing when I first heard it. Hopefully one day I’ll have enough courage to try doing Trance and make something fantastic just like the stuff you write man.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/30</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-30</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My fav track of yours is <a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/preview">Ni (Preview)</a>.  It opens with that 1980’s Miami Vice style, with variations throughout the track. I was worried that you’d moved away from that style at one point, but was pleased when you returned to it. It’s marked as a “preview” but is already sounding great.</p>
<p>Second fav was <a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/cerulean-vip">Cerulean VIP</a>,   It’s just easy to listen to, despite having complexity to it.</p>
<p>I liked the D&amp;B style drums in <a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/the-revolt">Revolt</a> but I felt like I had to listen carefully to the lead as there’s a lot happening and it blends into the background sounds a bit, such as the pads. I’ve had this experience myself where the lead sounds more distinct on the device, but when it’s on Soundcloud some of the intricacies are less audible. Your more recent tracks have clearly audible leads so perhaps you’ve noticed this already.</p>
<p>Enjoyed the old school intro from <a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/to-vanish-from-anguish">To Vanish from Anguish</a>.</p>
<p>Your music’s interesting to check out. Thanks!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/29</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 02:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I get your point <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/ok_hand.png?v=5" title=":ok_hand:" class="emoji" alt=":ok_hand:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/28</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 02:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just to preview, really. I’d like to see other’s opinions on a track to see what I can improve.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/27</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 02:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right on point.<br>
Just out of curiosity; Why upload a track which is not 100% finished? Why not wait until it’s completely done? Forgive me for asking</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/26</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 02:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ni isn’t finished because there are still some things I need to add. For a track to be good, I need to make sure they don’t feel rushed. You see this with Auxians who constantly pump out a track every week; the track quality doesn’t feel “magical” or feel like they don’t put much love into it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/25</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 01:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/azureonyx">@AzureOnyx</a> I really like your stuff man! It’s uplifting and has energy, which is great. Therefore Ni and Melody’s Drum &amp; Bass are my favorites. How is Ni unfinished though? It’s over 5 minutes and it’s great lol <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:"><br>
When listening to The Revolt I noticed that the melody was slightly put to the background because of all the different fat sounds you used, so be careful with overlayering sometimes. The track has some trance and dnb influences, so I see why you chose to do this though! The two tracks mentioned above don’t have this, so they sound better imo. This is just my opinion though <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"><br>
Great stuff!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/24</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LittleSpikes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Congrats on being chosen for FMW<br>
I like your percussion, solid and powerful!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 13:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[anon73773654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wow, your tracks are quite nice! I really like the vibes in your latest WIP, AoM. I think even more bass would be great, could just be me though.</p>
<p>I also really like how you make VIPs of your tracks, like Cerulean. Each one is even awesome and awesome.</p>
<p>I’ll be sure to leave some comments/feedback here and like some more of your tracks tomorrow!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 06:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Your recent track that hasn’t been finsihed yet is also awesome</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197/21</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8197-21</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-10-azureonyx/8197.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 10: AzureOnyx_</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
