<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Joel García -&gt; IXACHI</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/joel-garcia-ixachi/21555</link>
    <description>Hello, I just wanted to announce here that I have rebranded from Joel García to IXACHI hehe. You can find me as IXACHI on Instagram, Twitter, YouTube and SoundCloud. The reason I rebranded is because I&#39;ve always wanted to make electronic (as in dubstep and electro-house) music, but as Joel García I made a bunch of actual pop songs with vocals, such as my track &quot;Us Two&quot;, I didn&#39;t think the electronic genre really fit the audience I was targeting to. So I decided to start all over again as IXACHI, which actually means &quot;great&quot; in Nahuatl, which is a native Mexican word (I&#39;m Mexican). I just wanted to let you know I&#39;m the same person hehe. Good day everyone!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 04:21:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/joel-garcia-ixachi/21555.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Joel García -&gt; IXACHI</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[joelgarcia]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello, I just wanted to announce here that I have rebranded from Joel García to IXACHI hehe. You can find me as IXACHI on Instagram, Twitter, YouTube and SoundCloud. The reason I rebranded is because I’ve always wanted to make electronic (as in dubstep and electro-house) music, but as Joel García I made a bunch of actual pop songs with vocals, such as my track “Us Two”, I didn’t think the electronic genre really fit the audience I was targeting to. So I decided to start all over again as IXACHI, which actually means “great” in Nahuatl, which is a native Mexican word (I’m Mexican). I just wanted to let you know I’m the same person hehe. Good day everyone!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/joel-garcia-ixachi/21555/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/joel-garcia-ixachi/21555/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 04:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-21555-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/joel-garcia-ixachi/21555.rss">Joel García -&gt; IXACHI</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
