<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241</link>
    <description>
![MoMo|120x120](upload://228bBTf0UlvawMrXraRAKmitN9z.png)![MoMo|120x120](upload://228bBTf0UlvawMrXraRAKmitN9z.png)![MoMo|120x120](upload://228bBTf0UlvawMrXraRAKmitN9z.png)  
&lt;big&gt; Featured Auxy Artist #16: @Hum4n01d  &lt;/big&gt;   

&lt;big&gt;H&lt;/big&gt;um4n01d enjoys coding and making music with Auxy, Logic Pro X &amp; GarageBand. He also appears to like strips of well-manicured hair located above the upper lip.   His favourite artists include TheFatRat, Martin Garrix &amp; Marshmello.  But he&#39;s not a fan of autotune featuring so prominently in modern music. Hum4n01d recently hosted a [remix contest](https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-way-hum4n01d-x-t-c-remix-competition/7972) for his  [The Way](https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/the-way) collab with Toxic Caves.  And he&#39;s currently participating in the [Third Auxy Tournament](https://disco.auxy.co/t/contest-third-auxy-tournament/9097). Listen to his music [here](https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/tracks ).

**Week starting: 16 Apr, 2018.** 
- Please listen to at least one of their tracks (or more) 
- Provide at least one Soundcloud comment / feedback about their music during their week. 
- Comment in this thread once you&#39;ve provided any feedback. 
- If you want to be featured, remember to comment for others! 

 **:soundcloud: Soundcloud:**  https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/tracks 

 **:spotify: Spotify:**  https://open.spotify.com/user/hum4n01dmusic

If you want to be in the weekly draw [add your name.](https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-who-wants-to-be-involved/5518)</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 04:37:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Random</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This topic was automatically closed after 18 hours. New replies are no longer allowed.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/45">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/45</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-45</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just listed to all of your tracks and noticed your music has a clear 1980’s influence.  Specifically, the nice arps in <strong>Pluck</strong> and <strong>Blur</strong>,  the bass-line in <strong>Prose</strong> and the synthwave-like stuff in <strong>Pluck</strong>. Love that 1980’s sound.  Plus, <strong>Electro beat</strong> could easily be a platform game theme, which is another pre-2000’s reference.</p>
<p><strong>Paralayers</strong> seems to have the most complex layering.  The first section was awesome, really grabbed me.</p>
<p>The haunting lead on <strong>The Way</strong> is sweet, but not sure who did which parts in the collab, so won’t comment on that track too much.</p>
<p><strong>Constructive feedback:</strong><br>
Your SoundCloud track list only includes two of your own tracks in 8 mths. So write more music! And if it’s more 1980’s inspired material, that’s fine with me!  <img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/6/613549d576e80a79fb87e3098a9aaeaf4c125b53.png?v=5" title=":_happybunny:" class="emoji emoji-custom" alt=":_happybunny:"> </p>
<p>Hope you’ve enjoyed being FMOTW.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/44">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/44</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 04:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-44</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sunny]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Last minuting my way in. Had a listen to your stuff <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/hum4n01d">@Hum4n01d</a></p>
<p>Great stuff, but I especially liked the remixes of your song! Great comp and I liked my favourite.</p>
<p>While you’ve moved on into wub wub styles, I think <strong>Paralayers</strong> is my fave. It’s a very cute song, and very danceable while doing chores. I like the almost electric guitar sound that comes in. You should use it again in conjunction with your new style! You could make something really metal!</p>
<p>Keep up the good work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/43">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/43</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 03:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-43</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ah yes that makes sense <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1/3.png?v=5" title=":+1:t3:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:t3:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/42">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/42</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 02:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-42</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>No problem <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/41">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/41</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-41</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>If we keep the thread open, it may distract from the next FMOTW.</p>
<p>Sooo… if you want, you can PM me any feedback for Hum4no1d &amp; I’ll add it here for you.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/40">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/40</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-40</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Stigmo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/hum4n01d">@Hum4n01d</a> unfortunately I will not be able to give you feedback before tomorrow. I will give you feedback somewhere next week through a DM. Or <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/mistermaster">@MisterMaster</a> could perhaps extend this thread until next week <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grimacing.png?v=5" title=":grimacing:" class="emoji" alt=":grimacing:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/39">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/39</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-39</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[anon73773654]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Time for me to leave some feedback <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/hum4n01d">@Hum4n01d</a> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"></p>
<p><em>Prose:</em> I know this is from a year ago so I won’t leave too much feedback. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye.png?v=6" title=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue_winking_eye:"> Groovy bassline, lead melody is pretty cool. P good for a first song in Auxy <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/smile.png?v=6" title=":smile:" class="emoji" alt=":smile:"></p>
<p><em>Blur:</em> Nice Craft beat. The 8-bit arp thing is on point, I love the feel of this. Would like an extended VIP of this. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p><em>Grand:</em> I love this bassline, it reminds me of the sort of bass in synthwave music. Those breaks are amazing, and it’s pure fire for no APs. Actually, it’s just pure fire, that buildup is amazing. Love your fun &amp; distinct style!</p>
<p><em>The Way (ft. TC)</em>: I absolutely love this. The chord progression is amazing, and the different drum kits fit together perfectly, and that arp sound effect adds a great effect. Again, this buildup is amazing. The melody (Stress, right?) is awesome. The pitch bend rise is super cool. 1:35 to 1:59 is my favorite, bc those drums <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/heart.png?v=6" title=":heart:" class="emoji" alt=":heart:"></p>
<p><em>Pluck:</em> I love the arp! I’m noticing that you use arpeggios a lot in your songs and they always fit perfectly, as well as groovy basslines. This is a pretty solid song. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
<p>Congrats on Forum Member of the Week, keep up the awesome work!! <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/smiley.png?v=6" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
<p><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/6/6b8abe3ae2119aad46672580a8b045bf188014b1.png" alt="imageedit_1_9376980494" width="200" height="200"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/38">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/38</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-38</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for all the feedback! I’ll make sure to check out your stuff today <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/smiley.png?v=5" title=":smiley:" class="emoji" alt=":smiley:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/37">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/37</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 22:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-37</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sure! I’ll don’t have the file though</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/36">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/36</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 21:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-36</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ok.</p>
<p>Pluck is very groovy at the start. The drums you used remind me of the eighties or nineties. But that changes when the drop hits! It goes to a modern dance song (or whatever genre it is in terrible with that.) The Chords are great and a LOVE the drums! Especially those fills <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"> At 1:24 to 1:26 the hihats have just panned up and then they go down again which sounds a bit odd but it’s not a big issue and the rest of the song is fantastic! And it’s back being groovy <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"> When the relaxing chords came in, I loved them SO MUCH! And those drums are really cool as well! I love this! And that high melody you added… great. I like the wubs you added <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/laughing.png?v=5" title=":laughing:" class="emoji" alt=":laughing:"> I really like that riser (I like a lot about this!) AND THE DROP IS AMAZING I ACTUALLY WANTED TO GET UP AND DANCE!! The pan out made me sad because the song was over. That was SUCH A GREAT SONG!! 12/10.</p>
<p>The way has some nice opening chords. The drums are on point like usual and I like the use of freak even though I normally wouldn’t. The little piano rolls are beautiful. The second melody is really nice, I really like the pitch with it. The stress (I think it’s stress) melody is nice, and I love the build. Especially the drums <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=5" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> the drop is really cool. I love the background kinda dubstep sound. And the little piano rolls again are just amazing. And those drums!!! The kinda second build is interesting because it is straight after the drop which keeps the structure great. And THOSE FILLLLLS! :o I really love good drums! And your songs have lots of what I like. The pan out again made me sad because the song was over. I liked the use off piano chords this time at the end. And the pan out with just the stress and the drums. And the end Fill is awesome!! AMAZING!</p>
<p>Grand sounds very grand. I LOVE the chords! My favourite so far. And also the sounds from the very beginning of the song. The drums are nice, and I love how the chords get toned. The drop is nice, especially THOSE FILLSS! The gossip (I think <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/thinking.png?v=5" title=":thinking:" class="emoji" alt=":thinking:">) melody is great. And the use of mist goes well with the grandness. And that trap beat is also nice. The drums after the drop has panned our are my favourite simple ones. Love the snare especially. And of course all the different elements, the background thingy, the chords and the mist melody. And when all pans out for the chords is just beautiful. AMAZING!</p>
<p>Remorse, your collab with MR SERPENT is just awesome. The chords are really cool and the freak (I think) is also awesome. The drums are cool, I like the hihats especially. Woah what just happened!? THAT WAS EPIC!! Wait I’m playing up back. So it all went quiet then sweeper and hihats panned up and the chords and everything kept on playing but with breaks with AMAZING FILLS! Wow! Loved it. I just love how many melodies you make, it adds so much variation and such interesting structure to the song. The pan out is cool because it pans up then out. And the bass note just at the end is awesome <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/clap.png?v=5" title=":clap:" class="emoji" alt=":clap:"></p>
<p>Blur. The drums ARE EPIC at the beginning. They sound like they were… toned? Or something like that. Anyway, with filters. The chords are awesome and the melody matches them perfectly. The use of corn (not sure) reminds me of when I first got auxy. Just a question, do you have premium? Because I’ve been hearing A LOT of the original sounds in your songs. And oh that was a quick song. I’ll replay it to make sure I didn’t miss anything. The opening melody I missed but I really really like! The drums are really cool and go with the style of chords. Great song, even if it was short. Very interesting.</p>
<p>Prose is nice! The bass at the start is very groovy. The kick clap pattern is also groovy. The don’t know what instrument it is melody is very nice. And in the build I love how the first bar of the chords and the melody repeat. Te buildup is simple but great. Loved that short song.</p>
<p>Paralayers is awesome. I love the fills at the beginning. Wow! How did you get that kinda bass electric guitar sound!? The the hihats are also epic. This one is so groovy! The chords are awesome, as is the melody. The background noises like basses are just so awesome how do you make them?! The drums when everything apart from the bass pans out are awesome. I love the hihats again. The low sound added on is nice. And I think I can hear some bee? Anyway, I like it! The ending is very nice. Those drums in the pan Out are really unique! Loved that.</p>
<p>Your collab with toxic caves, synter is cool. I can definitely tell is you! You have such an awesome style. Wow! This song moves fast. The start reminds me of a song which I’ve forgotten the name of. I like it, so I like your song xD. There are so many elements! Again multiple melodies. I love the structure in this one especially. And the drums <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:">. The background bassey noises I’ve found that you like a lot. To use I mean. But you probably like them as well if you use them so much. The drums are nice. There are so many elements to this song!!! The crash at the end is nice.</p>
<p>I’m sorry I left this till Sunday. I’ve had a lot on this week. I hope the feedback I have is okay. My favourite was probably pluck though I like all of your songs. Your style is very distinct. You have great music, well done!</p>
<p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/grin.png?v=5" title=":grin:" class="emoji" alt=":grin:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/35</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 19:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Eswyn]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/hum4n01d">@Hum4n01d</a> I really like your stuff! I particularly like The Way, I think it was well composed. Although simple, one of your tracks I really like is Prose. It has a pretty cool baseline, and a nice little lead. Do you mind if I remixed it?</p>
<p>I happen to really like a lot of your old Auxy stuff. Although very simple and often short, they have some pretty cool musical ideas going on.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/34</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 18:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thrashie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Congrats, man! ^-^</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/33</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[MisterMaster]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>There’s still time to check out Hum4no1d’s music!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/32</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 11:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>LOL Nice image. Thank you!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/31</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-31</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[T3CH]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Awesome Job!!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/30</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-30</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[LittleSpikes]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p></p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/a/a7749e37b7a86bd6586455314f1b63271c89e176.jpeg" title="E6B24557-624B-423D-AED9-CF967BDEF29F.jpeg" rel="nofollow noopener"><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/a/a7749e37b7a86bd6586455314f1b63271c89e176.jpeg" alt="image" width="500" height="500" data-small-upload="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/optimized/2X/a/a7749e37b7a86bd6586455314f1b63271c89e176_2_10x10.png"></a></div><br>
Love your logo. Obviously.<p></p>
<p>It’s a shame that I hadn’t listened to your works…<br>
Overall, your music sounds like BGM for cool games!! Well constructed.<br>
My favorites are Remose, Prose, Paralayers(love the epic feeling of the song).<br>
There are some songs that I just skip, but I think that’s just a matter of my taste.<br>
(If I manage to have more time to listen, I will consider the reason why I skip those track)</p>
<p>Keep up!!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/29</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 12:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Crap I had so many typos. It should make more sense now^</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/28</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 07:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I made this one before I had any sound packs, though punch existed</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/27</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The way was pretty good too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/26</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Pluck. Nice introduction with the arp like feel. Transition after the drums was bit different, I’d suggest having it longer and more suspending. Starting off less can sometimes be more and graduate it up. I’d also suggest the intro being longer but that’s just my opinion. Drop was pretty cool. I perinslaly would prefer the drums to be louder. The pad in the break could of been better by using a different sound. Variation in bas slime could of been better aswell and also adding a subass</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/25</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>They’re on my profile lol</p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/pluck" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/pluck</a></p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/the-way" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://soundcloud.com/hum4n01dmusic/the-way</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/24</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Could u please link me ur new songs?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/23</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks! Any song before Prose was made with GarageBand loops and is really only still up for anybody who wants to see how I got started. I’d recommend listening to a couple of my new tracks instead <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/22</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DJ_La_Rocca]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Grand. Reasonably good introduction. I’d suggest mixing your frequencies more by adding subbasses and possibly a better choice of rhythm in the drop. Nice arps in the second half of the drop.</p>
<p>Blur. Nice intro, kind slike glitchop. Nice melody. And nice entrance of the chords. Transitions were much nicer in this track. Considering the style of this track I don’t recommend anything but I would of added some bass.</p>
<p>Prose: nice bass line, perhaps the bass line being louder? If you are going to have the frequency low I suggest stacking the layers with something else. Nice drum and claps in the intro too. Didn’t like the 2 bar drum transition into the verse, could of just had the verse right after. Doodle was hardly able to hear.</p>
<p>Cherry, quite a different intro, that bass is actually quite awesome. Like the drums that came in the melody that came in aswell. Perhaps having some white noise? Nice verse with the whistles and the synth chords were great.</p>
<p>Gone had a cool techno feel. But the drops was very bassy and didn’t really work.</p>
<p>Overall I think u should make ur tracks longer and having some more variation.</p>
<p>That’s all I will give for now! Keep up the good work! <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/hum4n01d">@Hum4n01d</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241/21</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 06:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9241-21</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/forum-member-of-the-week-16-hum4n01d/9241.rss">Forum Member of the Week - 16: Hum4n01d</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
