<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Continuum - Tropical Madman [New Album Coming]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-continuum-tropical-madman-new-album-coming/6827</link>
    <description>Hello everyone. So from the past year I&#39;ve been getting so much better at making music! I&#39;ve took small lessons and listened to a few others tracks. This taught me so much i need to know. And i said to myself &quot;I should make another album&quot;. 

This new album will be called _The Continuum_. This album will contain at least 10 to 15 songs. I might add more. The genre will be mixed with different types of style. :sunglasses:

Also i&#39;m making a YouTube channel for my SoundCloud. This will mostly be like video on how i make music and songs for both YouTube and SoundCloud.

Well now that you know everything ill be seeing you next month! Got to go make dem songs brudda.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 11:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Work in Progress</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-continuum-tropical-madman-new-album-coming/6827.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The Continuum - Tropical Madman [New Album Coming]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Tropical_Madman]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hello everyone. So from the past year I’ve been getting so much better at making music! I’ve took small lessons and listened to a few others tracks. This taught me so much i need to know. And i said to myself “I should make another album”.</p>
<p>This new album will be called <em>The Continuum</em>. This album will contain at least 10 to 15 songs. I might add more. The genre will be mixed with different types of style. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/sunglasses.png?v=5" title=":sunglasses:" class="emoji" alt=":sunglasses:"></p>
<p>Also i’m making a YouTube channel for my SoundCloud. This will mostly be like video on how i make music and songs for both YouTube and SoundCloud.</p>
<p>Well now that you know everything ill be seeing you next month! Got to go make dem songs brudda.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-continuum-tropical-madman-new-album-coming/6827/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-continuum-tropical-madman-new-album-coming/6827/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 21:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-6827-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-continuum-tropical-madman-new-album-coming/6827.rss">The Continuum - Tropical Madman [New Album Coming]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
