<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Need help with mixing</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525</link>
    <description>Hey guys it’s tornait here

Been having a bit of a rough spell in terms of my creations. Feels like everything I’ve been putting out isn’t good enough, or sounds the same. And it seems that I’m so far behind in terms of, well... everything.

Anyways with that out of the way, I want to know more about how to make a good mix using Auxy and external software. Personally I have Logic Pro on my Mac and Klevgrand Grand Finale on my iPad... yet it seems so hard for me to mix something to satisfaction.

Can anyone give me some tips?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:30:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Db909]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>All great suggestions here.  I would also suggest playing around with mixing at a low volume, as low as you can go, so that you can really pick out the transients/loudest parts.  With these sitting together right, things will sound great turned back up.  You may have to occasionally turn it up and down to get a handle on the bass.  Also you can play around with setting the device to mono audio in the accessibility settings,  think of this as just another way of limiting your point of view to really focus in on how things are sitting together.  Mixing is how you craft the perception of the audio, so it can pay to play with your own perception like this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/12</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-12</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[TheRealJFalc]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>EQ is going to help a lot.</p>
<p>I’ve struggled with that same feeling of “being behind” for months now. It’s hard to get past it, but I’ve found making music that makes <em>me</em> happy as opposed to <em>others</em> has significantly helped me get back into actually writing music again. If you can get into the right mindset, other things will flow naturally.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 19:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-11</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[bedlegs]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve got studio monitors now but don’t have a cable to plug my phone into the interface. So I actually haven’t released any music using them. I just stick to my phone and earbuds. I use the Apple wired earbuds, beats solo 2 I think, or a single Bluetooth speaker. For the mixing you just have to keep experimenting. Don’t compare your music to other works constantly. If you have a track you’re stuck on, try creating a separate section. Don’t be afraid to make it quite different. It’s okay for music to be unexpected. Don’t worry about how it sounds compared to the scenes before it, just start something else. Once you think you have a good thing going, try and work it into your song. I’ve had parts that I rearranged completely, thinking that it would be the end of the song, to putting it in the middle and creating a whole new ending. Look back at other tracks your stuck on. What parts do you like about them, what don’t you like. Can you copy the patterns and see if you can incorporate it into another song you have, or maybe even a new song with the old pattern. I know you can do it, and you know you can too. It’s alright if you need a break. Find inspiration in other things beside music if it helps keep your mind off of it for a little bit. Sometimes it can take a lot of time but you’ll get there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 18:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-10</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Right now I have a pair of Sony WH-H900N headphones.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-9</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blakkaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="7" data-topic="15525">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/tornait/40/12724_2.png" class="avatar"> tornait:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>My current workflow… Well, it’s pretty much non-existent at this point. I work on a case-by-case basis.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>From my experience, developing a good routine is important.<br>
Something that is reproducible, quickly and easily, to get you <em>most</em> of the way.</p>
<p>I’d be interested to know what monitors/headphones you’re using for mixing?</p>
<p>While you don’t need super high-end gear to make a good mix, an investment in some decent equipment will make things much easier.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 13:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My current workflow… Well, it’s pretty much non-existent at this point. I work on a case-by-case basis. I’m split between multiple big  projects right now, really. When I do finish a track I find the final mix to be unsatisfactory, compared to the relatively good mixes I hear from others on SoundCloud. I think this is a good old-fashioned artist’s block…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 13:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[blakkaz]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="15525">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/tornait/40/12724_2.png" class="avatar"> tornait:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>Can anyone give me some tips?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Can you elaborate on where you feel your mixes are falling down?<br>
Perhaps an insight into your current workflow?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 07:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[JacobJustus]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Inspiration is everything! If you aren’t inspired to make something you won’t get anything it’s just as simple as that. Inspire your self to make a story behind every mix don’t just make mixes to make them, you want to have a story for every mix you make, a declaration to all!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/5">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/5</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 06:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-5</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks, guys. I’ll take these into consideration.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/4</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 06:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[El1011]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>EQ is going to be your best friend when it comes to mixing.  High/lowpass, boosting areas you want heard and lowering harsh frequencies or areas you dont want to hear.</p>
<p>As for a way to keep your tracks at a more manageable volume, lower the volume of all new tracks you make so that the instrument sits at around -12db and so that the master sits below 0db.  Then you can adjust the individual volumes to get the track sounding how you want, and at the end, put a limiter on the master to help bring the track’s volume back up for export.  at least that’s what i try to do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 20:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[foryou]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>honestly just experiment with different stuff until you like the way it sounds. there’s no one set way of mixing, it’s all up to personal preference. i tend to use a lot of low pass and high pass filters on my sounds to make sure there’s no clashing between frequencies. try that out and make sure you modify the volume on every instrument, don’t ever have anything turned all the way up.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 20:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Need help with mixing</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys it’s tornait here</p>
<p>Been having a bit of a rough spell in terms of my creations. Feels like everything I’ve been putting out isn’t good enough, or sounds the same. And it seems that I’m so far behind in terms of, well… everything.</p>
<p>Anyways with that out of the way, I want to know more about how to make a good mix using Auxy and external software. Personally I have Logic Pro on my Mac and Klevgrand Grand Finale on my iPad… yet it seems so hard for me to mix something to satisfaction.</p>
<p>Can anyone give me some tips?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 20:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15525-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/need-help-with-mixing/15525.rss">Need help with mixing</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
