<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>SKYCRASHERS - VideoGC [First full album]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876</link>
    <description>I did a _bit_ of post-production in Audacity. Mostly just lowering volume.)

Howdy y&#39;all! This is my first post here, and I thought I should start off with a bang. Over the past year I&#39;ve created an electronic album. I&#39;m not a musical master, so it&#39;s probably not the best thing to soothe your ears, but I&#39;m really proud of what I&#39;ve created. You can listen and download for free on [SoundCloud](http://soundcloud.com/videogc/sets/skycrashers), or buy me a pizza on [Bandcamp](http://videogc.bandcamp.com/releases). While creating the album, I had a loose story in my mind about a young boy who was transported to an alternate world for seemingly no reason. Even so, he tries his best to survive and prosper. In his journey he meets many strangers but overall must forge his own path alone.

Anyway, enjoy!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 14:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>SKYCRASHERS - VideoGC [First full album]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NIAZU]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I Like the feel of the album, I think the little story is pretty neat too.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876/2</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8876-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876.rss">SKYCRASHERS - VideoGC [First full album]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>SKYCRASHERS - VideoGC [First full album]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[VideoGC]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I did a <em>bit</em> of post-production in Audacity. Mostly just lowering volume.)</p>
<p>Howdy y’all! This is my first post here, and I thought I should start off with a bang. Over the past year I’ve created an electronic album. I’m not a musical master, so it’s probably not the best thing to soothe your ears, but I’m really proud of what I’ve created. You can listen and download for free on <a href="http://soundcloud.com/videogc/sets/skycrashers" rel="nofollow noopener">SoundCloud</a>, or buy me a pizza on <a href="http://videogc.bandcamp.com/releases" rel="nofollow noopener">Bandcamp</a>. While creating the album, I had a loose story in my mind about a young boy who was transported to an alternate world for seemingly no reason. Even so, he tries his best to survive and prosper. In his journey he meets many strangers but overall must forge his own path alone.</p>
<p>Anyway, enjoy!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 02:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-8876-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/skycrashers-videogc-first-full-album/8876.rss">SKYCRASHERS - VideoGC [First full album]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
