<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397</link>
    <description>Hey guys! I made my 1st music video the other day with beats I made in Auxy only! I love the app. Not so sure how good the song is as I recorded it on the iPad with the EarPods mic in GarageBand. I just wanted to share something with you guys to maybe inspire each other. This app is so powerful and I&#39;m sure in the right hands could make dreams come true. I&#39;ve had the app for about 2 months and prior I&#39;ve tried to produce, but was never able to make anything without using all loop packs. I really wanna get good at this, because I want to be a quality entertainer who could work on projects from start to finish. This app makes that possible! Any constructive feedback is welcome. Plus if you&#39;d like to do collabs let me know and I could write songs or raps over your tracks.

DISCLAIMER: I DO NOT CONDONE SMOKING OR DRINKING FOR THOSE OF YOU UNDER 21 WHO MAY VIEW THIS, the song is about prior struggles with that- I wouldn&#39;t advise it + the smoke I used was not real it was e-cig vapor... just thought I&#39;d add that

https://youtu.be/NjolZiKzKaw</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 22:21:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Work in Progress</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brandnaqua]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thank-you. Any critiques music-wise? <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=5" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 22:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-1397-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397.rss">My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[KVLE]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I Like It!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/2</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-1397-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397.rss">My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[brandnaqua]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey guys! I made my 1st music video the other day with beats I made in Auxy only! I love the app. Not so sure how good the song is as I recorded it on the iPad with the EarPods mic in GarageBand. I just wanted to share something with you guys to maybe inspire each other. This app is so powerful and I’m sure in the right hands could make dreams come true. I’ve had the app for about 2 months and prior I’ve tried to produce, but was never able to make anything without using all loop packs. I really wanna get good at this, because I want to be a quality entertainer who could work on projects from start to finish. This app makes that possible! Any constructive feedback is welcome. Plus if you’d like to do collabs let me know and I could write songs or raps over your tracks.</p>
<p>DISCLAIMER: I DO NOT CONDONE SMOKING OR DRINKING FOR THOSE OF YOU UNDER 21 WHO MAY VIEW THIS, the song is about prior struggles with that- I wouldn’t advise it + the smoke I used was not real it was e-cig vapor… just thought I’d add that</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NjolZiKzKaw?autoplay=1&amp;feature=oembed&amp;wmode=opaque">https://www.youtube.com/embed/NjolZiKzKaw</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-1397-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/my-first-music-video-w-music-produced-using-auxy/1397.rss">My First Music Video w Music Produced Using Auxy!</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
