<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>With It - WAVZ [Hip Hop]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/with-it-wavz-hip-hop/15059</link>
    <description>Auxy finally hit me with that repost after a couple months of liking my tracks from time to time, and following me! 🙏🏻 This stands out to me because I think it’s good step in the direction of getting some of the hip hop producers out there into the spotlight of the Auxy community. I was here when Auxy JUST started and since then there’s a small amount of HipHop producers i have come into contact with in this forum but hopefully we can keep producing amazing content for everyone to enjoy! A small victory, but it does motivate me to know people still listen to my projects even if it’s been a slow month! 

https://soundcloud.com/prod-by-wavz/with-it-prod-wavz

The song^</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:47:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/with-it-wavz-hip-hop/15059.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>With It - WAVZ [Hip Hop]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[WAVZ]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Auxy finally hit me with that repost after a couple months of liking my tracks from time to time, and following me! <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/pray/2.png?v=9" title=":pray:t2:" class="emoji" alt=":pray:t2:"> This stands out to me because I think it’s good step in the direction of getting some of the hip hop producers out there into the spotlight of the Auxy community. I was here when Auxy JUST started and since then there’s a small amount of HipHop producers i have come into contact with in this forum but hopefully we can keep producing amazing content for everyone to enjoy! A small victory, but it does motivate me to know people still listen to my projects even if it’s been a slow month!</p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/prod-by-wavz/with-it-prod-wavz" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/prod-by-wavz/with-it-prod-wavz</a></p>
<p>The song^</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/with-it-wavz-hip-hop/15059/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/with-it-wavz-hip-hop/15059/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 19:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-15059-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/with-it-wavz-hip-hop/15059.rss">With It - WAVZ [Hip Hop]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
