<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859</link>
    <description>It would be really cool if there was a ranking system kind of like reddit and then each month the top voted song would be featured/reposted? It would also serve as a good promotion system as people would listen to the most up-voted tracks!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 17:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>this doesn’t account for people who liked it so much that they keep listening to it</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/35">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/35</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-35</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[INDIR3CT]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Instead of every artist worrying about trying to get their track featured, how about a page be opened that allows every artists to submit ONE of their best tracks (project link) Allowing others to remix it. It would save time, and allow others to pick what they want to remix, whether a well known artist’s song, or some new and upcoming artists. This could allow others to remix the track and let the devs see a whole horizon full of tracks and projects, I don’t know if this would work, but hey…its just an idea <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/34">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/34</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-34</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="32" data-topic="4859">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
 kiP:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>there is a fair share of people who don’t like future bass, or any other genre frequently reposted by Auxy. Now of course that’s not too many people, but it’s a decent amount.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>The problem there is that, while FB* fans may not actually be a majority, non-FB fans are split amongst a range of genres. (It’s the basic issue with ‘<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/First-past-the-post_voting" rel="nofollow noopener">first past the post</a>’ voting schemes. The majority of the all votes given may not go to the single most popular option, but it’s the one with more votes than any other option that wins.)</p>
<p>(* or whatever the most popular genre is at any point)</p>
<p>e.g. …</p>
<p><img src="https://global.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/uploads/auxy/original/2X/c/c995ec278dc623021dfee92c2c013b0397e59988.png" alt="image" width="312" height="153"></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Another thing is that people, like me, will vote for songs which you might not like the genre, but you can tell is very well made. I don’t listen to trance, but if I hear a very well made trance track, I’d likely vote it up.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I like to think I’d be even-handed too (but then, we all like to think the best of ourselves.) <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=6" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I might be inclined to credit tracks that attempt something more unusual, even if it the execution wasn’t great.</p>
<p>But what if, even if well-made, an aficionado of that genre might recognise it as a really unoriginal song idea (or some other thing that makes it a weak example of the genre)?</p>
<p>That’s why I’m inclined to favour approaches that allow genre fans to vote with their own preferences, and then <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Normalization_(statistics)" rel="nofollow noopener">normalise</a> results to make comparing relative in-group appreciate more possible.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I think the only way to tell, is to put it into play. Which is unlikely.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The more complex we make the process of setting up the table, the less likely the process is to succeed.<br>
That’s why I started messing about with a tool that could be used to quickly and dispassionately calculate a value based on a track’s existing SC performance.</p>
<p>The challenge then shifts to deciding which tracks are to be compared each time.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
I’m not trying to be objectionable, just kicking the tyres on the thinking.<br>
(Please feel free to do likewise to mine. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/slight_smile.png?v=6" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/33">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/33</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 12:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-33</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>From what I’ve seen in this community, there is a fair share of people who don’t like future bass, or any other genre frequently reposted by Auxy. Now of course that’s not too many people, but it’s a decent amount. Another thing is that people, like me, will vote for songs which you might not like the genre, but you can tell is very well made. I don’t listen to trance, but if I hear a very well made trance track, I’d likely vote it up.</p>
<p>By the way, people should be allowed multiple votes.</p>
<p>Honestly, this is just a theory. But, your’s is just a theory as well. I think the only way to tell, is to put it into play. Which is unlikely.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/32</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 12:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Still, how does it address the potential problem of comparing music in a popular style against music in a less popular style? How will less popular styles be able to compete?</p>
<p>What you’re suggesting still boils down to a simple popularity contest, with genres with larger fanbases always likely to win out.</p>
<p>It could work if you’re comparing tracks within a single genre, but if it’s simply about popularity, rather than some other form of comparative merit, then just look at the SC play counts and declare your winner.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/31">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/31</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-31</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Polar]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Or not even numbers, everything was completely anonymous, and the songs were in completely random order. You wouldn’t even know how many votes a song’s had unless you’re a developer or a moderator. This could also prevent people from making alt accounts to upvote, because they wouldn’t know which one is their’s. <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/newnames">@newnames</a></p>
<p>I like this idea, but it would mean that the devs would have to work on another app/website, which takes time out of Auxy updates and APs.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/30">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/30</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-30</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="28" data-topic="4859">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/alyen/40/1438_1.png" class="avatar"> Alyen:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>SCore</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/+1.png?v=5" title=":+1:" class="emoji" alt=":+1:"> <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
<p>I think you’re right to suggest some kind of threshold of plays before consideration.<br>
Otherwise, any track, no matter how deserving, could achieve a 100% rating, by having the only person who listened to it, like it.</p>
<p>There’s also the issue of Likes starting to taper off (proportionally) as tracks achieve a certain level of popularity (plays) — i.e. the larger an audience gets, the % of listeners who will actually bother to Like a track starts to slow down. I suspect that can distort results against tracks with ‘high’ play counts.</p>
<p>Your example shows that. Similarly, Solar by Fantom87, with over 1K plays, would only SCore 7.<br>
Reminiscing by eddxe has over 9K plays, but would have a SCore of around 2.</p>
<p>So, it would need to factor in something to account for that, so that highly played tracks stand a chance.</p>
<p>One thing that might address that was if… anything over a certain play count gets reposted. So, this SCore thing only applies to tracks below a certain play count.<br>
(It’s likely that if a track has [e.g.] over 500 plays [regardless of Likes], it’s popular enough to deserve an automatic Auxy repost.)</p>
<p>Similarly, you’re correct in that Reposts are very valuable, a major endorsement of a track and should be factored in. They could potentially serve as a ‘multiplier’, worth more than a Like.</p>
<p>You’d also want to factor in play count somehow, so that higher play counts are still objectively valuable, not just in relation to Likes.</p>
<p>This is just some loose thinking. Spit-balling.</p>
<p>It shows it’s actually a complex thing to achieve a good algorithm. Companies like SC will spend proper time and budget deciding on the most effective factors and how much weight each adds to the score. (It’s actually an interesting subject/challenge if you’re at all geeky about code, data or math.)</p>
<p>I wasn’t attempting to offer that simple like:play ratio as the definitive solution, just start a conversation about how it might be tackled — as an alternative to a direct popular vote (which would almost always skew in favour of the existing popular makers/genres).</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/29</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 10:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="26" data-topic="4859">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/akabillposters/40/667_1.png" class="avatar"> akabillposters:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>One possible way around the possible skewing, or at least, to dampen its effect, might be to score/rate a track based on what % of people who listened to a track Liked it.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>I like this approach, but would there be a threshold of plays a track needs to have? I’ve listened to a lot of tracks in the community and most are not over 50 plays, some not over 10.</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/grandpamusic">@GrandpaMusic</a>’s <a href="https://soundcloud.com/avery-harness/spectroscope">Spectroscope</a><br>
Plays: 13(at the time writing this)<br>
Likes: 3<br>
SCore(as you’ve coined it): 23</p>
<p><a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/iaatoe">@IAATOE</a>’s  Reposted <a href="https://soundcloud.com/iaatoe/flow">Flow</a><br>
Plays: 208<br>
Likes:37<br>
SCore: 17.7</p>
<p>Granted, IAATOE’s Flow likely had a higher SCore before being reposted. The only two things SCore doesn’t account for is:<br>
1 One user playing a song more than one, devaluing it.<br>
2 repost</p>
<p>Anyways I think the SCore rating system would be worth seeing in action, two type of tracks will be valued by it; Hot tracks and tracks that need more exposure.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/28</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 09:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Aqzi]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Add chrome</p>
<div class="spoiler"><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/27">spoiler</a></div>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/27</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A process aiming to anonymise tracks, such as with the creation of a new SC account seems convoluted and high-maintenance.</p>
<p>Allowing members of the community to vote is an admirable ambition, but as others have mentioned, it runs into the problem of popular styles being likely to receive more appreciation, skewing the outcome in favour of those styles.*</p>
<p>That said, it’s worth trying it out to see if members really can vote neutrally - i.e. be as likely to vote for a good track from a genre they don’t like as a good track from their favourite/preferred genre.<br>
It’s unlikely, but worth trying out.</p>
<p>* One possible way around the possible skewing, or at least, to dampen its effect, might be to score/rate a track based on what % of people who listened to a track Liked it.</p>
<p>e.g.</p>
<p>Track 1 (popular genre, popular maker)<br>
Plays: 600, Likes: 300<br>
Score: 50%</p>
<p>Track 2 (less popular genre, lesser known maker)<br>
Plays: 40, Likes: 22<br>
Score: 55%</p>
<p>Winner: Track 2</p>
<p>It’s not perfect (the more nuance you build in, accounting for more factors, the more reliable it becomes as a quality rating tool), but as an approach in principle, it could level the playing field somewhat, compared to a direct ‘popular vote’ system.</p>
<p>Tracks could be nominated, then judged at the end on their ‘normalised’ SC performance (like:play ratio).</p>
<p>Anyhoo, just a thought.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/26</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 08:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Alyen]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="4859" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/this/40/3083_1.png" class="avatar"> THIS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what if the tracks wouldn’t be labeled. it would be just the music with a number.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Perhaps putting the entry tracks on one SC account would solve this problem.</p>
<p>I would prefer that more than one person would have access to this account, to oversight each other. I also think that those who would be putting this together and maintaining it, shouldn’t have a vote or an entry.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/25</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 01:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>good idea</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/24</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 23:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="22" data-topic="4859" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/notmiles/40/3685_1.png" class="avatar"> NotMiles:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>To add on to this, you’d see the title and artist once it links you to SoundCloud anyways.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Auxy might post it as an annonymous track… <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/man_shrugging.png?v=5" title=":man_shrugging:" class="emoji" alt=":man_shrugging:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/23</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To add on to this, you’d see the title and artist once it links you to SoundCloud anyways.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/22</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="19" data-topic="4859" data-full="true">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/this/40/3083_1.png" class="avatar"> THIS:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>what if the tracks wouldn’t be labeled. it would be just the music with a number.</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>people would still be able to tell their friends what track is theirs…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/21</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-21</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>In the grand scheme of things, I think we should let the developers find what they think is a good representation of the app. Imo it’s for the better.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/20</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-20</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[THIS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>what if the tracks wouldn’t be labeled. it would be just the music with a number.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/19</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-19</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote" data-post="17" data-topic="4859">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/newnames/40/3599_1.png" class="avatar"> NEWNAMES:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>is there a way to prevent this from happening?</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>That would be a nope</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/18</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-18</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NEWNAMES]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Wouldn’t there be patronage?</p>
<p>People would vote for their friends’ tracks…</p>
<p>I’m just wondering… is there a way to prevent this from happening?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/17</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-17</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well, r/Auxy is a thing that exists</p>
<p>More people use Disco tho</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/16</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-16</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>A reddit type thing</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/15</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-15</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Probably wouldn’t be on the disco though</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/14</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-14</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>So, people submit a song to a nomination thread and then people vote on it?</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/13</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-13</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Oooooohhhhhhh. That could work.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/12</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 20:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-12</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Hum4n01d]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>neither unless it was built into the disco somehow. this would be seperate</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859/11</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4859-11</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/nominating-voting-for-featured-tracks/4859.rss">Nominating/voting for featured tracks!?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
