<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471</link>
    <description>https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/project-destroyer-build-6

This isn&#39;t an official title, it&#39;s a title to vent my frustrations I have with the current build of Auxy. I&#39;ve talked about this within The Auxy Collective for _far_ too many times, it&#39;s honestly a chore to even use this app as something I genuinely enjoy using.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 01:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Work in Progress</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I see, I use strings minimally (that’s pretty obvious though) I rarely layer them. I will say the pitch adjustment has always been reliable. The new attack and release adjustments I thought would be useful but it’s really not the same as analog and knobs. Really I think they may jump the shark here, I really used Auxy for its simplicity originally and it was really something to do when not recording analog. Now every update seems to eliminate something and replace it with ten things. Hard to keep up with and to replicate accurately past sounds. That maybe why I remain genre less, Auxy is an experiment platform to me and given all the folks jumping to ableton and FL studio kinda shows that’s what it’s becoming for others I think.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/4">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/4</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16471-4</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471.rss">Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>To put it simply, the problem with this update that I personally experienced, and with others, is from the inability to replicate Auxy 5 when using the new automation tweaks.</p>
<p>I use strings pretty often because the style of trance that i’m producing does heavily use strings. At the moment, using the strings collection is a lot harder to use than how it was. I made a post awhile ago explaining this problem, but basically the strings don’t merge together as seamlessly as A5, you can audibly hear the attack in A6 now. Pads like silk was perfect for replicating strings and I do use it from time to time if I want to layer the long chords. Now it’s used for genres like future bass where silk was heavily used.</p>
<p>I did lightly use automation in A5, but I can’t use it as fluently as before, knowing that the automation nodes, or dots, don’t snap into equal value, with the exception of pitch. Right now, I can only do simple automation, reverting me back to when Auxy used “Transitions” rather than A5’s automation.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/3</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16471-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471.rss">Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Devoid-of-joy]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>What on the new build gives you trouble? I’m not saying it doesn’t have issues. Personally I was excited for the increased automations but in the end it’s execution isn’t exactly versatile. All the distortion kinda drowned out the same, and after my complaints of no delays on the drum kits they put them back in but it’s across the whole kit which pretty much sucks.<br>
As for this track, I dig it, I got excited with the 41 second run cause it takes me back to my cybergrind listening days.</p>
<p>P.s. if ya don’t want to reiterate on the issues, you don’t have to, I’m just not involved with the collective, I just don’t fit there.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 22:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16471-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471.rss">Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/project-destroyer-build-6" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/azureonyx/project-destroyer-build-6</a></p>
<p>This isn’t an official title, it’s a title to vent my frustrations I have with the current build of Auxy. I’ve talked about this within The Auxy Collective for <em>far</em> too many times, it’s honestly a chore to even use this app as something I genuinely enjoy using.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 09:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-16471-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/project-destroyer-build-6-azure-onyxscore-heavy-distortion/16471.rss">Project Destroyer Build 6 - Azure Onyxscore [Heavy Distortion]</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
