<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dos Mil Dieciocho (OSEM) - Mr Mooo [ALBUM] {Mainly Future Bass)</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/dos-mil-dieciocho-osem-mr-mooo-album-mainly-future-bass/13475</link>
    <description>Well guys... it&#39;s finally finished. OSEM has been such an awesome experience for me. It was interesting how much my style changed over this year. The album is mainly future bass but there is also some trap and some dance &amp;amp; EDM. 2018 was such an amazing year for me on Soundcloud, with over 11,000 plays, 1,000 likes and 400 comments. That blows my mind completely. I can&#39;t thank every single one of you guys who listens to my music enough for this. I&#39;m so grateful for all of you.

I hope you all had an amazing Christmas, and happy new year!

I can&#39;t wait for what 2019 will hold for me and for others. Get ready for some awesome uploads coming from me very soon though.

All these songs were 100% made with Auxy.

Link to album: &lt;bg&gt;https://soundcloud.com/mr_mooo/sets/osem&lt;/big&gt;

Reply with which song you like best!</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 08:17:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/dos-mil-dieciocho-osem-mr-mooo-album-mainly-future-bass/13475.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Dos Mil Dieciocho (OSEM) - Mr Mooo [ALBUM] {Mainly Future Bass)</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Mr_Mooo]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Well guys… it’s finally finished. OSEM has been such an awesome experience for me. It was interesting how much my style changed over this year. The album is mainly future bass but there is also some trap and some dance &amp; EDM. 2018 was such an amazing year for me on Soundcloud, with over 11,000 plays, 1,000 likes and 400 comments. That blows my mind completely. I can’t thank every single one of you guys who listens to my music enough for this. I’m so grateful for all of you.</p>
<p>I hope you all had an amazing Christmas, and happy new year!</p>
<p>I can’t wait for what 2019 will hold for me and for others. Get ready for some awesome uploads coming from me very soon though.</p>
<p>All these songs were 100% made with Auxy.</p>
<p>Link to album: <a href="https://soundcloud.com/mr_mooo/sets/osem" rel="nofollow noopener">https://soundcloud.com/mr_mooo/sets/osem</a></p>
<p>Reply with which song you like best!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/dos-mil-dieciocho-osem-mr-mooo-album-mainly-future-bass/13475/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/dos-mil-dieciocho-osem-mr-mooo-album-mainly-future-bass/13475/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 07:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-13475-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/dos-mil-dieciocho-osem-mr-mooo-album-mainly-future-bass/13475.rss">Dos Mil Dieciocho (OSEM) - Mr Mooo [ALBUM] {Mainly Future Bass)</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
