<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>The issue with downloading samples and instruments</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-issue-with-downloading-samples-and-instruments/17668</link>
    <description>I&#39;ve been setting up an iPad mini today, and decided to download Auxy onto it, however, upon its completion I was faced with an issue. Downloading all of the samples and instruments. Since there is no option to download all samples or instruments within specific categories, the entirety of specific sound and sample packs, or to download everything simultaneously with just one button, I had to go through each instrument and sample one by one and download it. Simply put, it didn&#39;t take long to become slightly annoying and tedious. There are well over 1000 samples, and to have to download them all this way should honestly have been dealt with by now. I ask that this be changed in a future version for the sake of convenience and saving people time. I&#39;m certain I&#39;m not the only person who would like this change, and hope something can be done to fix it.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 18:55:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Auxy Feedback</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-issue-with-downloading-samples-and-instruments/17668.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>The issue with downloading samples and instruments</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Nindota]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve been setting up an iPad mini today, and decided to download Auxy onto it, however, upon its completion I was faced with an issue. Downloading all of the samples and instruments. Since there is no option to download all samples or instruments within specific categories, the entirety of specific sound and sample packs, or to download everything simultaneously with just one button, I had to go through each instrument and sample one by one and download it. Simply put, it didn’t take long to become slightly annoying and tedious. There are well over 1000 samples, and to have to download them all this way should honestly have been dealt with by now. I ask that this be changed in a future version for the sake of convenience and saving people time. I’m certain I’m not the only person who would like this change, and hope something can be done to fix it.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-issue-with-downloading-samples-and-instruments/17668/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-issue-with-downloading-samples-and-instruments/17668/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-17668-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/the-issue-with-downloading-samples-and-instruments/17668.rss">The issue with downloading samples and instruments</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
