<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Eohr - tired of waiting</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/eohr-tired-of-waiting/21636</link>
    <description>HI EVERYBODY!!!! I&#39;m back. This is weird. Haven&#39;t posted on here in a while and I think the community has probably changed a super ton, but I figured I could share this song cause I know you all would be interested probably hopefully!

I love Auxy and I don&#39;t think I&#39;ll ever really completely stop making music with it. This summer was a lull because I released my debut album of like &quot;real songs&quot; and I&#39;m putting out an EP at the end of this month with more cool stuff I&#39;ve been making in Logic, but for now, I hope you all enjoy this nice melodic pretty (&quot;future bass&quot;?) track I made in April 2021.

https://soundcloud.com/eohr/tired-of-waiting</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 06:25:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Post Your Tracks</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/eohr-tired-of-waiting/21636.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Eohr - tired of waiting</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[eohr]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>HI EVERYBODY!!! I’m back. This is weird. Haven’t posted on here in a while and I think the community has probably changed a super ton, but I figured I could share this song cause I know you all would be interested probably hopefully!</p>
<p>I love Auxy and I don’t think I’ll ever really completely stop making music with it. This summer was a lull because I released my debut album of like “real songs” and I’m putting out an EP at the end of this month with more cool stuff I’ve been making in Logic, but for now, I hope you all enjoy this nice melodic pretty (“future bass”?) track I made in April 2021.</p>
<p><a href="https://soundcloud.com/eohr/tired-of-waiting" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">https://soundcloud.com/eohr/tired-of-waiting</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/eohr-tired-of-waiting/21636/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/eohr-tired-of-waiting/21636/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 06:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-21636-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/eohr-tired-of-waiting/21636.rss">Eohr - tired of waiting</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
