<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535</link>
    <description>Tornait here. I’m starting to feel out of it. Ever since I’ve posted What So, I’ve looked at my other songs, and started to feel that the rest of my music was... lackluster, or just generally unaccepted. Case in point, my latest release, War Head. I think it’s a nice track, but then I look at the ratings of the track compared to all my others. 

Like all creators should feel, I love creating and posting new songs. I pour out passion into every song I make. One thing I’d like people to understand is... Whenever people like a song I post, it gives me motivation to make more. Whenever people leave my stuff alone, however, it gives me self-doubt, and puts me into a funk.

Yeah, I’m pretty eccentric with my styles.

Maybe I am too eccentric with my styles. But the real question is... Do you guys enjoy **all** of my music? Is there anything that I have to change? Do **I** have to change?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:15:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Production Talk</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Akyut]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Music doesn’t need to be technical to be good. Most, if not all enjoyment found in music is completely subjective, hence why people like some genres and dislike others.</p>
<p>Now, for my personal opinion on this : If you make music for the numbers, you shouldn’t bother in the first place. In my eyes, music is passion given form. A little cheesy, I know, but it gets the point across. If I feel myself start to stagnate, then I change it up. If I enjoy what I’m producing at the time, then I take that as a good sign and continue forward with the project.</p>
<p>Out of every five projects I finish, only one will be uploaded to my soundcloud. It’s not for lack of quality, it’s because I don’t feel anything when I listen to those tracks. Hell, I’ve had a couple pieces I’ve spent weeks on, only to at the last minute grow bored with the track and move on to the next. I don’t think it’s a waste of time though, because from every track I create I learn something new.</p>
<p>When the rare track I do publish comes along, I’m then able to incorporate new elements into my style, and then I build on top of that. If you feel yourself plateauing, don’t give up on music, instead take inspiration from elsewhere and create something you feel good about! As long as it means something to you, it can be considered good music.</p>
<p>Holy crap that was a rant, sorry for the long response! Probably went on a couple tangents too, whoops <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/sweat_smile.png?v=5" title=":sweat_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":sweat_smile:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/32">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/32</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-32</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Bassment_Chemists]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Im not sure why you are being so hard on yourself, I immensely liked your missionaries track man, lots of great stuff going on there. I hope the colabs reinvigorate your creative spark mate</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/29">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/29</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 03:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-29</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Db909]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Haters gonna hate,fakers gonna fake. I think Taytay said that.  Just keep making the music you enjoy making and learn all you can along the way, and don’t judge your music based on SoundCloud stuff.  YOU know when you did a good job or when you slacked a bit, the right audience might not have found your stuff yet</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/28">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/28</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 00:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-28</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[6Strings]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude thats absolutely brilliant!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/27">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/27</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 23:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-27</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>For everyone here… thank you all. You guys have inspired me to start work on even greater tracks, to finally get into my groove again.</p>
<p><a href="https://app.auxy.co/projects/Ezb_uXn-Pa3Z5smRfdnW6A==" rel="nofollow noopener">https://app.auxy.co/projects/Ezb_uXn-Pa3Z5smRfdnW6A==</a> Here’s a demo of my latest project. Hope you enjoy.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/26">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/26</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 19:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-26</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[akabillposters]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>My advice would be to keep making <em>your</em> music, be pro-active about improving your production skills (to better translate what’s in your head into tracks) - and don’t be too focussed on ‘success’ as measured within the reach of this community.</p>
<p>This community is still very small, and currently has certain leanings in terms of what’s popular. Due to the small size of the community, that can sometimes have what feels like a disproportionate effect on how much attention one might feel they’re getting.</p>
<p>Expand your horizons. Seek out other forums/groups to join <em>as well</em> - ideally ones that are focussed on the style of music you make or your approach to music, rather than the tool you use.</p>
<p>Calibrate your own expectations for your music. Focus on what’s most important — at this time. Is it popularity or quality?<br>
(Quality doesn’t always lead to popularity, and popularity doesn’t always mean quality.)</p>
<p>Set yourself some goals, whether that’s to improve production, to seek out other (additional) places where your music might resonate more, or be more active about promotion.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
Another thing I’d consider…</p>
<p>If your music would benefit from production options, sounds, whatever… that aren’t available within Auxy, don’t be afraid to switch to a tool that’s better suited.</p>
<p>I think Auxy is outstanding for initial idea generation and development, but in some cases, it may be holding back your music from being its best form. (It’s why I don’t consider anything that I’ve done in Auxy to be in its final form.)</p>
<p>So, don’t limit your thinking to what can be achieved in Auxy or what Auxy makes easy.<br>
<span class="bbcode-u">Make your <em>music</em> the priority</span> – and use whichever tool is best for helping you get there.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<br>
There are some worthwhile articles aimed at improving writing and production here…</p>
<p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/post-writing-and-production-tips-links-embeds-only/2333/">https://disco.auxy.co/t/post-writing-and-production-tips-links-embeds-only/2333/</a></p>
<p>There are also practical things you can start doing to increase the size of your audience, which will help your chances of getting appreciation and traction.</p>
<p><a href="https://blog.landr.com/?s=promotion" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://blog.landr.com/?s=promotion</a><br>
<a href="https://blog.landr.com/8-ways-actually-get-heard-soundcloud/" class="onebox" target="_blank">https://blog.landr.com/8-ways-actually-get-heard-soundcloud/</a></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/25">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/25</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 08:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-25</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BobTheGUYYYYY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Do you feel supported now?<br>
FEEL SUPPORTED!<br>
THAT’S AN ORDER! <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/laughing.png?v=5" title=":laughing:" class="emoji" alt=":laughing:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/24">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/24</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-24</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[NotMiles]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Naw man, there’s nothing wrong with your style. I think it’s safe to say everyone here has gone through a period where they feel as though their music isn’t good enough, that it’s lackluster, as you said. It’s times like those where it’s a good idea to take a step back and think about your motivations for making music. Are you doing this for likes, comments, followers, or those sweet, sweet, Auxy reposts? Or are you doing this because you just love making music, because it’s your passion? If it’s the latter, then likes and reposts, (while they still are really nice to get) shouldn’t matter if you are creating music that you enjoy making and listening to. My belief is that if you put every bit of passion into whatever you do, the attention will come. <strong>It just takes time.</strong></p>
<p>On the subject of improvement, I’ll give you the same advice you gave me, listen to the pros or even other members of this forum to get inspiration. Try to do some of the things they do in your music. One thing that’s really helped me lately is watching Andrew Huang’s YouTube videos. They give me tons of ideas of new stuff to try out in my music and also they’re a really cool look into the creative process of a professional musician.</p>
<p>Do I enjoy your music? Hell yeah I do! I didn’t follow ya for nothing! Do I enjoy <strong>all</strong> of your music? Well, Imma just say this: there are a ton of artists that I love listen to, but I don’t like every single song that they put out. That would be kinda crazy (I think). I love about 90% of their stuff. Sure, some songs may not hit the mark, but I’ll still be a fan after I hear a song that I didn’t quite like. I’ll still get excited when their (your) next new song shows up on my SoundCloud feed.</p>
<p>Don’t be too hard on yourself, man. Remember, music-making is supposed to be fun!</p>
<p>That is all.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/23">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/23</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-23</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[SUFOS]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Just to the things you like to do. You can’t do it wrong.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/22">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/22</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-22</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[DKsounds]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Ive come to that feeling before too, m8, but i just kept with it and i started learning with every track i put out. Just keep doing what you are doing and learn more as you go!<img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/hugs.png?v=5" title=":hugs:" class="emoji" alt=":hugs:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/21">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/21</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-21</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Thanks for the feedback. Honestly, I don’t really have the patience of a saint, and automation sometimes confuses me and feels too… involved. Hopefully I can get to the point where automation feels better for me.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/20">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/20</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-20</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Southborne]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Dude! It’s literally just experience and being around longer… you’ll improve as you journey with you technique and style. Push it bro</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/19">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/19</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 05:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-19</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BobTheGUYYYYY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’m down!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/18">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/18</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 05:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-18</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Maybe that would lift my spirits. I’ve already started a few collabs with quite a few good people, but now they’re (almost) all busy. So… I could do with something like this.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/17">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/17</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 05:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-17</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[6Strings]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey. How about a collab eh? Maybe another person join us as well. THEN we make some beautiful stuff!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/16">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/16</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 05:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-16</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[enby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Of course! I’ve done a lot of different stuff from writing to painting. The communities that I entered helped keep me going so I understand how nice it is to get support and encouragement from others.</p>
<p>Furthermore, I appreciate your drive to be a serious musician. However, don’t forget to have fun too. It doesn’t hurt to take a break every once and a while in order to collab with others and participate in competitions. That’s my favorite part of this forum, honestly.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/15">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/15</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-15</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright. You’ve made valid points. And I am constantly seeking to perfect my sound, and get better overall. Thanks for hearing me out.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/14">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/14</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-14</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[enby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>When you say talent, you mean experience. Like I said, a lot of the well received users on here have been here for a while and have been making music for a while. The more music you make, the sooner you’ll pick up their tricks. You can also always read about methods here on the forum and on other sights too. You make good tracks and it’d be a shame to give up now. Eccentric or not, it doesn’t matter. The music you make is about you, not the numbers they generate.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/13">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/13</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-13</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>True. But I listen to the stuff this community makes, and I’m amazed by it. When I post a track, there’s two clashing forces in my mind: optimism and cynicism. Cynicism usually wins out, especially compared to the sheer talent other users have with the app. I guess I’m just not technical enough. And that’s why I feel like my music is… too eccentric to be accepted.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/12">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/12</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-12</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BobTheGUYYYYY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>It’s all good. Keep having fun!</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/11">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/11</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-11</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[enby]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Still, releasing stuff on your SC for a year isn’t a very long time. You’ve only just begun. If you feel like you’re getting bored with your music, then maybe try some new things. Music is a journey.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/10">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/10</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-10</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[AzureOnyx]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Sometimes, Auxy doesn’t have enough sounds. <a class="mention" href="https://disco.auxy.co/u/Auxy">@Auxy</a>, what’s next for AP-002? Definately need new sounds in Auxy</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/9">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/9</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-9</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Alright, and thanks for the kind words. I’m just a guy with low self-esteem and lots of out-there ideas. And maybe a little bit of jealousy issues.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/8">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/8</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-8</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[tornait]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I’ve only joined this Disco on October the 11th, but my SoundCloud account has been around for over a year now. I guess it’s because I was such a late adopter of this Disco…</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/7">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/7</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-7</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I feel like I’ve plateaued</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[BobTheGUYYYYY]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Don’t worry about it. I make unrecognized, mediocre music all the time! But I never get discouraged- because it’s just fun to use Auxy. Even if it’s your ambition, you don’t have to be one of those people who gets featured every time for everything, or gets a billion likes on all their songs. It shouldn’t matter to you if you enjoy making music.</p>
<p>Hey, I thought War Head was pretty cool.</p>
<p>So… you can take this advice or not… but… I’d just say, relax. You just need to enjoy the ride. <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/wink.png?v=5" title=":wink:" class="emoji" alt=":wink:"></p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/6">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535/6</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 04:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-4535-6</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/i-feel-like-i-ve-plateaued/4535.rss">I feel like I’ve plateaued</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
