<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>How to Make Money with YouTube </title>
    <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833</link>
    <description>This is adapted from my blog, https://norfleetmusic.wordpress.com! If you&#39;re interested in music distribution you will probably like it, and I plan to post more in the coming weeks. Feel free to check it out!

---

Hey all,

I was pretty surprised at how many likes the post about Spotify got, so I decided to make another one. Today I&#39;m going to talk a little bit about how YouTube works with monetization. I know a little more about that, so it should be easier.

Three types of monetization on YouTube:
1. YouTube Partner Program
2. Content ID
3. Multi-Channel Network (MCN)

## YouTube Partner Program

If you know about monetization on YouTube, chances are it&#39;s this kind. If your channel meets their minimum requirements, you can apply to join the **YouTube Partner Program**, which gives you access to extra features, including monetization of your channel.

As of early 2018, to join the YPP, you must meet the following requirements:
1. At least 1,000 subscribers to your channel
2. At least 4,000 hours of watch time in the past 365 days on your channel
3. You abide by the Terms &amp; Conditions of YouTube

They review every channel manually, after applying filters for spam, as well as lack of meeting the requirements.

I&#39;m not in the YPP, so I do not know as much about it. If anybody is, please reply and don&#39;t hesitate to share your knowledge!

## Content ID

Content ID is a system created by YouTube that detects copyrighted content automatically whenever a YouTube video is uploaded. Content ID can be content from TV shows or movies, but it is usually sound recordings or music.

When content is detected, the following things can happen:
1. Analytics tracking. The label or aggregator who claims the content will have access to normally private analytics. This is not very commonly used.
2. Monetization. Ads will be placed on the video, and the revenue distributed to the label or aggregator. This is the default for most aggregators and labels.
3. Blocking. This is mainly used by large record labels such as Warner or Sony, and TV networks, notably the BBC.
4. Revenue sharing. This option is only available to already monetized videos (not including Content ID claims). Instead of claiming all revenue from the video, a percentage will be given to the channel owner, and a percentage to the claimant. This is usually used for manually detected cover songs, though it is also used for other purposes.

Most aggregators are partnered with YouTube and can upload your music to Content ID if you own the rights to it.

If your video or stream receives a claim, you are allowed to dispute it if you believe it is wrong. You can also remove the song with YouTube&#39;s built-in feature.

## Multi-Channel Network

A multi-channel network (MCN) is a company that trades a cut of ad revenue for features such as a higher monetization rate, exclusive promotion tools, built-in monetization, etc. 

The main benefit of an MCN is that monetization is guaranteed, regardless of the size of the channel. While most MCNs are generally private and only available to users who would _already_ be large enough to monetize their content, MCNs are able to monetize all channels, no matter the size.

Like the YPP, I am not affiliated with an MCN, so my knowledge is certainly limited.

## Conclusion

Hope this was helpful. For smaller creators, I would say that Content ID is your best bet to earn money through YouTube — it helps that it&#39;s fairly easily accessible through most aggregators.

If you have any questions or need some help, please send me a DM! I&#39;d be happy to help.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:19:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Branding &amp; Distribution</category>
    <atom:link href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>How to Make Money with YouTube </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[stereofield]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <aside class="quote no-group" data-post="1" data-topic="9833">
<div class="title">
<div class="quote-controls"></div>
<img alt="" width="20" height="20" src="https://sjc6.discourse-cdn.com/standard10/user_avatar/disco.auxy.co/norfleet/40/7481_1.png" class="avatar"> Norfleet:</div>
<blockquote>
<p>I’m not in the YPP, so I do not know as much about it. If anybody is, please reply and don’t hesitate to share your knowledge!</p>
</blockquote>
</aside>
<p>Used to be <img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/apple/roll_eyes.png?v=5" title=":roll_eyes:" class="emoji" alt=":roll_eyes:"> but then right after they accepted me they changed their minimum and pulled me out</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/3">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/3</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9833-3</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833.rss">How to Make Money with YouTube </source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Make Money with YouTube </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Produk]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>just hit 1k subs on the channel, might monetize in the future if I can start doing consistent content over the summer</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 21:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9833-2</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833.rss">How to Make Money with YouTube </source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>How to Make Money with YouTube </title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Norfleet]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>This is adapted from my blog, <a href="https://norfleetmusic.wordpress.com" rel="nofollow noopener">https://norfleetmusic.wordpress.com</a>! If you’re interested in music distribution you will probably like it, and I plan to post more in the coming weeks. Feel free to check it out!</p>
<hr>
<p>Hey all,</p>
<p>I was pretty surprised at how many likes the post about Spotify got, so I decided to make another one. Today I’m going to talk a little bit about how YouTube works with monetization. I know a little more about that, so it should be easier.</p>
<p>Three types of monetization on YouTube:</p>
<ol>
<li>YouTube Partner Program</li>
<li>Content ID</li>
<li>Multi-Channel Network (MCN)</li>
</ol>
<h2>YouTube Partner Program</h2>
<p>If you know about monetization on YouTube, chances are it’s this kind. If your channel meets their minimum requirements, you can apply to join the <strong>YouTube Partner Program</strong>, which gives you access to extra features, including monetization of your channel.</p>
<p>As of early 2018, to join the YPP, you must meet the following requirements:</p>
<ol>
<li>At least 1,000 subscribers to your channel</li>
<li>At least 4,000 hours of watch time in the past 365 days on your channel</li>
<li>You abide by the Terms &amp; Conditions of YouTube</li>
</ol>
<p>They review every channel manually, after applying filters for spam, as well as lack of meeting the requirements.</p>
<p>I’m not in the YPP, so I do not know as much about it. If anybody is, please reply and don’t hesitate to share your knowledge!</p>
<h2>Content ID</h2>
<p>Content ID is a system created by YouTube that detects copyrighted content automatically whenever a YouTube video is uploaded. Content ID can be content from TV shows or movies, but it is usually sound recordings or music.</p>
<p>When content is detected, the following things can happen:</p>
<ol>
<li>Analytics tracking. The label or aggregator who claims the content will have access to normally private analytics. This is not very commonly used.</li>
<li>Monetization. Ads will be placed on the video, and the revenue distributed to the label or aggregator. This is the default for most aggregators and labels.</li>
<li>Blocking. This is mainly used by large record labels such as Warner or Sony, and TV networks, notably the BBC.</li>
<li>Revenue sharing. This option is only available to already monetized videos (not including Content ID claims). Instead of claiming all revenue from the video, a percentage will be given to the channel owner, and a percentage to the claimant. This is usually used for manually detected cover songs, though it is also used for other purposes.</li>
</ol>
<p>Most aggregators are partnered with YouTube and can upload your music to Content ID if you own the rights to it.</p>
<p>If your video or stream receives a claim, you are allowed to dispute it if you believe it is wrong. You can also remove the song with YouTube’s built-in feature.</p>
<h2>Multi-Channel Network</h2>
<p>A multi-channel network (MCN) is a company that trades a cut of ad revenue for features such as a higher monetization rate, exclusive promotion tools, built-in monetization, etc.</p>
<p>The main benefit of an MCN is that monetization is guaranteed, regardless of the size of the channel. While most MCNs are generally private and only available to users who would <em>already</em> be large enough to monetize their content, MCNs are able to monetize all channels, no matter the size.</p>
<p>Like the YPP, I am not affiliated with an MCN, so my knowledge is certainly limited.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Hope this was helpful. For smaller creators, I would say that Content ID is your best bet to earn money through YouTube — it helps that it’s fairly easily accessible through most aggregators.</p>
<p>If you have any questions or need some help, please send me a DM! I’d be happy to help.</p>
          <p><a href="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 16:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">disco.auxy.co-post-9833-1</guid>
        <source url="https://disco.auxy.co/t/how-to-make-money-with-youtube/9833.rss">How to Make Money with YouTube </source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
